<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Summaries by David Barrett on Shortened Books</title>
    <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/contributors/david-barrett/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book Summaries by David Barrett on Shortened Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 17:58:56 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shortenedbooks.com/contributors/david-barrett/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Covert Passive-Aggressive Narcissist Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Debbie Mirza</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-covert-passive-aggressive-narcissist-by-debbie-mirza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 17:58:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-covert-passive-aggressive-narcissist-by-debbie-mirza/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Covert Passive-Aggressive Narcissist: Recognizing the Traits and Finding Healing After Hidden Emotional and Psychological Abuse&amp;rdquo; is a comprehensive guide written by Debbie Mirza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Kill A Narcissist Summary of Key Ideas and Review - JH Simon</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-kill-a-narcissist-by-jh-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 17:29:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-kill-a-narcissist-by-jh-simon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How To Kill A Narcissist: Debunking The Myth Of Narcissism And Recovering From Narcissistic Abuse&amp;rdquo; by JH Simon is a compelling and insightful guide that delves deep into the world of narcissism and its pervasive effects on individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Science of Narcissism Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Keith Campbell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-new-science-of-narcissism-by-keith-campbell-carolyn-crist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 13:42:52 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-new-science-of-narcissism-by-keith-campbell-carolyn-crist/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The New Science of Narcissism: Understanding One of the Greatest Psychological Challenges of Our Time—and What You Can Do About It&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book that delves into the complex world of narcissism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All My Knotted-Up Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Beth Moore</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/all-my-knotted-up-life-by-beth-moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:07:59 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/all-my-knotted-up-life-by-beth-moore/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;All My Knotted-Up Life: A Memoir&amp;rdquo; by Beth Moore is a poignant and introspective journey into the life of the renowned author, speaker, and Bible teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Return to Love Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Marianne Williamson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-return-to-love-by-marianne-williamson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:31:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-return-to-love-by-marianne-williamson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Return to Love: Reflections on the Principles of a Course in Miracles&amp;rdquo; by Marianne Williamson is a profound exploration of spiritual concepts and the transformative power of love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Earth Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eckhart Tolle</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-new-earth-by-eckhart-tolle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:08:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-new-earth-by-eckhart-tolle/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A New Earth: Awakening to Your Life’s Purpose&amp;rdquo; is a profound spiritual manifesto written by Eckhart Tolle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Force for Good Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Goleman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-force-for-good-by-daniel-goleman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 06:11:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-force-for-good-by-daniel-goleman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Force for Good: The Dalai Lama’s Vision for Humanity,&amp;rdquo; written by Daniel Goleman, delves into the profound insights and wisdom of the Dalai Lama, the spiritual leader of Tibet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Your Best Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Carey Nieuwhof</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/at-your-best-by-carey-nieuwhof/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 01:53:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/at-your-best-by-carey-nieuwhof/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;At Your Best: How to Get Time, Energy, and Priorities Working in Your Favor&amp;rdquo; by Carey Nieuwhof is a transformative guide that unveils the key principles and strategies required to optimize your time, harness your energy, and align your priorities to achieve peak performance and fulfillment in both your personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altered Traits Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Goleman and Richard J. Davidson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/altered-traits-by-daniel-goleman-richard-davidson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:50:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/altered-traits-by-daniel-goleman-richard-davidson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Altered Traits: Science Reveals How Meditation Changes Your Mind, Brain, and Body&amp;rdquo; by Daniel Goleman and Richard Davidson is a captivating exploration into the transformative power of meditation on the human mind, brain, and body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Monk&#39;s Guide to Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gelong Thubten</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-monk-s-guide-to-happiness-by-gelong-thubten/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:50:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-monk-s-guide-to-happiness-by-gelong-thubten/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Monk&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Happiness: Meditation in the 21st Century&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking and insightful book that delves into the pursuit of happiness and the transformative power of meditation in our modern world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Secrets to Powerful Manifesting Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mandy Morris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/8-secrets-to-powerful-manifesting-by-mandy-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:29:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/8-secrets-to-powerful-manifesting-by-mandy-morris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;8 Secrets to Powerful Manifesting&amp;rdquo; by Mandy Morris is an enlightening and empowering self-help book that delves into the art of manifestation and how to create the life you desire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24/6 Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tiffany Shlain</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/24-6-by-tiffany-shlain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:01:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/24-6-by-tiffany-shlain/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;24/6: The Power of Unplugging One Day a Week&amp;rdquo; by Tiffany Shlain is a thought-provoking and timely exploration of the importance of disconnecting from technology for one day each week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18 Minutes Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Peter Bregman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/18-minutes-by-peter-bregman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:21:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/18-minutes-by-peter-bregman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;18 Minutes&amp;rdquo; is a compelling self-help book written by Peter Bregman, aiming to guide readers toward better time management, focus, and productivity in their personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He Can Who Thinks He Can Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Orison Swett Marden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/he-can-who-thinks-he-can-by-orison-swett-marden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 18:26:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/he-can-who-thinks-he-can-by-orison-swett-marden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;He Can Who Thinks He Can: And Other Papers on Success in Life&amp;rdquo; by Orison Swett Marden is a timeless and inspirational self-help book that delves into the power of positive thinking and the immense potential that lies within each individual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rhythm of Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matthew Kelly</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-rhythm-of-life-by-matthew-kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:00:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-rhythm-of-life-by-matthew-kelly/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Rhythm of Life: Living Every Day with Passion &amp;amp; Purpose&amp;rdquo; by Matthew Kelly is a self-help book that aims to inspire individuals to live with intention, passion, and a sense of purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Essence of Success Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Earl Nightingale</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-essence-of-success-by-earl-nightingale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:07:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-essence-of-success-by-earl-nightingale/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Essence of Success&amp;rdquo; by Earl Nightingale is a motivational and self-help book that aims to guide readers towards achieving success and fulfillment in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thich Nhat Hanh</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/silence-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:44:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/silence-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Silence: The Power of Quiet in a World Full of Noise&amp;rdquo; by Thich Nhat Hanh is a profound and enlightening book that explores the transformative power of silence in our modern, noisy world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choose the Life You Want Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tal Ben-Shahar</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/choose-the-life-you-want-by-tal-ben-shahar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:44:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/choose-the-life-you-want-by-tal-ben-shahar/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Choose the Life You Want: The Mindful Way to Happiness&amp;rdquo; by Tal Ben-Shahar is a self-help book that offers practical guidance on how to cultivate happiness and fulfillment in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do the Work Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Pressfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/do-the-work-by-steven-pressfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:30:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/do-the-work-by-steven-pressfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do the Work: Overcome Resistance and Get Out of Your Own Way&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and practical guide written by Steven Pressfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toughness Training for Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Loehr</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/toughness-training-for-life-by-james-loehr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:42:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/toughness-training-for-life-by-james-loehr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Toughness Training for Life: A Revolutionary Program for Maximizing Health, Happiness, and Productivity&amp;rdquo; by James Loehr is a self-help book that explores the concept of toughness and how it can be developed to improve various aspects of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Way of the Fight Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Georges St-Pierre</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-fight-by-georges-st-pierre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:31:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-fight-by-georges-st-pierre/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Way of the Fight&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Georges St-Pierre, a Canadian mixed martial artist and former UFC welterweight champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Good Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steve Chandler</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/crazy-good-by-steve-chandler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:08:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/crazy-good-by-steve-chandler/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Crazy Good: A Book of CHOICES&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Steve Chandler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bulletproof Diet Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dave Asprey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-bulletproof-diet-by-dave-asprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:41:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-bulletproof-diet-by-dave-asprey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Bulletproof Diet: Lose up to a Pound a Day, Reclaim Energy and Focus, Upgrade Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Dave Asprey, a biohacker and entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Motivation Manifesto Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brendon Burchard</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-motivation-manifesto-by-brendon-burchard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:37:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-motivation-manifesto-by-brendon-burchard/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Motivation Manifesto: 9 Declarations to Claim Your Personal Power&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Brendon Burchard, a renowned motivational speaker and personal development trainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-theories Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Carol Dweck</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/self-theories-by-carol-dweck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:17:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/self-theories-by-carol-dweck/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Self-theories: Their Role in Motivation, Personality, and Development&amp;rdquo; by Carol S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage Your Day-to-Day Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jocelyn Glei</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/manage-your-day-to-day-by-jocelyn-glei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:35:14 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/manage-your-day-to-day-by-jocelyn-glei/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Manage Your Day-to-Day: Build Your Routine, Find Your Focus, and Sharpen Your Creative Mind&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book edited by Jocelyn Glei.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Fully Charged? Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Rath</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/are-you-fully-charged-by-tom-rath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:09:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/are-you-fully-charged-by-tom-rath/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Are You Fully Charged?: The 3 Keys to Energizing Your Work and Life&amp;rdquo; by Tom Rath is a self-help book that focuses on three essential elements that contribute to a fulfilled and energized life: meaning, interactions, and energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shallows Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Nicholas Carr</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-shallows-by-nicholas-carr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:28:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-shallows-by-nicholas-carr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Shallows: What the Internet Is Doing to Our Brains&amp;rdquo; is an insightful book written by Nicholas Carr, exploring the impact of the internet on our cognitive abilities and the way we think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Brain at Work Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Rock</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/your-brain-at-work-by-david-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:02:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/your-brain-at-work-by-david-rock/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Your Brain at Work: Strategies for Overcoming Distraction, Regaining Focus, and Working Smarter All Day Long&amp;rdquo; by David Rock is an excellent guide that explores the intricacies of the human brain and provides practical strategies for improving productivity and effectiveness in the workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passage Meditation Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/passage-meditation-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 10:10:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/passage-meditation-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Passage Meditation&amp;rdquo; is a profound and practical guidebook written by Eknath Easwaran, a renowned spiritual teacher, author, and translator of Indian classics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Through Stillness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Russell Simmons and Chris Morrow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/success-through-stillness-by-russell-simmons-chris-morrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:43:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/success-through-stillness-by-russell-simmons-chris-morrow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Success Through Stillness: Meditation Made Simple&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Russell Simmons and Chris Morrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clean Gut Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Alejandro Junger</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/clean-gut-by-alejandro-junger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 19:51:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/clean-gut-by-alejandro-junger/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Clean Gut: The Breakthrough Plan for Eliminating the Root Cause of Disease and Revolutionizing Your Health&amp;rdquo; by Alejandro Junger is a comprehensive guide that explores the connection between gut health and overall well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sleep Revolution Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Arianna Huffington</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-sleep-revolution-by-arianna-huffington/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 16:31:41 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-sleep-revolution-by-arianna-huffington/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Sleep Revolution: Transforming Your Life, One Night at a Time&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Arianna Huffington, the co-founder and editor-in-chief of The Huffington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robert Cialdini</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/influence-by-robert-cialdini/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:37:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/influence-by-robert-cialdini/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Influence: The Psychology of Persuasion&amp;rdquo; is a bestselling book written by Robert Cialdini, a renowned social psychologist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miracle of Mindfulness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thich Nhat Hanh</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:59:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Miracle of Mindfulness: An Introduction to the Practice of Meditation&amp;rdquo; is a renowned book written by Thich Nhat Hanh, a Vietnamese Buddhist monk, teacher, and peace activist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultra Mindset Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Travis Macy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-ultra-mindset-by-travis-macy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:30:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-ultra-mindset-by-travis-macy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Ultra Mindset: An Endurance Champion&amp;rsquo;s 8 Core Principles for Success in Business, Sports, and Life&amp;rdquo; by Travis Macy is a compelling book that explores the mindset required to achieve success in various aspects of life, drawing insights from the author&amp;rsquo;s experience as an endurance athlete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Road to Sparta Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dean Karnazes</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-road-to-sparta-by-dean-karnazes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:22:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-road-to-sparta-by-dean-karnazes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Road to Sparta: Reliving the Ancient Battle and Epic Run That Inspired the World&amp;rsquo;s Greatest Footrace&amp;rdquo; is a non-fiction book written by Dean Karnazes, an accomplished ultra-marathon runner and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brian Tracy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/goals-by-brian-tracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 08:40:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/goals-by-brian-tracy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Goals!: How to Get Everything You Want—Faster Than You Ever Thought Possible&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Brian Tracy, a renowned author and motivational speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brain Warrior&#39;s Way Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Daniel Amen and Tana Amen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-brain-warrior-s-way-by-daniel-amen-tana-amen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:46:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-brain-warrior-s-way-by-daniel-amen-tana-amen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Brain Warrior&amp;rsquo;s Way: Ignite Your Energy and Focus, Attack Illness and Aging, Transform Pain into Purpose&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Daniel Amen and Tana Amen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pursuing the Good Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Christopher Peterson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/pursuing-the-good-life-by-christopher-peterson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:31:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/pursuing-the-good-life-by-christopher-peterson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Pursuing the Good Life: 100 Reflections on Positive Psychology&amp;rdquo; by Christopher Peterson is a thought-provoking book that explores the principles and practices of positive psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Track Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Emma Seppälä</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-track-by-emma-seppala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:17:40 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-track-by-emma-seppala/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness Track: How to Apply the Science of Happiness to Accelerate Your Success&amp;rdquo; by Emma Seppälä is a self-help book that explores the relationship between happiness and success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathe In, Breathe Out Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Loehr and Jeffrey Migdow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/breathe-in-breathe-out-by-james-loehr-jeffrey-migdow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 06:39:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/breathe-in-breathe-out-by-james-loehr-jeffrey-migdow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Breathe In, Breathe Out: Inhale Energy and Exhale Stress by Guiding and Controlling Your Breathing&amp;rdquo; by James Loehr and Jeffrey Migdow is a comprehensive guide that explores the power of conscious breathing techniques in promoting physical and mental well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Live on 24 Hours a Day Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Arnold Bennett</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-live-on-24-hours-a-day-by-arnold-bennett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:40:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-live-on-24-hours-a-day-by-arnold-bennett/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Live on 24 Hours a Day&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Arnold Bennett and first published in 1910.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Emperor of All Maladies Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Siddhartha Mukherjee</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-emperor-of-all-maladies-by-siddhartha-mukherjee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:00:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-emperor-of-all-maladies-by-siddhartha-mukherjee/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Emperor of All Maladies: A Biography of Cancer&amp;rdquo; by Siddhartha Mukherjee is a profound exploration of the history, science, and impact of cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Influence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Pantalon</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/instant-influence-by-michael-pantalon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 09:08:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/instant-influence-by-michael-pantalon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Instant Influence: How to Get Anyone to Do Anything&amp;hellip;Fast&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Michael Pantalon, a psychologist and expert in motivational interviewing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Morning Routine Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Benjamin Spall and Michael Xander</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/my-morning-routine-by-benjamin-spall-michael-xander/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:36:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/my-morning-routine-by-benjamin-spall-michael-xander/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;My Morning Routine: How Successful People Start Every Day Inspired&amp;rdquo; is a book co-authored by Benjamin Spall and Michael Xander.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Overfat Pandemic Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Philip Maffetone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-overfat-pandemic-by-philip-maffetone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:41:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-overfat-pandemic-by-philip-maffetone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Overfat Pandemic: Exposing the Problem and Its Simple Solution for Everyone Who Needs to Eliminate Excess Body Fat&amp;rdquo; by Philip Maffetone is a book that tackles the issue of overfat, which refers to individuals who have excess body fat that negatively impacts their health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Longitude Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dava Sobel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/longitude-by-dava-sobel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:56:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/longitude-by-dava-sobel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Longitude: The True Story of a Lone Genius Who Solved the Greatest Scientific Problem of His Time&amp;rdquo; by Dava Sobel is a non-fiction book that tells the captivating story of the quest to solve the problem of determining longitude at sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discipline Equals Freedom Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jocko Willink</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/discipline-equals-freedom-by-jocko-willink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 09:42:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/discipline-equals-freedom-by-jocko-willink/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Discipline Equals Freedom: Field Manual Mk1-MOD1&amp;rdquo; is a motivational self-help book written by retired Navy SEAL officer Jocko Willink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Practicing Stoic Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ward Farnsworth</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-practicing-stoic-by-ward-farnsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 08:29:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-practicing-stoic-by-ward-farnsworth/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Practicing Stoic: A Philosophical User&amp;rsquo;s Manual&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Ward Farnsworth that delves into the principles and practices of Stoicism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plato&#39;s Lemonade Stand Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Morris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/plato-s-lemonade-stand-by-tom-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 07:27:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/plato-s-lemonade-stand-by-tom-morris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Plato&amp;rsquo;s Lemonade Stand: Stirring Change into Something Great&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by Tom Morris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Human Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dave Asprey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/super-human-by-dave-asprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 07:16:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/super-human-by-dave-asprey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Super Human: The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book written by Dave Asprey, the creator of Bulletproof Coffee and a well-known biohacker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parenting Champions Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Lanny Bassham</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/parenting-champions-by-lanny-bassham/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:32:19 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/parenting-champions-by-lanny-bassham/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Parenting Champions: What Every Parent Should Know About the Mental Game&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Lanny Bassham, a renowned mental coach and Olympic gold medalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raise Your Game Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alan Stein Jr. and Jon Sternfeld</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/raise-your-game-by-alan-stein-jr-jon-sternfeld/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:19:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/raise-your-game-by-alan-stein-jr-jon-sternfeld/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Raise Your Game: High-Performance Secrets from the Best of the Best&amp;rdquo; by Alan Stein Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Means Business Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alan Cohen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spirit-means-business-by-alan-cohen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:00:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spirit-means-business-by-alan-cohen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spirit Means Business: The Way to Prosper Wildly Without Selling Your Soul&amp;rdquo; is a transformative book written by Alan Cohen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Habit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jack Hodge</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-habit-by-jack-hodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:45:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-habit-by-jack-hodge/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Habit: Harnessing the Power to Establish Routines that Guarantee Success in Business and in Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Charles Duhigg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadershift Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Maxwell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leadershift-by-john-maxwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 10:03:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leadershift-by-john-maxwell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Leadershift: The 11 Essential Changes Every Leader Must Embrace&amp;rdquo; is a book written by John C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Born to Run Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Christopher McDougall</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/born-to-run-by-christopher-mcdougall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 06:12:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/born-to-run-by-christopher-mcdougall/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Born to Run: A Hidden Tribe, Superathletes, and the Greatest Race the World Has Never Seen&amp;rdquo; by Christopher McDougall is a captivating non-fiction book that explores the world of ultra-distance running and the remarkable endurance of the Tarahumara, a reclusive indigenous tribe living in the remote Copper Canyons of Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/creativity-by-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 04:40:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/creativity-by-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Creativity: Flow and the Psychology of Discovery and Invention&amp;rdquo; by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi explores the nature of creativity and provides valuable insights into the psychological processes that underlie creative thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherever You Go, There You Are Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jon Kabat-Zinn</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-by-jon-kabat-zinn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:17:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-by-jon-kabat-zinn/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wherever You Go, There You Are: Mindfulness Meditation in Everyday Life&amp;rdquo; is a transformative book written by Jon Kabat-Zinn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 5 Second Rule Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mel Robbins</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-5-second-rule-by-mel-robbins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:27:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-5-second-rule-by-mel-robbins/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 5 Second Rule: Transform Your Life, Work, and Confidence with Everyday Courage&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Mel Robbins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Undefeated Mind Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alex Lickerman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-undefeated-mind-by-alex-lickerman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:39:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-undefeated-mind-by-alex-lickerman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Undefeated Mind: On the Science of Constructing an Indestructible Self&amp;rdquo; by Alex Lickerman is a self-help book that explores the concept of resilience and offers strategies for developing an unwavering mindset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As a Man Thinketh Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Allen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/as-a-man-thinketh-by-james-allen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:07:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/as-a-man-thinketh-by-james-allen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;As a Man Thinketh&amp;rdquo; is a classic self-help book written by James Allen and first published in 1903.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Originals Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Adam Grant</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/originals-by-adam-grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:24:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/originals-by-adam-grant/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Originals: How Non-Conformists Move the World&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by Adam Grant, a renowned organizational psychologist and Wharton professor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spartan Fit! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joe De Sena and John Durant</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spartan-fit-by-joe-de-sena-john-durant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:08:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spartan-fit-by-joe-de-sena-john-durant/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spartan Fit!: 30 Days. Transform Your Mind. Transform Your Body. Commit to Grit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waking Up Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sam Harris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/waking-up-by-sam-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 15:10:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/waking-up-by-sam-harris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Waking Up: A Guide to Spirituality Without Religion&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Sam Harris, a neuroscientist, philosopher, and prominent atheist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Die Empty Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Todd Henry</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/die-empty-by-todd-henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:35:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/die-empty-by-todd-henry/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Die Empty: Unleash Your Best Work Every Day&amp;rdquo; by Todd Henry is a motivational and practical guide that aims to help individuals tap into their full creative potential and make a meaningful impact in their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courage Under Fire Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Stockdale</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/courage-under-fire-by-james-stockdale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:18:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/courage-under-fire-by-james-stockdale/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Courage Under Fire: Testing Epictetus&amp;rsquo;s Doctrines in a Laboratory of Human Behavior&amp;rdquo; is a book written by James Stockdale, a former United States Navy admiral and Vietnam War veteran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Spartan Way Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joe De Sena</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-spartan-way-by-joe-de-sena/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:31:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-spartan-way-by-joe-de-sena/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Spartan Way: Eat Better. Train Better. Think Better. Be Better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4 Disciplines of Execution Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Chris McChesney, Sean Covey and Jim Huling</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-4-disciplines-of-execution-by-chris-mcchesney-sean-covey-jim-huling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:05:44 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-4-disciplines-of-execution-by-chris-mcchesney-sean-covey-jim-huling/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 4 Disciplines of Execution: Achieving Your Wildly Important Goals&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Chris McChesney, Sean Covey, and Jim Huling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Willpower Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Roy Baumeister and John Tierney</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/willpower-by-roy-baumeister-john-tierney/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:03:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/willpower-by-roy-baumeister-john-tierney/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Willpower: Rediscovering the Greatest Human Strength&amp;rdquo; by Roy Baumeister and John Tierney explores the concept of willpower and its role in achieving personal success and self-control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Way of the Bodhisattva Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Shantideva</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-bodhisattva-by-shantideva/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:45:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-bodhisattva-by-shantideva/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Way of the Bodhisattva&amp;rdquo; is a profound Mahayana Buddhist text written by the Indian scholar-monk Shantideva in the 8th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Hole Focus Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Isaiah Hankel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/black-hole-focus-by-isaiah-hankel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:34:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/black-hole-focus-by-isaiah-hankel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Black Hole Focus: How Intelligent People Can Create a Powerful Purpose for Their Lives&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Isaiah Hankel, an internationally recognized expert in the field of personal development and leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 10X Rule Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Grant Cardone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-10x-rule-by-grant-cardone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:23:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-10x-rule-by-grant-cardone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 10X Rule: The Only Difference Between Success and Failure&amp;rdquo; by Grant Cardone is a motivational and self-help book that aims to empower readers to take massive action in order to achieve extraordinary success in all areas of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musonius Rufus Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Cynthia King</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/musonius-rufus-by-cynthia-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:43:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/musonius-rufus-by-cynthia-king/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Musanion Rufus: Lectures and Sayings&amp;rdquo; is a collection of teachings and writings by the Stoic philosopher Musonius Rufus, compiled and translated by Cynthia King.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of TED* Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Emerald</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-ted-by-david-emerald/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:08:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-ted-by-david-emerald/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of TED*: *The Empowerment Dynamic&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by David Emerald.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick with It Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sean Young</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stick-with-it-by-sean-young/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:38:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stick-with-it-by-sean-young/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Stick with It: A Scientifically Proven Process for Changing Your Life - for Good&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Sean Young, a renowned psychologist and expert in the field of behavioral science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Doris Kearns Goodwin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leadership-by-doris-kearns-goodwin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:33:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leadership-by-doris-kearns-goodwin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Leadership: In Turbulent Times&amp;rdquo; is a compelling non-fiction book written by Doris Kearns Goodwin, a renowned historian and Pulitzer Prize-winning author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With Winning in Mind Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Lanny Bassham</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/with-winning-in-mind-by-lanny-bassham/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:08:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/with-winning-in-mind-by-lanny-bassham/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;With Winning in Mind&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Lanny Bassham, a renowned sports psychologist and Olympic gold medalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ed Diener and Robert Biswas Diener</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happiness-by-ed-diener-robert-biswas-diener/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 05:46:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happiness-by-ed-diener-robert-biswas-diener/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Happiness: Unlocking the Mysteries of Psychological Wealth&amp;rdquo; is an intriguing book written by Ed Diener and Robert Biswas-Diener.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Ownership Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jocko Willink and Leif Babin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/extreme-ownership-by-jocko-willink-leif-babin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 03:32:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/extreme-ownership-by-jocko-willink-leif-babin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Extreme Ownership: How U.S. Navy SEALs Lead and Win&amp;rdquo; is a book written by former Navy SEAL officers Jocko Willink and Leif Babin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oxygen Advantage Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Patrick McKeown</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-oxygen-advantage-by-patrick-mckeown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:41:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-oxygen-advantage-by-patrick-mckeown/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Oxygen Advantage: Simple, Scientifically Proven Breathing Techniques to Help You Become Healthier, Slimmer, Faster, and Fitter&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Patrick McKeown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jefferson Bible Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thomas Jefferson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-jefferson-bible-by-thomas-jefferson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:50:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-jefferson-bible-by-thomas-jefferson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Jefferson Bible: The Life and Morals of Jesus of Nazareth&amp;rdquo; is a unique work by Thomas Jefferson, the third President of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happier Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tal Ben-Shahar</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happier-by-tal-ben-shahar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 15:52:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happier-by-tal-ben-shahar/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Happier: Learn the Secrets to Daily Joy and Lasting Fulfillment&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Tal Ben-Shahar, a former Harvard University professor and expert in positive psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stephen R. Covey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-7-habits-of-highly-effective-people-by-stephen-covey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 17:26:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-7-habits-of-highly-effective-people-by-stephen-covey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Stephen R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rumi Daylight Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Camille Adams Helminski</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rumi-daylight-by-camille-helminski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:25:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rumi-daylight-by-camille-helminski/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Rumi Daylight: A Daybook of Spiritual Guidance&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Camille Adams Helminski, an author, translator, and spiritual teacher who has focused much of her work on the teachings of Rumi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bhagavad Gita Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-bhagavad-gita-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 11:10:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-bhagavad-gita-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Bhagavad Gita&amp;rdquo; is a Hindu scripture that contains a dialogue between the warrior Arjuna and his charioteer Krishna, who is actually an incarnation of the Hindu god Vishnu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man&#39;s Search For Meaning Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Viktor Frankl</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mans-search-for-meaning-by-viktor-frankl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 09:25:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mans-search-for-meaning-by-viktor-frankl/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Man&amp;rsquo;s Search for Meaning: An Introduction to Logotherapy&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Viktor Frankl, a psychiatrist and Holocaust survivor, first published in 1946.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Rules For Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jordan Peterson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/12-rules-for-life-by-jordan-peterson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:07:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/12-rules-for-life-by-jordan-peterson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;12 Rules for Life: An Antidote to Chaos&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book by Canadian clinical psychologist and psychology professor Jordan Peterson.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
