<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Summaries of the best books on &#39;Mindfulness and Happiness&#39; on Shortened Books</title>
    <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/categories/mindfulness-and-happiness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Summaries of the best books on &#39;Mindfulness and Happiness&#39; on Shortened Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 01:53:02 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shortenedbooks.com/categories/mindfulness-and-happiness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>At Your Best Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Carey Nieuwhof</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/at-your-best-by-carey-nieuwhof/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 01:53:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/at-your-best-by-carey-nieuwhof/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;At Your Best: How to Get Time, Energy, and Priorities Working in Your Favor&amp;rdquo; by Carey Nieuwhof is a transformative guide that unveils the key principles and strategies required to optimize your time, harness your energy, and align your priorities to achieve peak performance and fulfillment in both your personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altered Traits Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Goleman and Richard J. Davidson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/altered-traits-by-daniel-goleman-richard-davidson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:50:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/altered-traits-by-daniel-goleman-richard-davidson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Altered Traits: Science Reveals How Meditation Changes Your Mind, Brain, and Body&amp;rdquo; by Daniel Goleman and Richard Davidson is a captivating exploration into the transformative power of meditation on the human mind, brain, and body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Work No Play Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dale Sidebottom</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/all-work-no-play-by-dale-sidebottom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:27:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/all-work-no-play-by-dale-sidebottom/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;All Work No Play: A Surprising Guide to Feeling More Mindful, Grateful and Cheerful&amp;rdquo; by Dale Sidebottom is a captivating exploration into the transformative power of play in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice Not Given Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mark Epstein</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/advice-not-given-by-mark-epstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:06:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/advice-not-given-by-mark-epstein/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Advice Not Given: A Guide to Getting Over Yourself&amp;rdquo; by Mark Epstein is an exploration of the intersection between Eastern philosophy, psychology, and personal growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abundance Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Deepak Chopra</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/abundance-by-deepak-chopra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:50:41 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/abundance-by-deepak-chopra/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Abundance: The Inner Path to Wealth&amp;rdquo; authored by Deepak Chopra, is a thought-provoking and insightful guide that delves into the realm of personal transformation and self-discovery to attain true wealth and abundance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Year of Positive Thinking Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Cyndie Spiegel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-year-of-positive-thinking-by-cyndie-spiegel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:40:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-year-of-positive-thinking-by-cyndie-spiegel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Year of Positive Thinking: Daily Inspiration, Wisdom, and Courage&amp;rdquo; by Cyndie Spiegel is a captivating guide that takes readers on a transformative journey through the course of a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Monk&#39;s Guide to Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gelong Thubten</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-monk-s-guide-to-happiness-by-gelong-thubten/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:50:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-monk-s-guide-to-happiness-by-gelong-thubten/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Monk&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Happiness: Meditation in the 21st Century&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking and insightful book that delves into the pursuit of happiness and the transformative power of meditation in our modern world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Secrets to Powerful Manifesting Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mandy Morris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/8-secrets-to-powerful-manifesting-by-mandy-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:29:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/8-secrets-to-powerful-manifesting-by-mandy-morris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;8 Secrets to Powerful Manifesting&amp;rdquo; by Mandy Morris is an enlightening and empowering self-help book that delves into the art of manifestation and how to create the life you desire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24/6 Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tiffany Shlain</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/24-6-by-tiffany-shlain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:01:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/24-6-by-tiffany-shlain/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;24/6: The Power of Unplugging One Day a Week&amp;rdquo; by Tiffany Shlain is a thought-provoking and timely exploration of the importance of disconnecting from technology for one day each week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18 Minutes Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Peter Bregman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/18-minutes-by-peter-bregman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:21:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/18-minutes-by-peter-bregman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;18 Minutes&amp;rdquo; is a compelling self-help book written by Peter Bregman, aiming to guide readers toward better time management, focus, and productivity in their personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10% Happier Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dan Harris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/10-happier-by-dan-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:01:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/10-happier-by-dan-harris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;10% Happier: How I Tamed the Voice in My Head, Reduced Stress without Losing My Edge and Found Self-Help That Actually Works&amp;rdquo; is a captivating memoir by Dan Harris, an accomplished news anchor and journalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Equation Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Neil Pasricha</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-equation-by-neil-pasricha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:12:20 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-equation-by-neil-pasricha/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness Equation: Want Nothing + Do Anything = Have Everything&amp;rdquo; by Neil Pasricha is a self-help book that explores the concept of happiness and provides practical strategies to achieve a more fulfilling life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadcasting Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michelle Gielan</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/broadcasting-happiness-by-michelle-gielan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:13:12 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/broadcasting-happiness-by-michelle-gielan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Broadcasting Happiness: The Science of Igniting and Sustaining Positive Change&amp;rdquo; by Michelle Gielan is a book that explores the power of positive communication and its impact on personal and professional success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Track Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Emma Sepp채l채</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-track-by-emma-seppala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:17:40 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-track-by-emma-seppala/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness Track: How to Apply the Science of Happiness to Accelerate Your Success&amp;rdquo; by Emma Sepp채l채 is a self-help book that explores the relationship between happiness and success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Wash Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Perlmutter and Austin Perlmutter</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/brain-wash-by-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 09:59:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/brain-wash-by-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Brain Wash: Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness&amp;rdquo; is a captivating book co-authored by Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness of Pursuit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Chris Guillebeau</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-of-pursuit-by-chris-guillebeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:38:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-of-pursuit-by-chris-guillebeau/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness of Pursuit: Finding the Quest That Will Bring Purpose to Your Life&amp;rdquo; by Chris Guillebeau is a self-help book that explores the concept of quests and how they can bring purpose and happiness to one&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Myths of Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sonja Lyubomirsky</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-myths-of-happiness-by-sonja-lyubomirsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:34:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-myths-of-happiness-by-sonja-lyubomirsky/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Myths of Happiness: What Should Make You Happy, but Doesn&amp;rsquo;t, What Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t Make You Happy, but Does&amp;rdquo; is a profound book written by Sonja Lyubomirsky, a prominent psychology professor and researcher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to the Good Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - William Irvine</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-guide-to-the-good-life-by-william-irvine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:54:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-guide-to-the-good-life-by-william-irvine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Guide to the Good Life: The Ancient Art of Stoic Joy&amp;rdquo; by William B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authentic Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Martin Seligman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/authentic-happiness-by-martin-seligman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:54:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/authentic-happiness-by-martin-seligman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Authentic Happiness: Using the New Positive Psychology to Realize Your Potential for Lasting Fulfillment&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book written by Martin Seligman, a renowned psychologist and the founder of positive psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Hypothesis Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jonathan Haidt</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-hypothesis-by-jonathan-haidt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:12:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-hypothesis-by-jonathan-haidt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness Hypothesis: Finding Modern Truth in Ancient Wisdom&amp;rdquo; by Jonathan Haidt is a stimulating book that explores the complex nature of human happiness by combining modern scientific research with ancient philosophical wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ed Diener and Robert Biswas Diener</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happiness-by-ed-diener-robert-biswas-diener/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 05:46:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happiness-by-ed-diener-robert-biswas-diener/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Happiness: Unlocking the Mysteries of Psychological Wealth&amp;rdquo; is an intriguing book written by Ed Diener and Robert Biswas-Diener.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The How of Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sonja Lyubomirsky</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-how-of-happiness-by-sonja-lyubomirsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:28:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-how-of-happiness-by-sonja-lyubomirsky/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The How of Happiness: A New Approach to Getting the Life You Want&amp;rdquo; by Sonja Lyubomirsky is a self-help book that explores the science of happiness and provides practical strategies to cultivate happiness in one&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happier Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tal Ben-Shahar</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happier-by-tal-ben-shahar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 15:52:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happier-by-tal-ben-shahar/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Happier: Learn the Secrets to Daily Joy and Lasting Fulfillment&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Tal Ben-Shahar, a former Harvard University professor and expert in positive psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Together Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Suzann Pawelski and James O. Pawelski</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happy-together-by-suzann-pawelski-and-james-pawelski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 10:32:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happy-together-by-suzann-pawelski-and-james-pawelski/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Happy Together: Using the Science of Positive Psychology to Build Love That Lasts&amp;rdquo; by Suzann Pileggi Pawelski and James O.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
