<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Summaries of the Best Books on &#39;Personal Development&#39; on Shortened Books</title>
    <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/categories/personal-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Summaries of the Best Books on &#39;Personal Development&#39; on Shortened Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 01:53:02 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shortenedbooks.com/categories/personal-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>At Your Best Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Carey Nieuwhof</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/at-your-best-by-carey-nieuwhof/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 01:53:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/at-your-best-by-carey-nieuwhof/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;At Your Best: How to Get Time, Energy, and Priorities Working in Your Favor&amp;rdquo; by Carey Nieuwhof is a transformative guide that unveils the key principles and strategies required to optimize your time, harness your energy, and align your priorities to achieve peak performance and fulfillment in both your personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abundance Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Deepak Chopra</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/abundance-by-deepak-chopra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:50:41 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/abundance-by-deepak-chopra/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Abundance: The Inner Path to Wealth&amp;rdquo; authored by Deepak Chopra, is a thought-provoking and insightful guide that delves into the realm of personal transformation and self-discovery to attain true wealth and abundance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Year of Positive Thinking Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Cyndie Spiegel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-year-of-positive-thinking-by-cyndie-spiegel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:40:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-year-of-positive-thinking-by-cyndie-spiegel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Year of Positive Thinking: Daily Inspiration, Wisdom, and Courage&amp;rdquo; by Cyndie Spiegel is a captivating guide that takes readers on a transformative journey through the course of a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Secrets to Powerful Manifesting Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mandy Morris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/8-secrets-to-powerful-manifesting-by-mandy-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:29:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/8-secrets-to-powerful-manifesting-by-mandy-morris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;8 Secrets to Powerful Manifesting&amp;rdquo; by Mandy Morris is an enlightening and empowering self-help book that delves into the art of manifestation and how to create the life you desire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10% Happier Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dan Harris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/10-happier-by-dan-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:01:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/10-happier-by-dan-harris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;10% Happier: How I Tamed the Voice in My Head, Reduced Stress without Losing My Edge and Found Self-Help That Actually Works&amp;rdquo; is a captivating memoir by Dan Harris, an accomplished news anchor and journalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Mental Training Summary of Key Ideas and Review - DC Gonzalez</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-mental-training-by-dc-gonzalez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 23:13:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-mental-training-by-dc-gonzalez/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Art of Mental Training&amp;rdquo; is a powerful and insightful book that delves into the world of mental training and its profound impact on achieving performance excellence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Writing Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stephen King</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/on-writing-by-stephen-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 22:55:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/on-writing-by-stephen-king/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;On Writing: A Memoir of the Craft&amp;rdquo; is a captivating and instructive book penned by the prolific and renowned author Stephen King.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miracle Morning Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Hal Elrod</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-morning-by-hal-elrod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 19:36:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-morning-by-hal-elrod/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Miracle Morning: The Not-So-Obvious Secret Guaranteed to Transform Your Life (Before 8 AM)&amp;rdquo; by Hal Elrod is a self-help book that presents a transformative morning routine designed to enhance personal development and improve various aspects of one&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Life Is Your Message Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/your-life-is-your-message-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 19:33:42 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/your-life-is-your-message-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Your Life Is Your Message: Finding Harmony with Yourself, Others and the Earth&amp;rdquo; is a transformative and insightful book written by Eknath Easwaran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He Can Who Thinks He Can Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Orison Swett Marden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/he-can-who-thinks-he-can-by-orison-swett-marden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 18:26:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/he-can-who-thinks-he-can-by-orison-swett-marden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;He Can Who Thinks He Can: And Other Papers on Success in Life&amp;rdquo; by Orison Swett Marden is a timeless and inspirational self-help book that delves into the power of positive thinking and the immense potential that lies within each individual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improv Wisdom Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Patricia Ryan Madson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/improv-wisdom-by-patricia-ryan-madson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 14:11:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/improv-wisdom-by-patricia-ryan-madson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Improv Wisdom: Don&amp;rsquo;t Prepare, Just Show Up&amp;rdquo; is a compelling and insightful book written by Patricia Ryan Madson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stuart Brown and Christopher Vaughan</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/play-by-stuart-brown-christopher-vaughan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 13:43:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/play-by-stuart-brown-christopher-vaughan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Play: How it Shapes the Brain, Opens the Imagination, and Invigorates the Soul&amp;rdquo; is a fascinating exploration of the importance and transformative power of play in human development and fulfillment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mark Williams and Danny Penman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mindfulness-by-mark-williams-danny-penman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 18:01:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mindfulness-by-mark-williams-danny-penman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mindfulness: An Eight-Week Plan for Finding Peace in a Frantic World&amp;rdquo; is a transformative book that offers practical guidance and exercises to cultivate mindfulness and find peace amidst the chaos of everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strangest Secret Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Earl Nightingale</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-strangest-secret-by-earl-nightingale/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:43:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-strangest-secret-by-earl-nightingale/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Strangest Secret&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Earl Nightingale, a renowned author, motivational speaker, and radio personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rhythm of Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matthew Kelly</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-rhythm-of-life-by-matthew-kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:00:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-rhythm-of-life-by-matthew-kelly/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Rhythm of Life: Living Every Day with Passion &amp;amp; Purpose&amp;rdquo; by Matthew Kelly is a self-help book that aims to inspire individuals to live with intention, passion, and a sense of purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Concentration Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Theron Dumont</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-concentration-by-theron-dumont/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:23:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-concentration-by-theron-dumont/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Concentration&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Theron Dumont, a pseudonym for William Walker Atkinson, a prominent figure in the New Thought movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Message of A Master Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John McDonald</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-message-of-a-master-by-john-mcdonald/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 15:55:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-message-of-a-master-by-john-mcdonald/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Message of A Master&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by John McDonald.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Major Pieces to the Life Puzzle Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jim Rohn</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/five-major-pieces-to-the-life-puzzle-by-jim-rohn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:22:14 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/five-major-pieces-to-the-life-puzzle-by-jim-rohn/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Five Major Pieces to the Life Puzzle: A Guide to Personal Success&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Jim Rohn, a renowned motivational speaker and personal development expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Buddha in Your Mirror Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Woody Hochswender, Greg Martin and Ted Morino</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-buddha-in-your-mirror-by-woody-hochswender-greg-martin-ted-morino/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:09:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-buddha-in-your-mirror-by-woody-hochswender-greg-martin-ted-morino/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Buddha in Your Mirror: Practical Buddhism and the Search for Self&amp;rdquo; by Woody Hochswender, Greg Martin, and Ted Morino is a guidebook that explores the principles of Buddhism and their application in everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greatest Salesman in the World Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Og Mandino</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-by-og-mandino/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 10:37:52 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-by-og-mandino/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Greatest Salesman in the World: You Can Change Your Life with the Priceless Wisdom of Ten Ancient Scrolls Handed Down for Thousands of Years&amp;rdquo; by Og Mandino is a motivational and self-help book that combines storytelling with practical advice for achieving success in sales and in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Betting on You Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Laurie Ruettimann</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/betting-on-you-by-laurie-ruettimann/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:45:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/betting-on-you-by-laurie-ruettimann/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Betting on You&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Laurie Ruettimann that aims to empower individuals to take control of their careers and prioritize their own well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badass Habits Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jen Sincero</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/badass-habits-by-jen-sincero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:27:14 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/badass-habits-by-jen-sincero/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Badass Habits&amp;rdquo; by Jen Sincero is a self-help book that provides readers with practical guidance and insights on how to cultivate positive habits and transform their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acting with Power Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Deborah Gruenfeld</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/acting-with-power-by-deborah-gruenfeld/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:56:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/acting-with-power-by-deborah-gruenfeld/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Acting with Power: Why We Are More Powerful Than We Believe&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by Deborah Gruenfeld, a social psychologist and professor at Stanford Graduate School of Business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfectly Yourself Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matthew Kelly</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/perfectly-yourself-by-matthew-kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:58:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/perfectly-yourself-by-matthew-kelly/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Perfectly Yourself: Nine Lessons for Enduring Happiness&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Matthew Kelly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Better Way to Live Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Og Mandino</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-better-way-to-live-by-og-mandino/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:38:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-better-way-to-live-by-og-mandino/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Better Way to Live&amp;rdquo; is a powerful and inspiring book written by Og Mandino, a renowned author known for his motivational works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Heart and the Fist Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-heart-and-the-fist-by-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:26:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-heart-and-the-fist-by-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Heart and the Fist: The Education of a Humanitarian, the Making of a Navy SEAL&amp;rdquo; is a memoir written by Eric Greitens, detailing his personal journey from a humanitarian to becoming a Navy SEAL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Essence of Success Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Earl Nightingale</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-essence-of-success-by-earl-nightingale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:07:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-essence-of-success-by-earl-nightingale/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Essence of Success&amp;rdquo; by Earl Nightingale is a motivational and self-help book that aims to guide readers towards achieving success and fulfillment in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thich Nhat Hanh</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/silence-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:44:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/silence-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Silence: The Power of Quiet in a World Full of Noise&amp;rdquo; by Thich Nhat Hanh is a profound and enlightening book that explores the transformative power of silence in our modern, noisy world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resilience Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/resilience-by-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:23:42 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/resilience-by-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Resilience: Hard-Won Wisdom for Living a Better Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Eric Greitens, a former Navy SEAL, humanitarian, and Rhodes Scholar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Up Your Brain Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. David Perlmutter and Alberto Villoldo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/power-up-your-brain-by-david-perlmutter-alberto-villoldo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:35:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/power-up-your-brain-by-david-perlmutter-alberto-villoldo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Power Up Your Brain: The Neuroscience of Enlightenment&amp;rdquo; is a transformative book written by David Perlmutter, a renowned neurologist, and Alberto Villoldo, a psychologist and shamanic healer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lead the Field Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Earl Nightingale</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/lead-the-field-by-earl-nightingale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:20:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/lead-the-field-by-earl-nightingale/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Lead the Field&amp;rdquo; is a powerful self-help book written by Earl Nightingale, a renowned motivational speaker and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courageous Dreaming Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Alberto Villoldo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/courageous-dreaming-by-alberto-villoldo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 12:57:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/courageous-dreaming-by-alberto-villoldo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Courageous Dreaming: How Shamans Dream the World into Being&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Alberto Villoldo, a renowned psychologist and medical anthropologist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power of Mindful Learning Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ellen Langer</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/power-of-mindful-learning-by-ellen-langer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 21:05:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/power-of-mindful-learning-by-ellen-langer/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Mindful Learning&amp;rdquo; is a great book written by Ellen Langer, a renowned psychologist and Harvard professor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ellen Langer</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mindfulness-by-ellen-langer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:54:40 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mindfulness-by-ellen-langer/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mindfulness&amp;rdquo; is a transformative book written by Ellen Langer, a renowned social psychologist and mindfulness pioneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choose the Life You Want Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tal Ben-Shahar</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/choose-the-life-you-want-by-tal-ben-shahar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:44:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/choose-the-life-you-want-by-tal-ben-shahar/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Choose the Life You Want: The Mindful Way to Happiness&amp;rdquo; by Tal Ben-Shahar is a self-help book that offers practical guidance on how to cultivate happiness and fulfillment in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Maker Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. David Perlmutter</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/brain-maker-by-david-perlmutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:22:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/brain-maker-by-david-perlmutter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Brain Maker&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book by David Perlmutter that explores the intricate relationship between the gut microbiome and the brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grain Brain Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. David Perlmutter</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/grain-brain-by-david-perlmutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:13:03 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/grain-brain-by-david-perlmutter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Grain Brain: The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar—Your Brain&amp;rsquo;s Silent Killers&amp;rdquo; by David Perlmutter is a groundbreaking book that explores the connection between nutrition, brain health, and overall well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Life a Masterpiece Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Orison Swett Marden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/making-life-a-masterpiece-by-orison-swett-marden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:00:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/making-life-a-masterpiece-by-orison-swett-marden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Making Life a Masterpiece&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Orison Swett Marden, a renowned author and founder of Success Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Toughness Training for Sports Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Loehr</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-new-toughness-training-for-sports-by-james-loehr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:52:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-new-toughness-training-for-sports-by-james-loehr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The New Toughness Training for Sports: Mental Emotional Physical Conditioning from One of the World&amp;rsquo;s Premier Sports Psychologists&amp;rdquo; by James Loehr is a comprehensive guide that explores the crucial role of mental and emotional conditioning in sports performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Slight Edge Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jeff Olson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-slight-edge-by-jeff-olson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:38:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-slight-edge-by-jeff-olson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Slight Edge&amp;rdquo; by Jeff Olson is a motivational and self-help book that explores the concept of the slight edge and its profound impact on our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do the Work Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Pressfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/do-the-work-by-steven-pressfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:30:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/do-the-work-by-steven-pressfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do the Work: Overcome Resistance and Get Out of Your Own Way&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and practical guide written by Steven Pressfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procrastinate on Purpose Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Rory Vaden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/procrastinate-on-purpose-by-rory-vaden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:23:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/procrastinate-on-purpose-by-rory-vaden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Procrastinate on Purpose: 5 Permissions to Multiply Your Time&amp;rdquo; by Rory Vaden is a self-help book that explores the concept of time management and offers strategies to maximize productivity and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Wild Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. John Ratey and Richard Manning</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/go-wild-by-john-ratey-richard-manning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:12:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/go-wild-by-john-ratey-richard-manning/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Go Wild: Eat Fat, Run Free, Be Social, and Follow Evolution&amp;rsquo;s Other Rules for Total Health and Well-Being&amp;rdquo; is an intriguing book written by John Ratey, a renowned psychiatrist, and Richard Manning, an environmental author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Get Fat Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gary Taubes</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/why-we-get-fat-by-gary-taubes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:55:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/why-we-get-fat-by-gary-taubes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Why We Get Fat: And What to Do About It&amp;rdquo; is a stimulating and provocative book written by Gary Taubes, an investigative science journalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toughness Training for Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Loehr</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/toughness-training-for-life-by-james-loehr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:42:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/toughness-training-for-life-by-james-loehr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Toughness Training for Life: A Revolutionary Program for Maximizing Health, Happiness, and Productivity&amp;rdquo; by James Loehr is a self-help book that explores the concept of toughness and how it can be developed to improve various aspects of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mindful Athlete Summary of Key Ideas and Review - George Mumford</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-mindful-athlete-by-george-mumford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:29:40 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-mindful-athlete-by-george-mumford/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Mindful Athlete: Secrets to Pure Performance&amp;rdquo; is a transformative guide written by George Mumford, a renowned mindfulness coach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can if I Want To Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Arnold Lazarus and Dr. Allen Fay</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/i-can-if-i-want-to-by-arnold-lazarus-allen-fay/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:17:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/i-can-if-i-want-to-by-arnold-lazarus-allen-fay/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I Can if I Want To&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Arnold Lazarus and Allen Fay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Achievement Habit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Bernard Roth</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-achievement-habit-by-bernard-roth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:07:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-achievement-habit-by-bernard-roth/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Achievement Habit: Stop Wishing, Start Doing, and Take Command of Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Bernard Roth, a professor of engineering and the co-founder of the Stanford d.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Be an Imperfectionist Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stephen Guise</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-an-imperfectionist-by-stephen-guise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 17:52:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-an-imperfectionist-by-stephen-guise/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Be an Imperfectionist: The New Way to Self-Acceptance, Fearless Living, and Freedom from Perfectionism&amp;rdquo; by Stephen Guise is a self-help book that offers practical strategies and insights to overcome perfectionism and embrace imperfection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Work of Your Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stephen Cope</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-great-work-of-your-life-by-stephen-cope/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 16:12:41 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-great-work-of-your-life-by-stephen-cope/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Great Work of Your Life: A Guide for the Journey to Your True Calling&amp;rdquo; by Stephen Cope is a profound and insightful book that explores the concept of dharma, or one&amp;rsquo;s true calling, and provides guidance on how to discover and live out that calling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Mind for Numbers Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Barbara Oakley</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-mind-for-numbers-by-barbara-oakley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:54:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-mind-for-numbers-by-barbara-oakley/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Mind for Numbers: How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra)&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Barbara Oakley, a professor of engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paleo Manifesto Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Durant</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-paleo-manifesto-by-john-durant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:07:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-paleo-manifesto-by-john-durant/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Paleo Manifesto: Ancient Wisdom for Lifelong Health&amp;rdquo; is a book written by John Durant that explores the concept of paleo living, drawing inspiration from our ancestors&amp;rsquo; lifestyles and applying it to modern-day health and wellness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show Your Work! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Austin Kleon</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/show-your-work-by-austin-kleon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:00:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/show-your-work-by-austin-kleon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Show Your Work!&amp;rdquo; by Austin Kleon is a creative guidebook that encourages individuals to embrace their creativity and share it with the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Executive Toughness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jason Selk</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/executive-toughness-by-jason-selk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:34:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/executive-toughness-by-jason-selk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Executive Toughness: The Mental-Training Program to Increase Your Leadership Performance&amp;rdquo; by Jason Selk is a self-help book that aims to provide readers with practical strategies and techniques to enhance their leadership skills and mental toughness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastery Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robert Greene</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastery-by-robert-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:23:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastery-by-robert-greene/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mastery&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Robert Greene. Drawing inspiration from the lives of historical figures such as Leonardo da Vinci, Thomas Edison, and Albert Einstein, Greene explores the concept of mastery and provides guidance on how individuals can achieve greatness in their chosen fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hoops Whisperer Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Idan Ravin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-hoops-whisperer-by-idan-ravin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:11:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-hoops-whisperer-by-idan-ravin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Hoops Whisperer: On the Court and Inside the Heads of Basketball&amp;rsquo;s Best Players&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Idan Ravin, a renowned basketball trainer who has worked with some of the NBA&amp;rsquo;s biggest stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Way of the Fight Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Georges St-Pierre</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-fight-by-georges-st-pierre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:31:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-fight-by-georges-st-pierre/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Way of the Fight&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Georges St-Pierre, a Canadian mixed martial artist and former UFC welterweight champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Fight / Your Fight Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ronda Rousey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/my-fight-your-fight-by-ronda-rousey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:23:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/my-fight-your-fight-by-ronda-rousey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;My Fight / Your Fight&amp;rdquo; is a memoir written by Ronda Rousey, an accomplished mixed martial artist and former UFC Women&amp;rsquo;s Bantamweight Champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Good Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steve Chandler</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/crazy-good-by-steve-chandler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:08:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/crazy-good-by-steve-chandler/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Crazy Good: A Book of CHOICES&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Steve Chandler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Science of Self-Discipline Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Peter Hollins</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-science-of-self-discipline-by-peter-hollins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:58:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-science-of-self-discipline-by-peter-hollins/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Science of Self-Discipline: The Willpower, Mental Toughness, and Self-Control to Resist Temptation and Achieve Your Goals&amp;rdquo; by Peter Hollins is a comprehensive guide that delves into the realm of self-discipline and provides practical strategies for cultivating willpower, developing mental toughness, and exercising self-control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Book of Talent Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Coyle</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-little-book-of-talent-by-daniel-coyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:17:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-little-book-of-talent-by-daniel-coyle/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Little Book of Talent: 52 Tips for Improving Your Skills&amp;rdquo; by Daniel Coyle is a practical guide to developing and honing your skills in any field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Quick—But Don&#39;t Hurry Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Wooden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/be-quick-but-don-t-hurry-by-andrew-hill-john-wooden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 19:42:09 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/be-quick-but-don-t-hurry-by-andrew-hill-john-wooden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Be Quick—But Don&amp;rsquo;t Hurry: Finding Success in the Teachings of a Lifetime&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Andrew Hill and John Wooden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Marshmallow Test Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Walter Mischel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-marshmallow-test-by-walter-mischel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 19:32:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-marshmallow-test-by-walter-mischel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Marshmallow Test: Why Self-Control Is the Engine of Success&amp;rdquo; by Walter Mischel explores the fascinating research conducted by the author and his colleagues, focusing on the concept of self-control and its impact on success in various aspects of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louder than Words Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Todd Henry</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/louder-than-words-by-todd-henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 19:15:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/louder-than-words-by-todd-henry/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Louder than Words: Harness the Power of Your Authentic Voice&amp;rdquo; by Todd Henry is a compelling book that explores the importance of finding and expressing your authentic voice in a world filled with noise and distractions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bulletproof Diet Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dave Asprey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-bulletproof-diet-by-dave-asprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:41:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-bulletproof-diet-by-dave-asprey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Bulletproof Diet: Lose up to a Pound a Day, Reclaim Energy and Focus, Upgrade Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Dave Asprey, a biohacker and entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The School of Greatness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Lewis Howes</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-school-of-greatness-by-lewis-howes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:24:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-school-of-greatness-by-lewis-howes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The School of Greatness: A Real-World Guide to Living Bigger, Loving Deeper, and Leaving a Legacy&amp;rdquo; by Lewis Howes is a motivational and self-help book that aims to guide readers towards achieving greatness in all aspects of their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Your Brain, Change Your Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Daniel Amen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/change-your-brain-change-your-life-by-daniel-amen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:04:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/change-your-brain-change-your-life-by-daniel-amen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Change Your Brain, Change Your Life: The Breakthrough Program for Conquering Anxiety, Depression, Obsessiveness, Lack of Focus, Anger, and Memory Problems&amp;rdquo; is a transformative self-help book written by Daniel G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mental Edge Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Kenneth Baum</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-mental-edge-by-kenneth-baum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:48:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-mental-edge-by-kenneth-baum/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Mental Edge: Maximize Your Sports Potential with the Mind-Body Connection&amp;rdquo; by Kenneth Baum is a comprehensive guide that explores the powerful relationship between the mind and body in the context of sports performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Motivation Manifesto Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brendon Burchard</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-motivation-manifesto-by-brendon-burchard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:37:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-motivation-manifesto-by-brendon-burchard/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Motivation Manifesto: 9 Declarations to Claim Your Personal Power&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Brendon Burchard, a renowned motivational speaker and personal development trainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Box Thinking Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matthew Syed</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/black-box-thinking-by-matthew-syed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:20:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/black-box-thinking-by-matthew-syed/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Black Box Thinking: Why Most People Never Learn from Their Mistakes—But Some Do&amp;rdquo; is an interesting book written by Matthew Syed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Successful People Think Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Maxwell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-successful-people-think-by-john-maxwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:06:44 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-successful-people-think-by-john-maxwell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How Successful People Think&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by John C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bounce Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matthew Syed</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bounce-by-matthew-syed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:00:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bounce-by-matthew-syed/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Bounce: Mozart, Federer, Picasso, Beckham, and the Science of Success&amp;rdquo; is a captivating book written by Matthew Syed, a British journalist and former professional table tennis player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art &amp; Fear Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Bayles and Ted Orland</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/art-fear-by-david-bayles-ted-orland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:56:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/art-fear-by-david-bayles-ted-orland/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Art &amp;amp; Fear: Observations On the Perils (and Rewards) of Artmaking&amp;rdquo; is a book written by David Bayles and Ted Orland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Bets Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Peter Sims</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/little-bets-by-peter-sims/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:45:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/little-bets-by-peter-sims/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Little Bets: How Breakthrough Ideas Emerge from Small Discoveries&amp;rdquo; by Peter Sims explores the concept of using a series of small experiments, or &amp;ldquo;little bets,&amp;rdquo; to foster creativity, innovation, and the development of breakthrough ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-theories Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Carol Dweck</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/self-theories-by-carol-dweck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:17:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/self-theories-by-carol-dweck/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Self-theories: Their Role in Motivation, Personality, and Development&amp;rdquo; by Carol S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 15 Invaluable Laws of Growth Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Maxwell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-15-invaluable-laws-of-growth-by-john-maxwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:05:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-15-invaluable-laws-of-growth-by-john-maxwell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 15 Invaluable Laws of Growth: Live Them and Reach Your Potential&amp;rdquo; by John C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Your Potential Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jocelyn Glei</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/maximize-your-potential-by-jocelyn-glei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:48:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/maximize-your-potential-by-jocelyn-glei/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Maximize Your Potential: Grow Your Expertise, Take Bold Risks &amp;amp; Build an Incredible Career&amp;rdquo; by Jocelyn Glei is a book that aims to help individuals unlock their full potential and achieve success in their careers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage Your Day-to-Day Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jocelyn Glei</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/manage-your-day-to-day-by-jocelyn-glei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:35:14 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/manage-your-day-to-day-by-jocelyn-glei/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Manage Your Day-to-Day: Build Your Routine, Find Your Focus, and Sharpen Your Creative Mind&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book edited by Jocelyn Glei.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Mark Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jocelyn Glei</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/make-your-mark-by-jocelyn-glei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:22:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/make-your-mark-by-jocelyn-glei/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Make Your Mark: The Creative&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Building a Business with Impact&amp;rdquo; by Jocelyn Glei is a comprehensive guidebook that provides valuable insights and practical advice for creative individuals who aspire to build businesses with a meaningful impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Fully Charged? Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Rath</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/are-you-fully-charged-by-tom-rath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:09:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/are-you-fully-charged-by-tom-rath/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Are You Fully Charged?: The 3 Keys to Energizing Your Work and Life&amp;rdquo; by Tom Rath is a self-help book that focuses on three essential elements that contribute to a fulfilled and energized life: meaning, interactions, and energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make It Stick Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Peter Brown, Henry Roediger III and Mark Mcdaniel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/make-it-stick-by-peter-brown-henry-roediger-iii-mark-mcdaniel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:51:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/make-it-stick-by-peter-brown-henry-roediger-iii-mark-mcdaniel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Make It Stick: The Science of Successful Learning&amp;rdquo; by Peter Brown, Henry Roediger III, and Mark McDaniel is a mind-stretching book that explores the science behind effective learning and provides practical strategies to enhance learning and retention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmonic Wealth Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Arthur Ray</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/harmonic-wealth-by-james-arthur-ray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:43:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/harmonic-wealth-by-james-arthur-ray/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Harmonic Wealth: The Secret of Attracting The Life You Want&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by James Arthur Ray, a motivational speaker and entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Right Kind of Crazy Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Adam Steltzner and William Patrick</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-right-kind-of-crazy-by-adam-steltzner-william-patrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:32:20 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-right-kind-of-crazy-by-adam-steltzner-william-patrick/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Right Kind of Crazy: A True Story of Teamwork, Leadership, and High-Stakes Innovation&amp;rdquo; is a book co-authored by Adam Steltzner and William Patrick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Work Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jeff Goins</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-work-by-jeff-goins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:13:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-work-by-jeff-goins/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Art of Work: A Proven Path to Discovering What You Were Meant to Do&amp;rdquo; by Jeff Goins is a self-help book that explores the journey of finding one&amp;rsquo;s true calling in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miracle of Right Thought Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Orison Swett Marden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-of-right-thought-by-orison-swett-marden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:04:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-of-right-thought-by-orison-swett-marden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Miracle of Right Thought&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Orison Swett Marden, a renowned author and motivational speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Entrepreneur Roller Coaster Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Darren Hardy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-entrepreneur-roller-coaster-by-darren-hardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:39:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-entrepreneur-roller-coaster-by-darren-hardy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Entrepreneur Roller Coaster: It&amp;rsquo;s Your Turn to #JoinTheRide&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and practical guide written by Darren Hardy, a successful entrepreneur, speaker, and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shallows Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Nicholas Carr</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-shallows-by-nicholas-carr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:28:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-shallows-by-nicholas-carr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Shallows: What the Internet Is Doing to Our Brains&amp;rdquo; is an insightful book written by Nicholas Carr, exploring the impact of the internet on our cognitive abilities and the way we think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Equation Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Neil Pasricha</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-equation-by-neil-pasricha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:12:20 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-equation-by-neil-pasricha/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness Equation: Want Nothing + Do Anything = Have Everything&amp;rdquo; by Neil Pasricha is a self-help book that explores the concept of happiness and provides practical strategies to achieve a more fulfilling life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Brain at Work Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Rock</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/your-brain-at-work-by-david-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:02:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/your-brain-at-work-by-david-rock/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Your Brain at Work: Strategies for Overcoming Distraction, Regaining Focus, and Working Smarter All Day Long&amp;rdquo; by David Rock is an excellent guide that explores the intricacies of the human brain and provides practical strategies for improving productivity and effectiveness in the workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off Balance Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matthew Kelly</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/off-balance-by-matthew-kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 10:35:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/off-balance-by-matthew-kelly/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Off Balance&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Matthew Kelly that challenges the conventional notion of work-life balance and offers a fresh perspective on achieving personal and professional satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take Your Time Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/take-your-time-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 10:30:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/take-your-time-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Take Your Time: The Wisdom of Slowing Down&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by Eknath Easwaran, a renowned spiritual teacher and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golf is Not a Game of Perfect Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Bob Rotella</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/golf-is-not-a-game-of-perfect-by-bob-rotella/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 10:16:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/golf-is-not-a-game-of-perfect-by-bob-rotella/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Golf is Not a Game of Perfect&amp;rdquo; by Bob Rotella is a highly acclaimed self-help book that explores the mental side of golf and provides valuable insights and strategies to improve performance on the golf course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passage Meditation Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/passage-meditation-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 10:10:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/passage-meditation-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Passage Meditation&amp;rdquo; is a profound and practical guidebook written by Eknath Easwaran, a renowned spiritual teacher, author, and translator of Indian classics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outliers Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Malcolm Gladwell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/outliers-by-malcolm-gladwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:57:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/outliers-by-malcolm-gladwell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Outliers: The Story of Success&amp;rdquo; is a non-fiction book written by Malcolm Gladwell, a renowned journalist and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Affluence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Deepak Chopra</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/creating-affluence-by-deepak-chopra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:50:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/creating-affluence-by-deepak-chopra/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Creating Affluence: The A-to-Z Steps to a Richer Life&amp;rdquo; by Deepak Chopra is a self-help book that delves into the principles of abundance and prosperity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddhism Day by Day Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daisaku Ikeda</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/buddhism-day-by-day-by-daisaku-ikeda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 17:34:54 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/buddhism-day-by-day-by-daisaku-ikeda/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Buddhism Day by Day: Wisdom for Modern Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Daisaku Ikeda, a prominent Buddhist philosopher, peacebuilder, and educator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drive Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Pink</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/drive-by-daniel-pink/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 17:21:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/drive-by-daniel-pink/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Drive: The Surprising Truth About What Motivates Us&amp;rdquo; by Daniel Pink explores the factors that truly motivate individuals in their personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unleash the Warrior Within Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Richard Mack Machowicz</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/unleash-the-warrior-within-by-richard-mack-machowicz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:57:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/unleash-the-warrior-within-by-richard-mack-machowicz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Unleash the Warrior Within: Develop the Focus, Discipline, Confidence, and Courage You Need to Achieve Unlimited Goals&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Richard Mack Machowicz, a former Navy SEAL and a renowned motivational speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Born for This Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Chris Guillebeau</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/born-for-this-by-chris-guillebeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:41:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/born-for-this-by-chris-guillebeau/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Born for This: How to Find the Work You Were Meant to Do&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Chris Guillebeau, a bestselling author and entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choke Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sian Beilock</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/choke-by-sian-beilock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:28:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/choke-by-sian-beilock/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Choke: What the Secrets of the Brain Reveal About Getting It Right When You Have To&amp;rdquo; is an excellent book written by Sian Beilock, a cognitive scientist and expert in the field of performance psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep for Success! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. James Maas and Rebecca Robbins</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sleep-for-success-by-james-maas-rebecca-robbins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:14:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sleep-for-success-by-james-maas-rebecca-robbins/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sleep for Success!: Everything You Must Know About Sleep But are Too Tired to Ask&amp;rdquo; by James Maas and Rebecca Robbins is a comprehensive guide that delves into the fascinating world of sleep and its profound impact on our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary Greatness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stephen Covey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/primary-greatness-by-stephen-covey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:55:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/primary-greatness-by-stephen-covey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Primary Greatness: The 12 Levers of Success&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Stephen Covey, the renowned author of &amp;ldquo;The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadcasting Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michelle Gielan</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/broadcasting-happiness-by-michelle-gielan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:13:12 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/broadcasting-happiness-by-michelle-gielan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Broadcasting Happiness: The Science of Igniting and Sustaining Positive Change&amp;rdquo; by Michelle Gielan is a book that explores the power of positive communication and its impact on personal and professional success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Road to Character Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Brooks</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-road-to-character-by-david-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 12:47:42 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-road-to-character-by-david-brooks/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Road to Character&amp;rdquo; is a nonfiction book written by David Brooks, a renowned journalist and cultural commentator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noble Purpose Summary of Key Ideas and Review - William Damon</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/noble-purpose-by-william-damon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 12:31:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/noble-purpose-by-william-damon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Noble Purpose: The Joy of Living a Meaningful Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by William Damon, a renowned psychologist and professor at Stanford University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Champion&#39;s Comeback Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jim Afremow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-champion-s-comeback-by-jim-afremow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 12:11:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-champion-s-comeback-by-jim-afremow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Champion&amp;rsquo;s Comeback: How Great Athletes Recover, Reflect, and Reignite&amp;rdquo; by Jim Afremow is a book that delves into the mindset and strategies of successful athletes when faced with setbacks and challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Hacking Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sir John Hargrave</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mind-hacking-by-sir-john-hargrave/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:33:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mind-hacking-by-sir-john-hargrave/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mind Hacking: How to Change Your Mind for Good in 21 Days&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Sir John Hargrave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living Forward Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Hyatt and Daniel Harkavy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/living-forward-by-michael-hyatt-daniel-harkavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:17:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/living-forward-by-michael-hyatt-daniel-harkavy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Living Forward: A Proven Plan to Stop Drifting and Get the Life You Want&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Michael Hyatt and Daniel Harkavy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path to Purpose Summary of Key Ideas and Review - William Damon</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-path-to-purpose-by-william-damon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 10:51:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-path-to-purpose-by-william-damon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Path to Purpose: How Young People Find Their Calling in Life&amp;rdquo; by William Damon is a thought-provoking book that explores the journey of discovering one&amp;rsquo;s purpose and finding meaning in life, particularly focusing on the experiences and challenges faced by young individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Ideals Summary of Key Ideas and Review - William Damon and Anne Colby</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-ideals-by-william-damon-anne-colby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 09:03:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-ideals-by-william-damon-anne-colby/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Ideals: The Real Story of Moral Choice&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by William Damon and Anne Colby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Through Stillness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Russell Simmons and Chris Morrow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/success-through-stillness-by-russell-simmons-chris-morrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:43:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/success-through-stillness-by-russell-simmons-chris-morrow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Success Through Stillness: Meditation Made Simple&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Russell Simmons and Chris Morrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seventh Sense Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joshua Cooper Ramo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-seventh-sense-by-joshua-cooper-ramo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:30:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-seventh-sense-by-joshua-cooper-ramo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Seventh Sense: Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks&amp;rdquo; by Joshua Cooper Ramo is an intellectually challenging book that explores the concept of the seventh sense, a heightened awareness and understanding of the interconnectivity and dynamics of networks in our modern world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Confidence Gap Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Russ Harris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-confidence-gap-by-russ-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:13:44 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-confidence-gap-by-russ-harris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Confidence Gap: A Guide to Overcoming Fear and Self-Doubt&amp;rdquo; by Russ Harris is a self-help book that explores the concept of confidence and provides practical strategies to overcome fear and self-doubt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Common Denominator of Success Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Albert Gray</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/new-common-denominator-of-success-by-albert-gray/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:00:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/new-common-denominator-of-success-by-albert-gray/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The New Common Denominator of Success&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Albert E.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sitting Kills, Moving Heals Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Joan Vernikos</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sitting-kills-moving-heals-by-joan-vernikos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 05:38:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sitting-kills-moving-heals-by-joan-vernikos/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sitting Kills, Moving Heals: How Everyday Movement Will Prevent Pain, Illness, and Early Death—and Exercise Alone Won&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rdquo; by Joan Vernikos is a groundbreaking book that challenges the conventional belief that exercise alone is enough to counteract the negative effects of a sedentary lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Just Sit There Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Katy Bowman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/don-t-just-sit-there-by-katy-bowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 05:22:14 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/don-t-just-sit-there-by-katy-bowman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Just Sit There: Transitioning to a Standing and Dynamic Workstation for Whole-Body Health&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Katy Bowman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Focus Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Goleman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/focus-by-daniel-goleman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 05:01:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/focus-by-daniel-goleman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Focus: The Hidden Driver of Excellence&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Daniel Goleman, a renowned psychologist and science journalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leading an Inspired Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jim Rohn</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leading-an-inspired-life-by-jim-rohn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:47:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leading-an-inspired-life-by-jim-rohn/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Leading an Inspired Life&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and self-help book written by Jim Rohn, a renowned entrepreneur, speaker, and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Learn by Living Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eleanor Roosevelt</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/you-learn-by-living-by-eleanor-roosevelt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:27:39 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/you-learn-by-living-by-eleanor-roosevelt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;You Learn by Living: Eleven Keys for a More Fulfilling Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Eleanor Roosevelt, the former First Lady of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Trap Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Russ Harris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-trap-by-russ-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:12:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-trap-by-russ-harris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness Trap: How to Stop Struggling and Start Living&amp;rdquo; by Russ Harris is a self-help book that presents a revolutionary approach to achieving happiness and fulfillment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clean Gut Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Alejandro Junger</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/clean-gut-by-alejandro-junger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 19:51:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/clean-gut-by-alejandro-junger/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Clean Gut: The Breakthrough Plan for Eliminating the Root Cause of Disease and Revolutionizing Your Health&amp;rdquo; by Alejandro Junger is a comprehensive guide that explores the connection between gut health and overall well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How We Learn Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Benedict Carey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-we-learn-by-benedict-carey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 19:36:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-we-learn-by-benedict-carey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How We Learn: The Surprising Truth About When, Where, and Why It Happens&amp;rdquo; by Benedict Carey is an interesting exploration of the human learning process and the strategies that can optimize learning and memory retention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Always Hungry? Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. David Ludwig</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/always-hungry-by-david-ludwig/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 19:19:39 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/always-hungry-by-david-ludwig/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Always Hungry?: Conquer Cravings, Retrain Your Fat Cells, and Lose Weight Permanently&amp;rdquo; is a book written by David Ludwig, a renowned physician and researcher in the field of nutrition and obesity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of Food Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Pollan</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/in-defense-of-food-by-michael-pollan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 19:02:52 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/in-defense-of-food-by-michael-pollan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;In Defense of Food: An Eater&amp;rsquo;s Manifesto&amp;rdquo; by Michael Pollan is a thought-provoking book that explores the complex and often confusing world of nutrition and offers practical advice on how to make healthier food choices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoe Dog Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Phil Knight</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/shoe-dog-by-phil-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 17:16:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/shoe-dog-by-phil-knight/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Shoe Dog: A Memoir by the Creator of Nike&amp;rdquo; is a memoir written by Phil Knight, the co-founder of Nike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Smarter Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Shawn Stevenson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sleep-smarter-by-shawn-stevenson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 16:44:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sleep-smarter-by-shawn-stevenson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sleep Smarter: 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to A Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success&amp;rdquo; by Shawn Stevenson is a comprehensive guide that explores the importance of sleep and provides practical strategies to optimize sleep quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sleep Revolution Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Arianna Huffington</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-sleep-revolution-by-arianna-huffington/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 16:31:41 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-sleep-revolution-by-arianna-huffington/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Sleep Revolution: Transforming Your Life, One Night at a Time&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Arianna Huffington, the co-founder and editor-in-chief of The Huffington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts of a Philosophical Fighter Pilot Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Stockdale</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/thoughts-of-a-philosophical-fighter-pilot-by-james-stockdale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 16:14:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/thoughts-of-a-philosophical-fighter-pilot-by-james-stockdale/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Thoughts of a Philosophical Fighter Pilot&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by James Stockdale, a former United States Navy Vice Admiral and Vietnam War veteran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Becoming a Leader Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Warren Bennis</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/on-becoming-a-leader-by-warren-bennis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 16:00:42 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/on-becoming-a-leader-by-warren-bennis/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;On Becoming a Leader&amp;rdquo; by Warren Bennis is a book that explores the essential qualities and skills required to become an effective leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Charisma Myth Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Olivia Fox Cabane</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-charisma-myth-by-olivia-fox-cabane/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:48:21 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-charisma-myth-by-olivia-fox-cabane/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Charisma Myth: How Anyone Can Master the Art and Science of Personal Magnetism&amp;rdquo; by Olivia Fox Cabane is a self-help book that explores the concept of charisma and provides practical techniques for individuals to develop and enhance their own personal magnetism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robert Cialdini</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/influence-by-robert-cialdini/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:37:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/influence-by-robert-cialdini/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Influence: The Psychology of Persuasion&amp;rdquo; is a bestselling book written by Robert Cialdini, a renowned social psychologist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Existentialism Is a Humanism Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jean-Paul Sartre</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/existentialism-is-a-humanism-by-jean-paul-sartre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:23:03 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/existentialism-is-a-humanism-by-jean-paul-sartre/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Existentialism Is a Humanism&amp;rdquo; is a philosophical work written by Jean-Paul Sartre, one of the most prominent figures in existentialist philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Leadership Challenge Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Kouzes and Barry Posner</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-leadership-challenge-by-james-kouzes-barry-posner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:27:42 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-leadership-challenge-by-james-kouzes-barry-posner/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Leadership Challenge: How to Make Extraordinary Things Happen in Organizations&amp;rdquo; by James Kouzes and Barry Posner is a renowned leadership book that explores the principles and practices of effective leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Leader Who Had No Title Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robin Sharma</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-leader-who-had-no-title-by-robin-sharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:13:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-leader-who-had-no-title-by-robin-sharma/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Leader Who Had No Title: A Modern Fable on Real Success in Business and in Life&amp;rdquo; by Robin Sharma is a motivational and self-help book that presents a fictional story combined with practical advice to inspire individuals to become effective leaders and achieve success in all aspects of their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miracle of Mindfulness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thich Nhat Hanh</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:59:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Miracle of Mindfulness: An Introduction to the Practice of Meditation&amp;rdquo; is a renowned book written by Thich Nhat Hanh, a Vietnamese Buddhist monk, teacher, and peace activist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effortless Healing Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Joseph Mercola</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/effortless-healing-by-joseph-mercola/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:39:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/effortless-healing-by-joseph-mercola/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Effortless Healing: 9 Simple Ways to Sidestep Illness, Shed Excess Weight, and Help Your Body Fix Itself&amp;rdquo; by Joseph Mercola is a comprehensive guide that offers practical advice and actionable strategies to optimize health and support the body&amp;rsquo;s natural healing abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unsubscribe Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jocelyn Glei</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/unsubscribe-by-jocelyn-glei/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:20:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/unsubscribe-by-jocelyn-glei/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Unsubscribe: How to Kill Email Anxiety, Avoid Distractions, and Get Real Work Done&amp;rdquo; by Jocelyn Glei is a self-help book that addresses the overwhelming presence of email in our lives and provides practical strategies to manage email anxiety, increase productivity, and regain control over our workdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Engaged Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thomas Sterner</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fully-engaged-by-thomas-sterner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 11:54:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fully-engaged-by-thomas-sterner/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fully Engaged: Using the Practicing Mind in Daily Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Thomas Sterner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Creative Anxiety Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eric Maisel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastering-creative-anxiety-by-eric-maisel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 10:56:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastering-creative-anxiety-by-eric-maisel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mastering Creative Anxiety: 24 Lessons for Writers, Painters, Musicians, and Actors from America&amp;rsquo;s Foremost Creativity Coach&amp;rdquo; by Eric Maisel is a self-help book that addresses the common anxieties and challenges faced by creative individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapt Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Winifred Gallagher</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rapt-by-winifred-gallagher/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 10:30:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rapt-by-winifred-gallagher/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Rapt: Attention and the Focused Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Winifred Gallagher that explores the power and importance of attention in our daily lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultra Mindset Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Travis Macy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-ultra-mindset-by-travis-macy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:30:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-ultra-mindset-by-travis-macy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Ultra Mindset: An Endurance Champion&amp;rsquo;s 8 Core Principles for Success in Business, Sports, and Life&amp;rdquo; by Travis Macy is a compelling book that explores the mindset required to achieve success in various aspects of life, drawing insights from the author&amp;rsquo;s experience as an endurance athlete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Road to Sparta Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dean Karnazes</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-road-to-sparta-by-dean-karnazes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:22:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-road-to-sparta-by-dean-karnazes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Road to Sparta: Reliving the Ancient Battle and Epic Run That Inspired the World&amp;rsquo;s Greatest Footrace&amp;rdquo; is a non-fiction book written by Dean Karnazes, an accomplished ultra-marathon runner and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety Free Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Patrick McKeown</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/anxiety-free-by-patrick-mckeown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:01:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/anxiety-free-by-patrick-mckeown/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Anxiety Free: Stop Worrying and Quieten Your Mind&amp;rdquo; by Patrick McKeown is a self-help book that offers practical strategies and techniques to overcome anxiety and quiet the mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brian Tracy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/goals-by-brian-tracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 08:40:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/goals-by-brian-tracy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Goals!: How to Get Everything You Want—Faster Than You Ever Thought Possible&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Brian Tracy, a renowned author and motivational speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Way to Love Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Anthony de Mello</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-to-love-by-anthony-de-mello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 08:17:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-to-love-by-anthony-de-mello/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Way to Love: The Last Meditations of Anthony de Mello&amp;rdquo; is a spiritual guidebook written by Anthony de Mello, a Jesuit priest and spiritual teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Achievement Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brian Tracy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/maximum-achievement-by-brian-tracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 08:02:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/maximum-achievement-by-brian-tracy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Maximum Achievement: Strategies and Skills That Will Unlock Your Hidden Powers to Succeed&amp;rdquo; by Brian Tracy is a self-help book that aims to guide readers toward unlocking their full potential and achieving maximum success in various areas of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movement Matters Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Katy Bowman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/movement-matters-by-katy-bowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:49:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/movement-matters-by-katy-bowman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Movement Matters: Essays on Movement Science, Movement Ecology, and the Nature of Movement&amp;rdquo; is an engaging book written by Katy Bowman, a renowned biomechanist and movement educator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fail Fast, Fail Often Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ryan Babineaux and John Krumboltz</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fail-fast-fail-often-by-ryan-babineaux-john-krumboltz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:36:03 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fail-fast-fail-often-by-ryan-babineaux-john-krumboltz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fail Fast, Fail Often: How Losing Can Help You Win&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Ryan Babineaux and John Krumboltz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grain Brain Whole Life Plan Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. David Perlmutter</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-grain-brain-whole-life-plan-by-david-perlmutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:03:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-grain-brain-whole-life-plan-by-david-perlmutter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Grain Brain Whole Life Plan: Boost Brain Performance, Lose Weight, and Achieve Optimal Health&amp;rdquo; by David Perlmutter is a comprehensive guide that explores the connection between diet, brain health, and overall well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Four Purposes of Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dan Millman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-four-purposes-of-life-by-dan-millman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 06:44:21 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-four-purposes-of-life-by-dan-millman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Four Purposes of Life: Finding Meaning and Direction in a Changing World&amp;rdquo; by Dan Millman is a self-help book that explores the fundamental questions of human existence and provides guidance on finding meaning, purpose, and direction in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual Evolution Summary of Key Ideas and Review - George Vaillant</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spiritual-evolution-by-george-vaillant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 06:25:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spiritual-evolution-by-george-vaillant/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spiritual Evolution: How We Are Wired for Faith, Hope, and Love&amp;rdquo; by George Vaillant explores the inherent human capacity for spirituality and its significance in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brain Warrior&#39;s Way Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Daniel Amen and Tana Amen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-brain-warrior-s-way-by-daniel-amen-tana-amen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:46:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-brain-warrior-s-way-by-daniel-amen-tana-amen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Brain Warrior&amp;rsquo;s Way: Ignite Your Energy and Focus, Attack Illness and Aging, Transform Pain into Purpose&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Daniel Amen and Tana Amen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pursuing the Good Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Christopher Peterson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/pursuing-the-good-life-by-christopher-peterson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:31:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/pursuing-the-good-life-by-christopher-peterson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Pursuing the Good Life: 100 Reflections on Positive Psychology&amp;rdquo; by Christopher Peterson is a thought-provoking book that explores the principles and practices of positive psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Starting Something Stupid Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Richie Norton and Natalie Norton</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-starting-something-stupid-by-richie-norton-natalie-norton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:06:54 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-starting-something-stupid-by-richie-norton-natalie-norton/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Starting Something Stupid: How to Crush Fear, Make Dreams Happen, and Live without Regret&amp;rdquo; by Richie Norton and Natalie Norton is a motivational and practical guide that encourages readers to overcome fear and take action to pursue their dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathe Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Belisa Vranich</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/breathe-by-belisa-vranich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:44:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/breathe-by-belisa-vranich/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Breathe: The Simple, Revolutionary 14-Day Program to Improve Your Mental and Physical Health&amp;rdquo; by Belisa Vranich is a groundbreaking book that explores the power of breath and its impact on our overall well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Healing Power of the Breath Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Richard Brown and Patricia Gerbarg</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-healing-power-of-the-breath-by-richard-brown-patricia-gerbarg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:15:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-healing-power-of-the-breath-by-richard-brown-patricia-gerbarg/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Healing Power of the Breath: Simple Techniques to Reduce Stress and Anxiety, Enhance Concentration, and Balance Your Emotions&amp;rdquo; by Richard Brown and Patricia Gerbarg is a comprehensive guide that explores the transformative potential of breathwork as a tool for healing and well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strength in the Storm Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/strength-in-the-storm-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:01:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/strength-in-the-storm-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Strength in the Storm: Transform Stress, Live in Balance and Find Peace of Mind&amp;rdquo; by Eknath Easwaran is a self-help book that offers practical guidance and wisdom for managing stress and finding inner peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge of the Higher Worlds and its Attainment Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Rudolf Steiner</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/knowledge-of-the-higher-worlds-and-its-attainment-by-rudolf-steiner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:46:20 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/knowledge-of-the-higher-worlds-and-its-attainment-by-rudolf-steiner/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Knowledge of the Higher Worlds and Its Attainment&amp;rdquo; is a philosophical and spiritual work written by Rudolf Steiner, the founder of Anthroposophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Distracted Mind Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Adam Gazzaley and Larry Rosen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-distracted-mind-by-adam-gazzaley-larry-rosen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:32:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-distracted-mind-by-adam-gazzaley-larry-rosen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Distracted Mind: Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by Adam Gazzaley, a neuroscientist, and Larry Rosen, a psychologist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Master Key Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robert Peng and Rafael Nasser</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-master-key-by-robert-peng-rafael-nasser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:16:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-master-key-by-robert-peng-rafael-nasser/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Master Key: Qigong Secrets for Vitality, Love, and Wisdom&amp;rdquo; is a book co-authored by Robert Peng, a Qigong master and teacher, and Rafael Nasser, a writer and student of Robert Peng.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The As If Principle Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Richard Wiseman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-as-if-principle-by-richard-wiseman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 12:57:03 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-as-if-principle-by-richard-wiseman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The As If Principle: The Radically New Approach to Changing Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Richard Wiseman, a renowned psychologist and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eight Pillars of Prosperity Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Allen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/eight-pillars-of-prosperity-by-james-allen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 12:44:59 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/eight-pillars-of-prosperity-by-james-allen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Eight Pillars of Prosperity&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by James Allen, a prominent British philosophical writer and poet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak Performance Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brad Stulberg and Steve Magness</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/peak-performance-by-brad-stulberg-steve-magness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 12:27:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/peak-performance-by-brad-stulberg-steve-magness/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Peak Performance: Elevate Your Game, Avoid Burnout, and Thrive with the New Science of Success&amp;rdquo; by Brad Stulberg and Steve Magness is a self-help book that explores the concept of peak performance and provides practical strategies to achieve and sustain it in various aspects of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Progress Principle Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Teresa Amabile and Steven Kramer</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-progress-principle-by-teresa-amabile-steven-kramer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 12:11:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-progress-principle-by-teresa-amabile-steven-kramer/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Progress Principle: Using Small Wins to Ignite Joy, Engagement, and Creativity at Work&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Teresa Amabile and Steven Kramer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Breathing Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Al Lee and Don Campbell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/perfect-breathing-by-al-lee-don-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:56:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/perfect-breathing-by-al-lee-don-campbell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Perfect Breathing: Transform Your Life One Breath at a Time&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Al Lee and Don Campbell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barking Up the Wrong Tree Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eric Barker</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/barking-up-the-wrong-tree-by-eric-barker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:34:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/barking-up-the-wrong-tree-by-eric-barker/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Barking Up the Wrong Tree: The Surprising Science Behind Why Everything You Know About Success Is (Mostly) Wrong&amp;rdquo; by Eric Barker is a book that challenges common assumptions about success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Track Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Emma Seppälä</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-track-by-emma-seppala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:17:40 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-track-by-emma-seppala/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness Track: How to Apply the Science of Happiness to Accelerate Your Success&amp;rdquo; by Emma Seppälä is a self-help book that explores the relationship between happiness and success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wired to Create Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Scott Barry Kaufman and Carolyn Gregoire</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wired-to-create-by-scott-barry-kaufman-carolyn-gregoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:57:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wired-to-create-by-scott-barry-kaufman-carolyn-gregoire/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wired to Create: Unraveling the Mysteries of the Creative Mind&amp;rdquo; by Scott Barry Kaufman and Carolyn Gregoire is a captivating exploration of the creative process and the inner workings of the creative mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coaching the Mental Game Summary of Key Ideas and Review - H. A. Dorfman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/coaching-the-mental-game-by-h-a-dorfman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:26:39 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/coaching-the-mental-game-by-h-a-dorfman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Coaching the Mental Game: Leadership Philosophies and Strategies for Peak Performance in Sports—and Everyday Life&amp;rdquo; by H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Narcissism Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Craig Malkin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rethinking-narcissism-by-craig-malkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 08:58:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rethinking-narcissism-by-craig-malkin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Rethinking Narcissism: The Secret to Recognizing and Coping with Narcissists&amp;rdquo; by Craig Malkin is a groundbreaking book that offers a fresh perspective on narcissism, aiming to help readers understand and cope with narcissistic individuals in their personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head Strong Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dave Asprey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/head-strong-by-dave-asprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 08:39:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/head-strong-by-dave-asprey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Head Strong: The Bulletproof Plan to Activate Untapped Brain Energy to Work Smarter and Think Faster—in Just Two Weeks&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Dave Asprey, the creator of the Bulletproof Diet and Bulletproof Coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Plant Paradox Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Gundry</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-plant-paradox-by-steven-gundry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 07:42:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-plant-paradox-by-steven-gundry/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Plant Paradox: The Hidden Dangers in &amp;ldquo;Healthy&amp;rdquo; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Steven Gundry, a renowned heart surgeon and medical researcher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathe In, Breathe Out Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Loehr and Jeffrey Migdow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/breathe-in-breathe-out-by-james-loehr-jeffrey-migdow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 06:39:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/breathe-in-breathe-out-by-james-loehr-jeffrey-migdow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Breathe In, Breathe Out: Inhale Energy and Exhale Stress by Guiding and Controlling Your Breathing&amp;rdquo; by James Loehr and Jeffrey Migdow is a comprehensive guide that explores the power of conscious breathing techniques in promoting physical and mental well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fat for Fuel Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Joseph Mercola</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fat-for-fuel-by-joseph-mercola/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 06:26:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fat-for-fuel-by-joseph-mercola/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fat for Fuel: A Revolutionary Diet to Combat Cancer, Boost Brain Power, and Increase Your Energy&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book written by Joseph Mercola.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Connection Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Gelb</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-connection-by-michael-gelb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 05:42:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-connection-by-michael-gelb/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Art of Connection: 7 Relationship-Building Skills Every Leader Needs Now&amp;rdquo; by Michael Gelb is a guidebook that explores the essential skills required to cultivate meaningful and impactful relationships in today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braving the Wilderness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brené Brown</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/braving-the-wilderness-by-brene-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 05:29:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/braving-the-wilderness-by-brene-brown/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Braving the Wilderness: The Quest for True Belonging and the Courage to Stand Alone&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Brené Brown, a research professor and renowned author in the field of social psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bright Line Eating Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Susan Peirce Thompson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bright-line-eating-by-susan-peirce-thompson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 12:47:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bright-line-eating-by-susan-peirce-thompson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Bright Line Eating: The Science of Living Happy, Thin and Free&amp;rdquo; is a transformative self-help book written by Susan Peirce Thompson, Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Success System That Never Fails Summary of Key Ideas and Review - William Clement Stone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-success-system-that-never-fails-by-william-clement-stone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 12:30:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-success-system-that-never-fails-by-william-clement-stone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Success System That Never Fails&amp;rdquo; is a motivational self-help book written by William Clement Stone, an American businessman and philanthropist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Grit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Caroline Miller</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/getting-grit-by-caroline-miller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 12:18:21 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/getting-grit-by-caroline-miller/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Getting Grit: The Evidence-Based Approach to Cultivating Passion, Perseverance, and Purpose&amp;rdquo; by Caroline Miller is a self-help book that explores the concept of grit and provides evidence-based strategies for developing and enhancing one&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;grittiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Mud, No Lotus Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thich Nhat Hanh</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/no-mud-no-lotus-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 12:01:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/no-mud-no-lotus-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;No Mud, No Lotus: The Art of Transforming Suffering&amp;rdquo; is a profound and insightful book written by Thich Nhat Hanh, a renowned Buddhist monk, peace activist, and prolific author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Messy Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tim Harford</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/messy-by-tim-harford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 11:50:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/messy-by-tim-harford/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Messy: The Power of Disorder to Transform Our Lives&amp;rdquo; by Tim Harford is a stimulating exploration of the benefits of embracing disorder and randomness in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designed to Move Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Joan Vernikos</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/designed-to-move-by-joan-vernikos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 11:37:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/designed-to-move-by-joan-vernikos/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Designed to Move: The Science-Backed Program to Fight Sitting Disease and Enjoy Lifelong Health&amp;rdquo; by Joan Vernikos is a groundbreaking book that explores the detrimental effects of a sedentary lifestyle and provides a science-backed program to counteract the negative impact of sitting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Telomere Effect Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Elizabeth Blackburn and Elissa Epel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-telomere-effect-by-elizabeth-blackburn-elissa-epel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 11:24:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-telomere-effect-by-elizabeth-blackburn-elissa-epel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Telomere Effect: A Revolutionary Approach to Living Younger, Healthier, Longer&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book written by Elizabeth Blackburn, a Nobel Prize-winning scientist, and Elissa Epel, a health psychologist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Develop Self-Confidence and Influence People Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dale Carnegie</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-develop-self-confidence-and-influence-people-by-dale-carnegie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 11:10:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-develop-self-confidence-and-influence-people-by-dale-carnegie/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Develop Self-Confidence and Influence People&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Dale Carnegie, the renowned author of the classic &amp;ldquo;How to Win Friends and Influence People.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Religion Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dalai Lama</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/beyond-religion-by-dalai-lama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:55:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/beyond-religion-by-dalai-lama/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Beyond Religion: Ethics for a Whole World&amp;rdquo; is a book written by the 14th Dalai Lama, Tenzin Gyatso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Live on 24 Hours a Day Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Arnold Bennett</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-live-on-24-hours-a-day-by-arnold-bennett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:40:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-live-on-24-hours-a-day-by-arnold-bennett/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Live on 24 Hours a Day&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Arnold Bennett and first published in 1910.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripping over the Truth Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Travis Christofferson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/tripping-over-the-truth-by-travis-christofferson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:21:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/tripping-over-the-truth-by-travis-christofferson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Tripping over the Truth: How the Metabolic Theory of Cancer Is Overturning One of Medicine&amp;rsquo;s Most Entrenched Paradigms&amp;rdquo; by Travis Christofferson is an insightful book that challenges the traditional understanding of cancer and explores the metabolic theory of the disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Truth in Small Doses Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Clifton Leaf</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-truth-in-small-doses-by-clifton-leaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:09:14 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-truth-in-small-doses-by-clifton-leaf/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Truth in Small Doses: Why We&amp;rsquo;re Losing the War on Cancer—and How to Win It&amp;rdquo; is a mind-stretching book written by Clifton Leaf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Emperor of All Maladies Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Siddhartha Mukherjee</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-emperor-of-all-maladies-by-siddhartha-mukherjee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:00:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-emperor-of-all-maladies-by-siddhartha-mukherjee/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Emperor of All Maladies: A Biography of Cancer&amp;rdquo; by Siddhartha Mukherjee is a profound exploration of the history, science, and impact of cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Power Within You Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eric Butterworth</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/discover-the-power-within-you-by-eric-butterworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 09:37:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/discover-the-power-within-you-by-eric-butterworth/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Discover the Power Within You: A Guide to the Unexplored Depths Within&amp;rdquo; by Eric Butterworth is a transformative book that delves into the realm of spirituality and personal growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Sell Is Human Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Pink</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/to-sell-is-human-by-daniel-pink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 09:22:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/to-sell-is-human-by-daniel-pink/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;To Sell Is Human: The Surprising Truth About Moving Others&amp;rdquo; by Daniel Pink is a thought-provoking book that challenges traditional notions of selling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Influence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Pantalon</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/instant-influence-by-michael-pantalon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 09:08:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/instant-influence-by-michael-pantalon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Instant Influence: How to Get Anyone to Do Anything&amp;hellip;Fast&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Michael Pantalon, a psychologist and expert in motivational interviewing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>212 The Extra Degree Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sam Parker</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/212-the-extra-degree-by-sam-parker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:59:19 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/212-the-extra-degree-by-sam-parker/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;212 The Extra Degree: How One Small Change Can Lead to Big Results&amp;rdquo; by Sam Parker is a motivational book that emphasizes the power of making small, incremental changes to achieve significant results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Pink</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/when-by-daniel-pink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:47:20 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/when-by-daniel-pink/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;When: The Scientific Secrets of Perfect Timing&amp;rdquo; by Daniel Pink is a captivating exploration of the role that timing plays in our lives, both personally and professionally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Morning Routine Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Benjamin Spall and Michael Xander</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/my-morning-routine-by-benjamin-spall-michael-xander/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:36:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/my-morning-routine-by-benjamin-spall-michael-xander/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;My Morning Routine: How Successful People Start Every Day Inspired&amp;rdquo; is a book co-authored by Benjamin Spall and Michael Xander.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lead Yourself First Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Raymond Kethledge and Michael Erwin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/lead-yourself-first-by-raymond-kethledge-michael-erwin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:22:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/lead-yourself-first-by-raymond-kethledge-michael-erwin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Lead Yourself First: Inspiring Leadership Through Solitude&amp;rdquo; by Raymond Kethledge and Michael Erwin explores the concept of solitude as a powerful tool for leadership development and personal growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homo Deus Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Yuval Noah Harari</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/homo-deus-by-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:12:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/homo-deus-by-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Homo Deus: A Brief History of Tomorrow&amp;rdquo; is a profound book written by Yuval Noah Harari, the renowned historian and author of &amp;ldquo;Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Audience of One Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Srinivas Rao</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/an-audience-of-one-by-srinivas-rao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:02:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/an-audience-of-one-by-srinivas-rao/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;An Audience of One: Reclaiming Creativity for Its Own Sake&amp;rdquo; by Srinivas Rao is a thought-provoking book that challenges the conventional notions of creativity and encourages readers to embrace their creative instincts for personal fulfillment rather than external validation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infinite Self Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stuart Wilde</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/infinite-self-by-stuart-wilde/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 04:28:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/infinite-self-by-stuart-wilde/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Infinite Self: 33 Steps to Reclaiming Your Inner Power&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Stuart Wilde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rest Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alex Soojung-Kim Pang</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rest-by-alex-soojung-kim-pang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 19:40:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rest-by-alex-soojung-kim-pang/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Rest: Why You Get More Done When You Work Less&amp;rdquo; by Alex Soojung-Kim Pang is an interesting book that challenges the conventional notion that working longer hours leads to greater productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Icarus Deception Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Seth Godin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-icarus-deception-by-seth-godin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 19:32:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-icarus-deception-by-seth-godin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Icarus Deception: How High Will You Fly?&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by Seth Godin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21 Lessons for the 21st Century Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Yuval Noah Harari</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-by-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 19:06:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-by-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;21 Lessons for the 21st Century&amp;rdquo; by Yuval Noah Harari is a thought-provoking and insightful book that examines the most pressing issues and challenges of the contemporary world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Book of Endurance Training and Racing Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Philip Maffetone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-big-book-of-endurance-training-and-racing-by-philip-maffetone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:57:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-big-book-of-endurance-training-and-racing-by-philip-maffetone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Big Book of Endurance Training and Racing&amp;rdquo; by Philip Maffetone is a comprehensive guide to optimizing endurance performance through a holistic approach to training and racing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix Your Feet Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Philip Maffetone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fix-your-feet-by-philip-maffetone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:50:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fix-your-feet-by-philip-maffetone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fix Your Feet: Build the Best Foundation for Healthy, Pain-Free Knees, Hips, and Spine&amp;rdquo; by Philip Maffetone is a comprehensive guide that focuses on the importance of foot health and its impact on the overall well-being of the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Overfat Pandemic Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Philip Maffetone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-overfat-pandemic-by-philip-maffetone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:41:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-overfat-pandemic-by-philip-maffetone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Overfat Pandemic: Exposing the Problem and Its Simple Solution for Everyone Who Needs to Eliminate Excess Body Fat&amp;rdquo; by Philip Maffetone is a book that tackles the issue of overfat, which refers to individuals who have excess body fat that negatively impacts their health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Endurance Handbook Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Philip Maffetone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-endurance-handbook-by-philip-maffetone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:35:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-endurance-handbook-by-philip-maffetone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Endurance Handbook: How to Achieve Athletic Potential, Stay Healthy, and Get the Most Out of Your Body&amp;rdquo; by Philip Maffetone is a comprehensive guide that delves into the principles of endurance training and offers practical strategies for athletes of all levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win or Learn Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Kavanagh</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/win-or-learn-by-john-kavanagh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:29:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/win-or-learn-by-john-kavanagh/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Win or Learn: MMA, Conor McGregor &amp;amp; Me: A Trainer&amp;rsquo;s Journey&amp;rdquo; is a captivating book written by John Kavanagh, the renowned mixed martial arts (MMA) coach of Conor McGregor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Artist&#39;s Journey Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Pressfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-artist-s-journey-by-steven-pressfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:20:12 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-artist-s-journey-by-steven-pressfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Artist&amp;rsquo;s Journey: The Wake of the Hero&amp;rsquo;s Journey and the Lifelong Pursuit of Meaning&amp;rdquo; by Steven Pressfield explores the creative process and the artist&amp;rsquo;s journey to find meaning and fulfillment in their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody Wants to Read Your Sh*t Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Pressfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/nobody-wants-to-read-your-sh-t-by-steven-pressfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 17:04:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/nobody-wants-to-read-your-sh-t-by-steven-pressfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Nobody Wants to Read Your Sh*t: And Other Tough-Love Truths to Make You a Better Writer&amp;rdquo; by Steven Pressfield is a book that offers valuable insights and practical advice to aspiring writers who are struggling to gain recognition for their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Down a Dream Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tim Grahl</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/running-down-a-dream-by-tim-grahl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:52:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/running-down-a-dream-by-tim-grahl/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Running Down a Dream: Your Road Map To Winning Creative Battles&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and practical guidebook written by Tim Grahl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elite Minds Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stan Beecham</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/elite-minds-by-stan-beecham/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:59 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/elite-minds-by-stan-beecham/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Elite Minds: How Winners Think Differently to Create a Competitive Edge and Maximize Success&amp;rdquo; by Stan Beecham is a book that explores the mindset and thinking patterns of high achievers and provides insights into how they approach challenges and maximize their potential for success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Bad Do You Want It? Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matt Fitzgerald</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-bad-do-you-want-it-by-matt-fitzgerald/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:29:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-bad-do-you-want-it-by-matt-fitzgerald/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How Bad Do You Want It?: Mastering the Psychology of Mind Over Muscle&amp;rdquo; by Matt Fitzgerald is a captivating exploration of the role of mental strength in athletic performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CREATOR Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steve Chandler</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/creator-by-steve-chandler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:20:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/creator-by-steve-chandler/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CREATOR&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Steve Chandler aimed at inspiring readers to unleash their creative potential and take charge of their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are Special Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Fred Rogers</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/you-are-special-by-fred-rogers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:12:52 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/you-are-special-by-fred-rogers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;You Are Special: Neighborly Words of Wisdom from Mister Rogers&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming and insightful book written by Fred Rogers, the beloved host of the popular children&amp;rsquo;s television program, Mister Rogers&amp;rsquo; Neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The World According to Mister Rogers Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Fred Rogers</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-world-according-to-mister-rogers-by-fred-rogers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:02:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-world-according-to-mister-rogers-by-fred-rogers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The World According to Mister Rogers: Important Things to Remember&amp;rdquo; is a book compiled from the words and wisdom of Fred Rogers, the beloved host of the children&amp;rsquo;s television program &amp;ldquo;Mister Rogers&amp;rsquo; Neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Time Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jake Knapp and John Zeratsky</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/make-time-by-jake-knapp-john-zeratsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 15:49:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/make-time-by-jake-knapp-john-zeratsky/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Make Time: How to Focus on What Matters Every Day&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Jake Knapp and John Zeratsky, two former Google employees who have experienced the challenges of navigating a busy and distracting world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Rules Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Medina</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/brain-rules-by-john-medina/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 15:34:40 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/brain-rules-by-john-medina/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Brain Rules: 12 Principles for Surviving and Thriving at Work, Home, and School&amp;rdquo; by John Medina is a captivating book that delves into the inner workings of the human brain and provides practical insights on how to optimize our performance, learning, and overall well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Many Ways to Say I Love You Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Fred Rogers</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/many-ways-to-say-i-love-you-by-fred-rogers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 15:21:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/many-ways-to-say-i-love-you-by-fred-rogers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Many Ways to Say I Love You: Wisdom for Parents and Children from Mister Rogers&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming book that compiles insightful thoughts and advice from Fred Rogers, the beloved host of the television show &amp;ldquo;Mister Rogers&amp;rsquo; Neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Courage to Be Disliked Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ichiro Kishimi and Fumitake Koga</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-courage-to-be-disliked-by-ichiro-kishimi-fumitake-koga/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 15:08:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-courage-to-be-disliked-by-ichiro-kishimi-fumitake-koga/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Courage to Be Disliked: The Japanese Phenomenon That Shows You How to Change Your Life and Achieve Real Happiness&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Ichiro Kishimi, a philosopher, and Fumitake Koga, a writer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Longitude Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dava Sobel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/longitude-by-dava-sobel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:56:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/longitude-by-dava-sobel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Longitude: The True Story of a Lone Genius Who Solved the Greatest Scientific Problem of His Time&amp;rdquo; by Dava Sobel is a non-fiction book that tells the captivating story of the quest to solve the problem of determining longitude at sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden Rules for Everyday Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Omraam Aivanhov</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/golden-rules-for-everyday-life-by-omraam-aivanhov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:47:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/golden-rules-for-everyday-life-by-omraam-aivanhov/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Golden Rules for Everyday Life&amp;rdquo; is a profound and enlightening book written by Omraam Aivanhov, a renowned spiritual teacher and philosopher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stillness Speaks Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eckhart Tolle</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stillness-speaks-by-eckhart-tolle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:38:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stillness-speaks-by-eckhart-tolle/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Stillness Speaks&amp;rdquo; is a spiritual guidebook written by Eckhart Tolle, the renowned author of &amp;ldquo;The Power of Now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words to Live By Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/words-to-live-by-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:20:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/words-to-live-by-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Words to Live By: Daily Inspiration for Spiritual Living&amp;rdquo; is a profound and uplifting book written by Eknath Easwaran, a renowned spiritual teacher, author, and translator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyday Zen Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Charlotte Beck</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/everyday-zen-by-charlotte-beck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:00:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/everyday-zen-by-charlotte-beck/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Everyday Zen: Love and Work&amp;rdquo; is a profound and insightful book written by Charlotte Joko Beck, a renowned Zen teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Passion Paradox Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brad Stulberg and Steve Magness</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-passion-paradox-by-brad-stulberg-steve-magness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:48:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-passion-paradox-by-brad-stulberg-steve-magness/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Passion Paradox: A Guide to Going All In, Finding Success, and Discovering the Benefits of an Unbalanced Life&amp;rdquo; by Brad Stulberg and Steve Magness is an exploration of the complex relationship between passion, success, and fulfillment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indistractable Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Nir Eyal</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/indistractable-by-nir-eyal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:28:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/indistractable-by-nir-eyal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Indistractable: How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Nir Eyal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superheroes and Philosophy Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Morris and Matt Morris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/superheroes-and-philosophy-by-tom-morris-matt-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:14:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/superheroes-and-philosophy-by-tom-morris-matt-morris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Superheroes and Philosophy: Truth, Justice, and the Socratic Way&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book co-authored by Tom Morris and Matt Morris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress Less, Accomplish More Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Emily Fletcher</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stress-less-accomplish-more-by-emily-fletcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 11:18:41 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stress-less-accomplish-more-by-emily-fletcher/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Stress Less, Accomplish More: Meditation for Extraordinary Performance&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Emily Fletcher, a renowned meditation teacher and founder of the Ziva technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Be a Stoic Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Massimo Pigliucci</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-a-stoic-by-massimo-pigliucci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 11:02:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-a-stoic-by-massimo-pigliucci/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Be a Stoic: Using Ancient Philosophy to Live a Modern Life&amp;rdquo; by Massimo Pigliucci is an interesting book that explores the practical application of Stoic philosophy in the modern world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Character Strengths Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ryan Niemiec and Robert Mcgrath</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-character-strengths-by-ryan-niemiec-robert-mcgrath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 10:44:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-character-strengths-by-ryan-niemiec-robert-mcgrath/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Character Strengths: Appreciate and Ignite Your Positive Personality&amp;rdquo; by Ryan Niemiec and Robert McGrath is a self-help book that explores the concept of character strengths and their impact on personal well-being and success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Healthy Deviant Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Pilar Gerasimo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-healthy-deviant-by-pilar-gerasimo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 10:14:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-healthy-deviant-by-pilar-gerasimo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Healthy Deviant: A Rule Breaker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Being Healthy in an Unhealthy World&amp;rdquo; by Pilar Gerasimo is a self-help book that challenges conventional wisdom and offers a fresh perspective on health and well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Wash Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Perlmutter and Austin Perlmutter</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/brain-wash-by-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 09:59:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/brain-wash-by-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Brain Wash: Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness&amp;rdquo; is a captivating book co-authored by Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discipline Equals Freedom Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jocko Willink</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/discipline-equals-freedom-by-jocko-willink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 09:42:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/discipline-equals-freedom-by-jocko-willink/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Discipline Equals Freedom: Field Manual Mk1-MOD1&amp;rdquo; is a motivational self-help book written by retired Navy SEAL officer Jocko Willink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyperfocus Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Chris Bailey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/hyperfocus-by-chris-bailey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 08:48:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/hyperfocus-by-chris-bailey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Hyperfocus: How to Manage Your Attention in a World of Distraction&amp;rdquo; by Chris Bailey is a self-help book that delves into the challenges of maintaining focus and managing attention in an increasingly distracted world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life&#39;s Great Question Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Rath</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/life-s-great-question-by-tom-rath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 08:40:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/life-s-great-question-by-tom-rath/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Life&amp;rsquo;s Great Question: Discover How You Contribute To The World&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Tom Rath, an American author known for his work in the field of personal development and well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Practicing Stoic Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ward Farnsworth</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-practicing-stoic-by-ward-farnsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 08:29:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-practicing-stoic-by-ward-farnsworth/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Practicing Stoic: A Philosophical User&amp;rsquo;s Manual&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Ward Farnsworth that delves into the principles and practices of Stoicism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stoic Art of Living Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Morris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-stoic-art-of-living-by-tom-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 08:17:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-stoic-art-of-living-by-tom-morris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Stoic Art of Living: Inner Resilience and Outer Results&amp;rdquo; is a philosophical self-help book written by Tom Morris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Book Will Make You Dangerous Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tripp Lanier</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/this-book-will-make-you-dangerous-by-tripp-lanier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 08:09:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/this-book-will-make-you-dangerous-by-tripp-lanier/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;This Book Will Make You Dangerous: The Irreverent Guide for Men Who Refuse to Settle&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Tripp Lanier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Positive Psychology and the Body Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Kate Hefferon</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/positive-psychology-and-the-body-by-kate-hefferon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 07:56:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/positive-psychology-and-the-body-by-kate-hefferon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Positive Psychology and the Body: The Somatopsychic Side to Flourishing&amp;rdquo; by Kate Hefferon explores the interconnection between positive psychology and the body, highlighting the significance of the mind-body relationship in achieving overall well-being and flourishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Be Free Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Epictetus and Anthony Long</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-free-by-epictetus-anthony-long/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 07:46:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-free-by-epictetus-anthony-long/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Be Free: An Ancient Guide to the Stoic Life&amp;rdquo; is a book that explores the teachings of the Stoic philosopher Epictetus, as compiled by his student Arrian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limitless Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jim Kwik</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/limitless-by-jim-kwik/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 07:36:12 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/limitless-by-jim-kwik/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Limitless: Upgrade Your Brain, Learn Anything Faster, and Unlock Your Exceptional Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Jim Kwik, a renowned brain coach and memory expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plato&#39;s Lemonade Stand Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Morris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/plato-s-lemonade-stand-by-tom-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 07:27:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/plato-s-lemonade-stand-by-tom-morris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Plato&amp;rsquo;s Lemonade Stand: Stirring Change into Something Great&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by Tom Morris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Human Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dave Asprey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/super-human-by-dave-asprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 07:16:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/super-human-by-dave-asprey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Super Human: The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book written by Dave Asprey, the creator of Bulletproof Coffee and a well-known biohacker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Genius Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Max Lugavere</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-genius-life-by-max-lugavere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 07:07:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-genius-life-by-max-lugavere/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Genius Life: Heal Your Mind, Strengthen Your Body, and Become Extraordinary&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Max Lugavere, a well-known health and science journalist and filmmaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stress Test Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ian Robertson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-stress-test-by-ian-robertson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 06:36:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-stress-test-by-ian-robertson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Stress Test: How Pressure Can Make You Stronger and Sharper&amp;rdquo; by Ian Robertson explores the concept of stress and its impact on human performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Genius in All of Us Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Shenk</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-genius-in-all-of-us-by-david-shenk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 06:26:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-genius-in-all-of-us-by-david-shenk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Genius in All of Us: New Insights into Genetics, Talent, and IQ&amp;rdquo; by David Shenk explores the complex interplay between genetics, environment, and personal effort in shaping human intelligence and talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Winner Effect Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ian Robertson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-winner-effect-by-ian-robertson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 06:16:44 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-winner-effect-by-ian-robertson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Winner Effect: The Science of Success and How to Use It&amp;rdquo; by Ian Robertson explores the fascinating relationship between success, power, and the brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Bed Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Admiral William McRaven</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/make-your-bed-by-admiral-william-mcraven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 06:06:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/make-your-bed-by-admiral-william-mcraven/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Make Your Bed&amp;rdquo; is a motivational book written by Admiral William H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Fragility Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robin DiAngelo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/white-fragility-by-robin-diangelo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 05:50:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/white-fragility-by-robin-diangelo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;White Fragility: Why It&amp;rsquo;s So Hard for White People to Talk About Racism&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking and influential book written by Robin DiAngelo, an American author, lecturer, and diversity trainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fearless Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Eric Dyson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fearless-by-michael-eric-dyson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 05:38:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fearless-by-michael-eric-dyson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fearless: The Undaunted Courage and Ultimate Sacrifice of Navy SEAL Team SIX Operator Adam Brown&amp;rdquo; is a gripping and inspirational biography written by Eric Blehm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JAY-Z Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Eric Dyson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/jay-z-by-michael-eric-dyson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 05:22:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/jay-z-by-michael-eric-dyson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;JAY-Z: Made in America&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Michael Eric Dyson that delves into the life and cultural impact of one of the most influential figures in hip-hop and popular culture, Shawn Corey Carter, better known as JAY-Z.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Freak Factor Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Rendall</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-freak-factor-by-david-rendall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 05:11:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-freak-factor-by-david-rendall/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Freak Factor: Discovering Uniqueness by Flaunting Weakness&amp;rdquo; by David Rendall is a book that challenges conventional wisdom by encouraging individuals to embrace their weaknesses and use them as strengths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driven Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Douglas Brackmann and Randy Kelley</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/driven-by-douglas-brackmann-randy-kelley/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:58:03 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/driven-by-douglas-brackmann-randy-kelley/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Driven: Understanding and Harnessing the Genetic Gifts Shared by Entrepreneurs, Navy SEALs, Pro Athletes, and Maybe YOU&amp;rdquo; by Douglas Brackmann and Randy Kelley is a captivating exploration of the genetic factors that contribute to the exceptional performance of individuals in various fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Talk to Anyone, Anytime, Anywhere Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Larry King and Bill Gilbert</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-talk-to-anyone-anytime-anywhere-by-larry-king-bill-gilbert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:46:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-talk-to-anyone-anytime-anywhere-by-larry-king-bill-gilbert/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Talk to Anyone, Anytime, Anywhere: The Secrets of Good Communication&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Larry King, a renowned television and radio host, and Bill Gilbert, a communication expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parenting Champions Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Lanny Bassham</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/parenting-champions-by-lanny-bassham/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:32:19 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/parenting-champions-by-lanny-bassham/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Parenting Champions: What Every Parent Should Know About the Mental Game&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Lanny Bassham, a renowned mental coach and Olympic gold medalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raise Your Game Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alan Stein Jr. and Jon Sternfeld</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/raise-your-game-by-alan-stein-jr-jon-sternfeld/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:19:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/raise-your-game-by-alan-stein-jr-jon-sternfeld/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Raise Your Game: High-Performance Secrets from the Best of the Best&amp;rdquo; by Alan Stein Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Seuss &amp; Mr. Geisel Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Judith Morgan and Neil Morgan</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/dr-seuss-mr-geisel-by-judith-morgan-neil-morgan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:11:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/dr-seuss-mr-geisel-by-judith-morgan-neil-morgan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Dr. Seuss &amp;amp; Mr. Geisel: A Biography&amp;rdquo; by Judith and Neil Morgan is a comprehensive exploration of the life and work of Theodor Geisel, better known as Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Means Business Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alan Cohen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spirit-means-business-by-alan-cohen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:00:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spirit-means-business-by-alan-cohen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spirit Means Business: The Way to Prosper Wildly Without Selling Your Soul&amp;rdquo; is a transformative book written by Alan Cohen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can&#39;t Hurt Me Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Goggins</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:48:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Can&amp;rsquo;t Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds&amp;rdquo; is a self-help memoir written by David Goggins, a retired Navy SEAL and former U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relentless Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tim Grover and Shari Wenk</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/relentless-by-tim-grover-shari-wenk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:37:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/relentless-by-tim-grover-shari-wenk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Relentless: From Good to Great to Unstoppable&amp;rdquo; is a self-help and personal development book written by Tim Grover, a renowned sports performance coach who has worked with elite athletes, including Michael Jordan and Kobe Bryant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Effective Executive Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Peter Drucker</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-effective-executive-by-peter-drucker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:24:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-effective-executive-by-peter-drucker/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Effective Executive: The Definitive Guide to Getting the Right Things Done&amp;rdquo; is a management book written by Peter Drucker, one of the most influential thinkers in the field of management and leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sapiens Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Yuval Noah Harari</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sapiens-by-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:55:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sapiens-by-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind&amp;rdquo; by Yuval Noah Harari is a captivating exploration of the history of Homo sapiens, from the emergence of our species in Africa to the present day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sea Stories Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Admiral William McRaven</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sea-stories-by-admiral-william-mcraven/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:40:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sea-stories-by-admiral-william-mcraven/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sea Stories: My Life in Special Operations&amp;rdquo; is a captivating memoir written by Admiral William McRaven, a retired U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Rituals Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mason Currey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/daily-rituals-by-mason-currey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:28:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/daily-rituals-by-mason-currey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Daily Rituals: How Artists Work&amp;rdquo; by Mason Currey is a fascinating exploration of the daily routines and habits of some of the most renowned artists, writers, composers, and thinkers throughout history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Learning Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Josh Waitzkin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-learning-by-josh-waitzkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:17:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-learning-by-josh-waitzkin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Art of Learning: An Inner Journey to Optimal Performance&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Josh Waitzkin, a former child prodigy in chess who later became a world champion in martial arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hero with a Thousand Faces Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joseph Campbell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-hero-with-a-thousand-faces-by-joseph-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:04:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-hero-with-a-thousand-faces-by-joseph-campbell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Hero with a Thousand Faces&amp;rdquo; is an intriguing work written by Joseph Campbell, an American mythologist and writer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seven Principles for Making Marriage Work Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Gottman and Nan Silver</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-seven-principles-for-making-marriage-work-by-john-gottman-nan-silver/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:27:41 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-seven-principles-for-making-marriage-work-by-john-gottman-nan-silver/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Seven Principles for Making Marriage Work: A Practical Guide from the Country&amp;rsquo;s Foremost Relationship Expert&amp;rdquo; is a book written by renowned psychologist and relationship expert John Gottman, along with Nan Silver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Relaxation Response Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Herbert Benson and Miriam Klipper</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-relaxation-response-by-herbert-benson-miriam-klipper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:14:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-relaxation-response-by-herbert-benson-miriam-klipper/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Relaxation Response&amp;rdquo; by Herbert Benson and Miriam Klipper is a groundbreaking book that explores the physiological and psychological benefits of relaxation techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organize Tomorrow Today Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jason Selk, Tom Bartow and Matthew Rudy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/organize-tomorrow-today-by-jason-selk-tom-bartow-matthew-rudy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:00:09 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/organize-tomorrow-today-by-jason-selk-tom-bartow-matthew-rudy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Organize Tomorrow Today: 8 Ways to Retrain Your Mind to Optimize Performance at Work and in Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Jason Selk, Tom Bartow, and Matthew Rudy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thich Nhat Hanh</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fear-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:36:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fear-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fear: Essential Wisdom for Getting Through the Storm&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Thich Nhat Hanh, a renowned Buddhist monk, peace activist, and teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Things Done Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Allen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/getting-things-done-by-david-allen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:24:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/getting-things-done-by-david-allen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Getting Things Done: The Art of Stress-Free Productivity&amp;rdquo; by David Allen is a self-help book that provides a comprehensive system for organizing, prioritizing, and completing tasks in order to achieve stress-free productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Think Like a Roman Emperor Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Donald Robertson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-think-like-a-roman-emperor-by-donald-robertson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:14:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-think-like-a-roman-emperor-by-donald-robertson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Think Like a Roman Emperor: The Stoic Philosophy of Marcus Aurelius&amp;rdquo; by Donald Robertson is a compelling exploration of Stoic philosophy through the lens of the life and teachings of the Roman Emperor Marcus Aurelius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Say When You Talk To Your Self Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Shad Helmstetter</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/what-to-say-when-you-talk-to-your-self-by-shad-helmstetter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:57:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/what-to-say-when-you-talk-to-your-self-by-shad-helmstetter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What To Say When You Talk To Your Self&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Shad Helmstetter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Habit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jack Hodge</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-habit-by-jack-hodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:45:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-habit-by-jack-hodge/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Habit: Harnessing the Power to Establish Routines that Guarantee Success in Business and in Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Charles Duhigg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Success Principles Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jack Canfield and Janet Switzer</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-success-principles-by-jack-canfield-janet-switzer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:31:19 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-success-principles-by-jack-canfield-janet-switzer/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Success Principles: How to Get from Where You Are to Where You Want to Be&amp;rdquo; by Jack Canfield and Janet Switzer is a self-help book that aims to guide readers towards achieving their goals and creating a successful life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Monk Who Sold His Ferrari Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robin Sharma</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-monk-who-sold-his-ferrari-by-robin-sharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:19:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-monk-who-sold-his-ferrari-by-robin-sharma/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Monk Who Sold His Ferrari: A Fable About Fulfilling Your Dreams &amp;amp; Reaching Your Destiny&amp;rdquo; by Robin Sharma is a motivational and engaging self-help book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Myth Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joseph Campbell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-myth-by-joseph-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:04:14 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-myth-by-joseph-campbell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Myth&amp;rdquo; is a captivating exploration of mythology and its significance in human culture, written by Joseph Campbell, a renowned comparative mythologist and scholar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psycho-Cybernetics Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Maxwell Maltz</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/psycho-cybernetics-by-maxwell-maltz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 10:47:40 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/psycho-cybernetics-by-maxwell-maltz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Psycho-Cybernetics&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Maxwell Maltz, a plastic surgeon and motivational author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Stop Worrying and Start Living Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dale Carnegie</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-stop-worrying-and-start-living-by-dale-carnegie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 10:26:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-stop-worrying-and-start-living-by-dale-carnegie/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Stop Worrying and Start Living&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Dale Carnegie, the acclaimed author of &amp;ldquo;How to Win Friends and Influence People.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staring Down the Wolf Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mark Divine</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/staring-down-the-wolf-by-mark-divine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 10:14:44 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/staring-down-the-wolf-by-mark-divine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Staring Down the Wolf: 7 Leadership Commitments That Forge Elite Teams&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Mark Divine, a former Navy SEAL and founder of SEALFIT, a training program that incorporates the principles and practices of the Navy SEALs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadershift Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Maxwell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leadershift-by-john-maxwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 10:03:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leadershift-by-john-maxwell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Leadershift: The 11 Essential Changes Every Leader Must Embrace&amp;rdquo; is a book written by John C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stoic Challenge Summary of Key Ideas and Review - William Irvine</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-stoic-challenge-by-william-irvine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:25:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-stoic-challenge-by-william-irvine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Stoic Challenge: A Philosopher&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Becoming Tougher, Calmer, and More Resilient&amp;rdquo; by William Irvine is a book that explores the philosophy of Stoicism and provides practical advice on how to apply Stoic principles in daily life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Alter Ego Effect Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Todd Herman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-alter-ego-effect-by-todd-herman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 08:40:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-alter-ego-effect-by-todd-herman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Alter Ego Effect: The Power of Secret Identities to Transform Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Todd Herman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Worked for Me Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Colin Powell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/it-worked-for-me-by-colin-powell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 08:30:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/it-worked-for-me-by-colin-powell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It Worked for Me: In Life and Leadership&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Colin Powell, a retired four-star general in the United States Army and former U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Hope Happen Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Shane Lopez</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/making-hope-happen-by-shane-lopez/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 08:13:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/making-hope-happen-by-shane-lopez/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Making Hope Happen: Create the Future You Want for Yourself and Others&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Shane J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eat Move Sleep Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Rath</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/eat-move-sleep-by-tom-rath/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 07:52:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/eat-move-sleep-by-tom-rath/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Eat Move Sleep: How Small Choices Lead to Big Changes&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Tom Rath, a bestselling author and renowned expert on the role of human behavior in business and health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning Pro Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Pressfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/turning-pro-by-steven-pressfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 06:35:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/turning-pro-by-steven-pressfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Turning Pro: Tap Your Inner Power and Create Your Life&amp;rsquo;s Work&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Steven Pressfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Unstoppable Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alden Mills</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/be-unstoppable-by-alden-mills/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 06:21:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/be-unstoppable-by-alden-mills/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Be Unstoppable: The 8 Essential Actions to Succeed at Anything&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Alden Mills, a former Navy SEAL and successful entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Born to Run Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Christopher McDougall</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/born-to-run-by-christopher-mcdougall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 06:12:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/born-to-run-by-christopher-mcdougall/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Born to Run: A Hidden Tribe, Superathletes, and the Greatest Race the World Has Never Seen&amp;rdquo; by Christopher McDougall is a captivating non-fiction book that explores the world of ultra-distance running and the remarkable endurance of the Tarahumara, a reclusive indigenous tribe living in the remote Copper Canyons of Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Meditate Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matthieu Ricard</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/why-meditate-by-matthieu-ricard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:59:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/why-meditate-by-matthieu-ricard/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Why Meditate: Working with Thoughts and Emotions&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Matthieu Ricard, a French Buddhist monk, author, and translator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Russell Simmons and Chris Morrow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/do-you-by-russell-simmons-chris-morrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:45:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/do-you-by-russell-simmons-chris-morrow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do You!: 12 Laws to Access the Power in You to Achieve Happiness and Success&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Russell Simmons, a successful entrepreneur and co-founder of Def Jam Recordings, and Chris Morrow, a writer and entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Succeed Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Heidi Grant Halvorson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/succeed-by-heidi-grant-halvorson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:30:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/succeed-by-heidi-grant-halvorson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Succeed: How We Can Reach Our Goals&amp;rdquo; by Heidi Grant Halvorson is a self-help book that delves into the science of achievement and provides practical strategies to help individuals achieve their goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Long! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jerry Rice and Brian Curtis</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/go-long-by-jerry-rice-brian-curtis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:24:21 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/go-long-by-jerry-rice-brian-curtis/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Go Long!: My Journey Beyond the Game and the Fame&amp;rdquo; is a memoir written by Jerry Rice, widely considered one of the greatest wide receivers in the history of the National Football League (NFL).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conquest of Mind Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/conquest-of-mind-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:11:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/conquest-of-mind-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Conquest of Mind: Take Charge of Your Thoughts and Reshape Your Life Through Meditation&amp;rdquo; is a transformative book written by Eknath Easwaran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eat That Frog! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brian Tracy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/eat-that-frog-by-brian-tracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 04:52:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/eat-that-frog-by-brian-tracy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Eat That Frog!: 21 Great Ways to Stop Procrastinating and Get More Done in Less Time&amp;rdquo; by Brian Tracy is a self-help book that provides practical strategies for overcoming procrastination and increasing productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/creativity-by-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 04:40:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/creativity-by-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Creativity: Flow and the Psychology of Discovery and Invention&amp;rdquo; by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi explores the nature of creativity and provides valuable insights into the psychological processes that underlie creative thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wherever You Go, There You Are Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jon Kabat-Zinn</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-by-jon-kabat-zinn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:17:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-by-jon-kabat-zinn/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wherever You Go, There You Are: Mindfulness Meditation in Everyday Life&amp;rdquo; is a transformative book written by Jon Kabat-Zinn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindsight Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Siegel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mindsight-by-daniel-siegel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:01:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mindsight-by-daniel-siegel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mindsight: The New Science of Personal Transformation&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book written by Daniel Siegel, a renowned psychiatrist and neuroscientist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gifts of Imperfection Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brené Brown</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-gifts-of-imperfection-by-brene-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:46:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-gifts-of-imperfection-by-brene-brown/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Gifts of Imperfection&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Brené Brown, a research professor at the University of Houston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nonviolent Communication Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Marshall Rosenberg</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/nonviolent-communication-by-marshall-rosenberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:47:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/nonviolent-communication-by-marshall-rosenberg/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Nonviolent Communication: A Language of Life: Life-Changing Tools for Healthy Relationships&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Marshall Rosenberg, a psychologist and founder of the Center for Nonviolent Communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness of Pursuit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Chris Guillebeau</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-of-pursuit-by-chris-guillebeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:38:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-of-pursuit-by-chris-guillebeau/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness of Pursuit: Finding the Quest That Will Bring Purpose to Your Life&amp;rdquo; by Chris Guillebeau is a self-help book that explores the concept of quests and how they can bring purpose and happiness to one&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are the Placebo Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Joe Dispenza</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/you-are-the-placebo-by-joe-dispenza/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:22:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/you-are-the-placebo-by-joe-dispenza/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;You Are the Placebo: Making Your Mind Matter&amp;rdquo; by Joe Dispenza is a transformative book that explores the power of the mind in healing and personal transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counterclockwise Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ellen Langer</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/counterclockwise-by-ellen-langer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:12:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/counterclockwise-by-ellen-langer/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Counterclockwise: Mindful Health and the Power of Possibility&amp;rdquo; is an intellectually challenging book written by Ellen Langer, a renowned social psychologist and Harvard professor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attainment Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Troy Bassham</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/attainment-by-troy-bassham/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:59:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/attainment-by-troy-bassham/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Attainment: The 12 Elements of Elite Performance&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Troy Bassham, a renowned sports psychologist and coach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take the Stairs Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Rory Vaden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/take-the-stairs-by-rory-vaden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:13:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/take-the-stairs-by-rory-vaden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Take the Stairs: 7 Steps to Achieving True Success&amp;rdquo; is a captivating self-help book written by Rory Vaden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Spirit Medicine Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alberto Villoldo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/one-spirit-medicine-by-alberto-villoldo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:01:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/one-spirit-medicine-by-alberto-villoldo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;One Spirit Medicine: Ancient Ways to Ultimate Wellness&amp;rdquo; is a transformative guide written by Alberto Villoldo, a renowned medical anthropologist and shamanic healer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steal Like an Artist Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Austin Kleon</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/steal-like-an-artist-by-austin-kleon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:53:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/steal-like-an-artist-by-austin-kleon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Steal Like an Artist: 10 Things Nobody Told You About Being Creative&amp;rdquo; by Austin Kleon is a self-help book that explores the process of creativity and offers practical advice to aspiring artists and creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David and Goliath Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Malcolm Gladwell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/david-and-goliath-by-malcolm-gladwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:43:40 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/david-and-goliath-by-malcolm-gladwell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;David and Goliath: Underdogs, Misfits, and the Art of Battling Giants&amp;rdquo; is a non-fiction and engaging book written by Malcolm Gladwell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Myths of Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sonja Lyubomirsky</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-myths-of-happiness-by-sonja-lyubomirsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:34:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-myths-of-happiness-by-sonja-lyubomirsky/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Myths of Happiness: What Should Make You Happy, but Doesn&amp;rsquo;t, What Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t Make You Happy, but Does&amp;rdquo; is a profound book written by Sonja Lyubomirsky, a prominent psychology professor and researcher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Astronaut&#39;s Guide to Life on Earth Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Chris Hadfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/an-astronaut-s-guide-to-life-on-earth-by-chris-hadfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:02:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/an-astronaut-s-guide-to-life-on-earth-by-chris-hadfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;An Astronaut&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Life on Earth: What Going to Space Taught Me About Ingenuity, Determination, and Being Prepared for Anything&amp;rdquo; is a memoir written by Chris Hadfield, a retired Canadian astronaut and former commander of the International Space Station (ISS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Champion&#39;s Mind Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jim Afremow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-champion-s-mind-by-jim-afremow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:52:41 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-champion-s-mind-by-jim-afremow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Champion&amp;rsquo;s Mind: How Great Athletes Think, Train, and Thrive&amp;rdquo; by Jim Afremow is a compelling guide that delves into the mindset and training techniques of successful athletes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smarter Faster Better Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Charles Duhigg</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/smarter-faster-better-by-charles-duhigg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:40:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/smarter-faster-better-by-charles-duhigg/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Smarter Faster Better: The Secrets of Being Productive in Life and Business&amp;rdquo; by Charles Duhigg is a self-help book that explores the science and psychology behind productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 5 Second Rule Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mel Robbins</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-5-second-rule-by-mel-robbins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:27:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-5-second-rule-by-mel-robbins/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 5 Second Rule: Transform Your Life, Work, and Confidence with Everyday Courage&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Mel Robbins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unstoppable Teams Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alden Mills</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/unstoppable-teams-by-alden-mills/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:19:12 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/unstoppable-teams-by-alden-mills/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Unstoppable Teams: The Four Essential Actions of High-Performance Leadership&amp;rdquo; by Alden Mills is a leadership book that explores the fundamental principles and actions necessary to build and lead successful teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love 2.0 Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Barbara Fredrickson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/love-2-0-by-barbara-fredrickson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:09:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/love-2-0-by-barbara-fredrickson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Love 2.0: Creating Happiness and Health in Moments of Connection&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Barbara Fredrickson, a renowned psychologist and researcher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Maxwell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-21-irrefutable-laws-of-leadership-by-john-maxwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:55:03 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-21-irrefutable-laws-of-leadership-by-john-maxwell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership: Follow Them and People Will Follow You&amp;rdquo; by John C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Procrastination Equation Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Piers Steel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-procrastination-equation-by-piers-steel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:41:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-procrastination-equation-by-piers-steel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Procrastination Equation: How to Stop Putting Things Off and Start Getting Stuff Done&amp;rdquo; by Piers Steel is a self-help book that delves into the complex psychological factors underlying procrastination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Habits Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stephen Guise</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mini-habits-by-stephen-guise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:09:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mini-habits-by-stephen-guise/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mini Habits: Smaller Habits, Bigger Results&amp;rdquo; by Stephen Guise is a self-help book that offers a fresh perspective on building effective habits and achieving personal goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Scott Adams</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-by-scott-adams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:53:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-by-scott-adams/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big: Kind of the Story of My Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Scott Adams, the creator of the popular comic strip &amp;ldquo;Dilbert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Undefeated Mind Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alex Lickerman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-undefeated-mind-by-alex-lickerman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:39:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-undefeated-mind-by-alex-lickerman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Undefeated Mind: On the Science of Constructing an Indestructible Self&amp;rdquo; by Alex Lickerman is a self-help book that explores the concept of resilience and offers strategies for developing an unwavering mindset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The War of Art Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Pressfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-war-of-art-by-steven-pressfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:30:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-war-of-art-by-steven-pressfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The War of Art: Break Through the Blocks and Win Your Inner Creative Battles&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Steven Pressfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Full Engagement Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jim Loehr and Tony Schwartz</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-full-engagement-by-jim-loehr-tony-schwartz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:20:21 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-full-engagement-by-jim-loehr-tony-schwartz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Full Engagement: Managing Energy, Not Time, Is the Key to High Performance and Personal Renewal&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Jim Loehr and Tony Schwartz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 80/20 Principle Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Richard Koch</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-80-20-principle-by-richard-koch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:03:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-80-20-principle-by-richard-koch/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 80/20 Principle&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Richard Koch, a British author and management consultant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastery Summary of Key Ideas and Review - George Leonard</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastery-by-george-leonard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:36:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastery-by-george-leonard/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mastery: The Keys to Success and Long-Term Fulfillment&amp;rdquo; by George Leonard is a compelling guide that explores the path to mastery in any field and offers insights into achieving long-term success and personal fulfillment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Constructive Living Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Reynolds</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/constructive-living-by-david-reynolds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:20:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/constructive-living-by-david-reynolds/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Constructive Living&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by David K. Reynolds, blending elements from Western psychotherapy and Eastern philosophical traditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As a Man Thinketh Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Allen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/as-a-man-thinketh-by-james-allen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:07:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/as-a-man-thinketh-by-james-allen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;As a Man Thinketh&amp;rdquo; is a classic self-help book written by James Allen and first published in 1903.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Joseph Campbell Companion Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joseph Campbell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-joseph-campbell-companion-by-joseph-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 07:59:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-joseph-campbell-companion-by-joseph-campbell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Joseph Campbell Companion: Reflections on the Art of Living&amp;rdquo; is a collection of essays, interviews, and lectures by Joseph Campbell, a renowned mythologist, writer, and lecturer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smartcuts Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Shane Snow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/smartcuts-by-shane-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 07:46:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/smartcuts-by-shane-snow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Smartcuts: The Breakthrough Power of Lateral Thinking&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Shane Snow, an entrepreneur, journalist, and technology writer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Intelligence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Goleman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/emotional-intelligence-by-daniel-goleman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 07:36:12 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/emotional-intelligence-by-daniel-goleman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Emotional Intelligence: Why It Can Matter More Than IQ&amp;rdquo; by Daniel Goleman explores the concept of emotional intelligence and its significance for personal and professional success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Picture Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tony Horton</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-big-picture-by-tony-horton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 07:06:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-big-picture-by-tony-horton/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Big Picture: 11 Laws That Will Change Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Tony Horton, a well-known fitness trainer and personal development expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1:59 Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Philip Maffetone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/1-59-by-philip-maffetone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:55:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/1-59-by-philip-maffetone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;1:59: The Sub-Two-Hour Marathon Is Within Reach—Here&amp;rsquo;s How It Will Go Down, and What It Can Teach All Runners About Training and Racing&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Philip Maffetone, a renowned endurance coach and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Straight-A Student Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Cal Newport</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-become-a-straight-a-student-by-cal-newport/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:44:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-become-a-straight-a-student-by-cal-newport/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Become a Straight-A Student: The Unconventional Strategies Real College Students Use to Score High While Studying Less&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Cal Newport, a renowned author and professor of computer science at Georgetown University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Upside of Stress Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Kelly McGonigal</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-upside-of-stress-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:31:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-upside-of-stress-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Upside of Stress: Why Stress Is Good for You, and How to Get Good at It&amp;rdquo; by Kelly McGonigal is a groundbreaking book that challenges the traditional negative perception of stress and offers a fresh perspective on its benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Originals Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Adam Grant</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/originals-by-adam-grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:24:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/originals-by-adam-grant/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Originals: How Non-Conformists Move the World&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by Adam Grant, a renowned organizational psychologist and Wharton professor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Limits Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Phelps</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/no-limits-by-michael-phelps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:18:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/no-limits-by-michael-phelps/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;No Limits: The Will to Succeed&amp;rdquo; is a memoir written by Michael Phelps, one of the most successful and decorated athletes in Olympic history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spartan Fit! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joe De Sena and John Durant</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spartan-fit-by-joe-de-sena-john-durant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:08:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spartan-fit-by-joe-de-sena-john-durant/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spartan Fit!: 30 Days. Transform Your Mind. Transform Your Body. Commit to Grit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Obstacle Is the Way Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ryan Holiday</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-obstacle-is-the-way-by-ryan-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 05:21:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-obstacle-is-the-way-by-ryan-holiday/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Obstacle Is the Way: The Timeless Art of Turning Trials into Triumph&amp;rdquo; is an intellectually challenging and inspiring self-help book written by Ryan Holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spark Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Ratey and Eric Hagerman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spark-by-john-ratey-eric-hagerman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 05:08:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spark-by-john-ratey-eric-hagerman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spark: The Revolutionary New Science of Exercise and the Brain&amp;rdquo; is a book written by John Ratey, a renowned psychiatrist, and Eric Hagerman, a journalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Born Heroes Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Christopher McDougall</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/natural-born-heroes-by-christopher-mcdougall/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:51:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/natural-born-heroes-by-christopher-mcdougall/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Natural Born Heroes: Mastering the Lost Secrets of Strength and Endurance&amp;rdquo; is a non-fiction book written by Christopher McDougall, the author of the best-selling book &amp;ldquo;Born to Run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolution Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joe Manganiello</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/evolution-by-joe-manganiello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:41:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/evolution-by-joe-manganiello/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Evolution: The Cutting-Edge Guide to Breaking Down Mental Walls and Building the Body You&amp;rsquo;ve Always Wanted&amp;rdquo; is a self-help and fitness book written by Joe Manganiello.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Willpower Instinct Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Kelly McGonigal</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-willpower-instinct-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:26:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-willpower-instinct-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Willpower Instinct: How Self-Control Works, Why It Matters, and What You Can Do to Get More of It&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Kelly McGonigal, a health psychologist and lecturer at Stanford University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conscious Breathing Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Anders Olsson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/conscious-breathing-by-anders-olsson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:10:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/conscious-breathing-by-anders-olsson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Conscious Breathing: Discover The Power of Your Breath&amp;rdquo; by Anders Olsson is a transformative guide that explores the profound impact of conscious breathing on physical, mental, and emotional well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move Your DNA Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Katy Bowman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/move-your-dna-by-katy-bowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:59:44 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/move-your-dna-by-katy-bowman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Move Your DNA: Restore Your Health Through Natural Movement&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Katy Bowman, a biomechanist and movement educator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Character Strengths Matter Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Shannon Polly and Kathryn Britton</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/character-strengths-matter-by-shannon-polly-kathryn-britton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:46:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/character-strengths-matter-by-shannon-polly-kathryn-britton/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Character Strengths Matter: How to Live a Full Life&amp;rdquo; by Shannon Polly and Kathryn Britton is a book that explores the concept of character strengths and how they can be harnessed to live a more fulfilling and meaningful life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10-Minute Toughness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jason Selk</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/10-minute-toughness-by-jason-selk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:29:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/10-minute-toughness-by-jason-selk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;10-Minute Toughness: The Mental Training Program for Winning Before the Game Begins&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Jason Selk, a renowned performance coach and mental toughness expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bored and Brilliant Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Manoush Zomorodi</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bored-and-brilliant-by-manoush-zomorodi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:09:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bored-and-brilliant-by-manoush-zomorodi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Bored and Brilliant: How Spacing Out Can Unlock Your Most Productive and Creative Self&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Manoush Zomorodi, a journalist and podcast host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling Upward Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Richard Rohr</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/falling-upward-by-richard-rohr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 15:26:59 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/falling-upward-by-richard-rohr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Falling Upward: A Spirituality for the Two Halves of Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Richard Rohr, a Franciscan priest and renowned spiritual teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waking Up Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sam Harris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/waking-up-by-sam-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 15:10:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/waking-up-by-sam-harris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Waking Up: A Guide to Spirituality Without Religion&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Sam Harris, a neuroscientist, philosopher, and prominent atheist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Distraction Addiction Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alex Soojung-Kim Pang</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-distraction-addiction-by-alex-soojung-kim-pang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:49:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-distraction-addiction-by-alex-soojung-kim-pang/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Distraction Addiction: Getting the Information You Need and the Communication You Want, Without Enraging Your Family, Annoying Your Colleagues, and Destroying Your Soul&amp;rdquo; is an engaging book written by Alex Soojung-Kim Pang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Die Empty Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Todd Henry</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/die-empty-by-todd-henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:35:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/die-empty-by-todd-henry/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Die Empty: Unleash Your Best Work Every Day&amp;rdquo; by Todd Henry is a motivational and practical guide that aims to help individuals tap into their full creative potential and make a meaningful impact in their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Inner Game of Tennis Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Timothy Gallwey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-inner-game-of-tennis-by-timothy-gallwey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:28:14 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-inner-game-of-tennis-by-timothy-gallwey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Inner Game of Tennis: The Classic Guide to the Mental Side of Peak Performance&amp;rdquo; by Timothy Gallwey is a groundbreaking book that explores the psychological aspects of tennis and how they can be applied to improve overall performance in sports and life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courage Under Fire Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Stockdale</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/courage-under-fire-by-james-stockdale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:18:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/courage-under-fire-by-james-stockdale/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Courage Under Fire: Testing Epictetus&amp;rsquo;s Doctrines in a Laboratory of Human Behavior&amp;rdquo; is a book written by James Stockdale, a former United States Navy admiral and Vietnam War veteran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bruce Lee Striking Thoughts Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Bruce Lee</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bruce-lee-striking-thoughts-by-bruce-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 12:56:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bruce-lee-striking-thoughts-by-bruce-lee/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Bruce Lee Striking Thoughts: Bruce Lee&amp;rsquo;s Wisdom for Daily Living&amp;rdquo; is a compilation of Bruce Lee&amp;rsquo;s philosophical and insightful writings, compiled and edited by John Little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Iron Will Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Orison Swett Marden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/an-iron-will-by-orison-swett-marden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 12:47:42 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/an-iron-will-by-orison-swett-marden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;An Iron Will&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Orison Swett Marden, a prominent American author and founder of Success magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EntreLeadership Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dave Ramsey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/entreleadership-by-dave-ramsey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 12:36:39 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/entreleadership-by-dave-ramsey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;EntreLeadership: 20 Years of Practical Business Wisdom from the Trenches&amp;rdquo; by Dave Ramsey is a comprehensive guide that combines the principles of entrepreneurship and leadership to help individuals build successful businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Complaint Free World Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Will Bowen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-complaint-free-world-by-will-bowen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 12:27:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-complaint-free-world-by-will-bowen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Complaint Free World: How to Stop Complaining and Start Enjoying the Life You Always Wanted&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Will Bowen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Now Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eckhart Tolle</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-now-by-eckhart-tolle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 12:18:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-now-by-eckhart-tolle/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Now: A Guide to Spiritual Enlightenment&amp;rdquo; by Eckhart Tolle is a transformative self-help book that aims to guide readers toward achieving spiritual enlightenment and living in the present moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fountainhead Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ayn Rand</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-fountainhead-by-ayn-rand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 12:06:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-fountainhead-by-ayn-rand/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Fountainhead&amp;rdquo; is a philosophical novel written by Ayn Rand and first published in 1943.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Second Mountain Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Brooks</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-second-mountain-by-david-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:52:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-second-mountain-by-david-brooks/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Second Mountain: The Quest for a Moral Life&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by David Brooks, an American journalist, commentator, and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gandhi the Man Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/gandhi-the-man-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:43:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/gandhi-the-man-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Gandhi the Man: How One Man Changed Himself to Change the World&amp;rdquo; by Eknath Easwaran is a profound exploration of the life and teachings of Mahatma Gandhi, the influential leader of India&amp;rsquo;s nonviolent independence movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Spartan Way Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joe De Sena</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-spartan-way-by-joe-de-sena/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:31:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-spartan-way-by-joe-de-sena/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Spartan Way: Eat Better. Train Better. Think Better. Be Better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book of Understanding Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Osho</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-book-of-understanding-by-osho/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:24:09 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-book-of-understanding-by-osho/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Book of Understanding: Creating Your Own Path to Freedom&amp;rdquo; is a spiritual guide written by Osho, an Indian mystic and philosopher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ONE Thing Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gary Keller and Jay Papasan</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-one-thing-by-gary-keller-jay-papasan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:12:52 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-one-thing-by-gary-keller-jay-papasan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The ONE Thing: The Surprisingly Simple Truth About Extraordinary Results&amp;rdquo; by Gary Keller and Jay Papasan is a self-help book that focuses on the power of focusing on one thing at a time to achieve extraordinary results in all areas of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Win Friends and Influence People Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dale Carnegie</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-win-friends-and-influence-people-by-dale-carnegie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:06:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-win-friends-and-influence-people-by-dale-carnegie/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Win Friends and Influence People&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Dale Carnegie and first published in 1936.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Checklist Manifesto Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Atul Gawande</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-checklist-manifesto-by-atul-gawande/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:53:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-checklist-manifesto-by-atul-gawande/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Checklist Manifesto: How to Get Things Right&amp;rdquo; by Atul Gawande is a non-fiction book that explores the power and effectiveness of checklists in various fields, ranging from medicine and aviation to construction and finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Reliance Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ralph Waldo Emerson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/self-reliance-by-ralph-waldo-emerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:21:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/self-reliance-by-ralph-waldo-emerson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Self-Reliance&amp;rdquo; is an essay written by Ralph Waldo Emerson, one of the most prominent American transcendentalist philosophers of the 19th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4 Disciplines of Execution Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Chris McChesney, Sean Covey and Jim Huling</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-4-disciplines-of-execution-by-chris-mcchesney-sean-covey-jim-huling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:05:44 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-4-disciplines-of-execution-by-chris-mcchesney-sean-covey-jim-huling/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 4 Disciplines of Execution: Achieving Your Wildly Important Goals&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Chris McChesney, Sean Covey, and Jim Huling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming Alive Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Barry Michels and Phil Stutz</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/coming-alive-by-barry-michels-phil-stutz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:55:59 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/coming-alive-by-barry-michels-phil-stutz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Coming Alive: 4 Tools to Defeat Your Inner Enemy, Ignite Creative Expression &amp;amp; Unleash Your Soul&amp;rsquo;s Potential&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Barry Michels and Phil Stutz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Philosophy of Cognitive-Behavioural Therapy (CBT) Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Donald Robertson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-philosophy-of-cognitive-behavioural-therapy-cbt-by-donald-robertson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:48:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-philosophy-of-cognitive-behavioural-therapy-cbt-by-donald-robertson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Philosophy of Cognitive-Behavioural Therapy (CBT): Stoic Philosophy as Rational and Cognitive Psychotherapy&amp;rdquo; by Donald Robertson is a comprehensive exploration of the philosophical underpinnings of cognitive-behavioral therapy (CBT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Inner Citadel Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Pierre Hadot</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-inner-citadel-by-pierre-hadot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:38:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-inner-citadel-by-pierre-hadot/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Inner Citadel: The Meditations of Marcus Aurelius&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Pierre Hadot, a renowned philosopher and historian of ancient philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thus Spoke Zarathustra Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Friedrich Nietzsche</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/thus-spoke-zarathustra-by-friedrich-nietzsche/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:27:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/thus-spoke-zarathustra-by-friedrich-nietzsche/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Thus Spoke Zarathustra: A Book for All and None&amp;rdquo; is a philosophical novel written by Friedrich Nietzsche, a prominent German philosopher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Four Agreements Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Don Miguel Ruiz</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-four-agreements-by-don-miguel-ruiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:18:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-four-agreements-by-don-miguel-ruiz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Four Agreements: A Practical Guide to Personal Freedom&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Don Miguel Ruiz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Willpower Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Roy Baumeister and John Tierney</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/willpower-by-roy-baumeister-john-tierney/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:03:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/willpower-by-roy-baumeister-john-tierney/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Willpower: Rediscovering the Greatest Human Strength&amp;rdquo; by Roy Baumeister and John Tierney explores the concept of willpower and its role in achieving personal success and self-control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wooden Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Wooden and Steve Jamison</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wooden-by-john-wooden-steve-jamison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:51:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wooden-by-john-wooden-steve-jamison/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wooden: A Lifetime of Observations and Reflections On and Off the Court&amp;rdquo; is a book written by John Wooden, a renowned basketball coach, and Steve Jamison.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robert Emmons</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/thanks-by-robert-emmons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:40:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/thanks-by-robert-emmons/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Thanks!: How Practicing Gratitude Can Make You Happier&amp;rdquo; by Robert Emmons is a thought-provoking book that explores the power of gratitude and its impact on personal happiness and well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Kerr</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/legacy-by-james-kerr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:29:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/legacy-by-james-kerr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Legacy: What The All Blacks Can Teach Us About The Business Of Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by James Kerr that explores the culture and success of the New Zealand national rugby team, known as the All Blacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to the Good Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - William Irvine</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-guide-to-the-good-life-by-william-irvine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:54:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-guide-to-the-good-life-by-william-irvine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Guide to the Good Life: The Ancient Art of Stoic Joy&amp;rdquo; by William B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Way of the Bodhisattva Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Shantideva</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-bodhisattva-by-shantideva/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:45:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-bodhisattva-by-shantideva/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Way of the Bodhisattva&amp;rdquo; is a profound Mahayana Buddhist text written by the Indian scholar-monk Shantideva in the 8th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Hole Focus Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Isaiah Hankel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/black-hole-focus-by-isaiah-hankel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:34:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/black-hole-focus-by-isaiah-hankel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Black Hole Focus: How Intelligent People Can Create a Powerful Purpose for Their Lives&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Isaiah Hankel, an internationally recognized expert in the field of personal development and leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 10X Rule Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Grant Cardone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-10x-rule-by-grant-cardone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:23:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-10x-rule-by-grant-cardone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 10X Rule: The Only Difference Between Success and Failure&amp;rdquo; by Grant Cardone is a motivational and self-help book that aims to empower readers to take massive action in order to achieve extraordinary success in all areas of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving What Is Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Byron Katie and Stephen Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/loving-what-is-by-byron-katie-stephen-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:14:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/loving-what-is-by-byron-katie-stephen-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Loving What Is: Four Questions That Can Change Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a transformative self-help book written by Byron Katie, with Stephen Mitchell serving as a contributing editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authentic Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Martin Seligman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/authentic-happiness-by-martin-seligman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:54:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/authentic-happiness-by-martin-seligman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Authentic Happiness: Using the New Positive Psychology to Realize Your Potential for Lasting Fulfillment&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book written by Martin Seligman, a renowned psychologist and the founder of positive psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musonius Rufus Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Cynthia King</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/musonius-rufus-by-cynthia-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:43:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/musonius-rufus-by-cynthia-king/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Musanion Rufus: Lectures and Sayings&amp;rdquo; is a collection of teachings and writings by the Stoic philosopher Musonius Rufus, compiled and translated by Cynthia King.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overachievement Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Eliot</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/overachievement-by-john-eliot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:30:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/overachievement-by-john-eliot/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Overachievement: The Science of Working Less to Accomplish More&amp;rdquo; by John Eliot is an interesting book that challenges the traditional belief that hard work and long hours are the keys to success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Leo Buscaglia</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/love-by-leo-buscaglia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:20:20 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/love-by-leo-buscaglia/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Love: What Life Is All About&amp;rdquo; is a captivating and insightful book written by Leo Buscaglia, a renowned author and professor known for his teachings on love and human connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Hypothesis Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jonathan Haidt</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-hypothesis-by-jonathan-haidt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:12:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-hypothesis-by-jonathan-haidt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness Hypothesis: Finding Modern Truth in Ancient Wisdom&amp;rdquo; by Jonathan Haidt is a stimulating book that explores the complex nature of human happiness by combining modern scientific research with ancient philosophical wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Upward Spiral Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alex Korb</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-upward-spiral-by-alex-korb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:54:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-upward-spiral-by-alex-korb/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Upward Spiral: Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time&amp;rdquo; by Alex Korb is a compelling self-help book that explores the relationship between neuroscience and depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Courage Quotient Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robert Biswas-Diener</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-courage-quotient-by-robert-biswas-diener/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:34:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-courage-quotient-by-robert-biswas-diener/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Courage Quotient: How Science Can Make You Braver&amp;rdquo; by Robert Biswas-Diener is a captivating exploration of courage, delving into the science behind this essential human trait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wealth Warrior Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steve Chandler</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wealth-warrior-by-steve-chandler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:23:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wealth-warrior-by-steve-chandler/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wealth Warrior: The Personal Prosperity Revolution&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Steve Chandler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of TED* Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Emerald</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-ted-by-david-emerald/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:08:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-ted-by-david-emerald/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of TED*: *The Empowerment Dynamic&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by David Emerald.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Superman Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Kotler</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-rise-of-superman-by-steven-kotler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:56:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-rise-of-superman-by-steven-kotler/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Rise of Superman: Decoding the Science of Ultimate Human Performance&amp;rdquo; by Steven Kotler is a captivating exploration into the realm of extreme sports and the state of mind known as flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual Economics Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eric Butterworth</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spiritual-economics-by-eric-butterworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:43:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spiritual-economics-by-eric-butterworth/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spiritual Economics: The Principles and Process of True Prosperity&amp;rdquo; by Eric Butterworth is a transformative book that explores the connection between spirituality and prosperity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindset Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Carol Dweck</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mindset-by-carol-dweck/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:28:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mindset-by-carol-dweck/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mindset: The New Psychology of Success&amp;rdquo; by Carol Dweck is a groundbreaking book that explores the concept of mindset and its impact on personal and professional success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enchiridion Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Epictetus</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/enchiridion-by-epictetus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:16:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/enchiridion-by-epictetus/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Enchiridion&amp;rdquo; is a philosophical manual written by the ancient Greek philosopher Epictetus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irresistible Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Adam Alter</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/irresistible-by-adam-alter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:53:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/irresistible-by-adam-alter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Irresistible: The Rise of Addictive Technology and the Business of Keeping Us Hooked&amp;rdquo; by Adam Alter explores the pervasive influence of technology and its addictive nature on our daily lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick with It Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sean Young</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stick-with-it-by-sean-young/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:38:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stick-with-it-by-sean-young/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Stick with It: A Scientifically Proven Process for Changing Your Life - for Good&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Sean Young, a renowned psychologist and expert in the field of behavioral science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psychology of Hope Summary of Key Ideas and Review - C.R. Snyder</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/psychology-of-hope-by-c-r-snyder/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:28:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/psychology-of-hope-by-c-r-snyder/</guid>
      <description>The book &amp;ldquo;Psychology of Hope: You Can Get Here from There&amp;rdquo; by C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Compassion Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Kristin Neff</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/self-compassion-by-kristin-neff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:17:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/self-compassion-by-kristin-neff/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Self-Compassion: The Proven Power of Being Kind to Yourself&amp;rdquo; by Kristin Neff is a good book that explores the concept of self-compassion and its transformative power in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Sleep Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matthew Walker</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/why-we-sleep-by-matthew-walker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:08:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/why-we-sleep-by-matthew-walker/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Why We Sleep: Unlocking the Power of Sleep and Dreams&amp;rdquo; is a captivating and insightful book written by Matthew Walker, a renowned sleep scientist and professor of neuroscience and psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Agency Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Anthony Rao</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-agency-by-anthony-rao/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:59:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-agency-by-anthony-rao/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Agency: The 7 Principles to Conquer Obstacles, Make Effective Decisions, and Create a Life on Your Own Terms&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Anthony Rao, a psychologist with over 20 years of experience working with children and families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pathways to Bliss Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joseph Campbell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/pathways-to-bliss-by-joseph-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:51:52 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/pathways-to-bliss-by-joseph-campbell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Pathways to Bliss: Mythology and Personal Transformation&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Joseph Campbell, a renowned mythologist and comparative religion scholar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seneca&#39;s Letters from a Stoic Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Seneca</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/seneca-s-letters-from-a-stoic-by-seneca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:43:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/seneca-s-letters-from-a-stoic-by-seneca/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Seneca&amp;rsquo;s Letters from a Stoic&amp;rdquo; is a collection of letters written by the ancient Roman philosopher Seneca to his friend Lucilius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Doris Kearns Goodwin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leadership-by-doris-kearns-goodwin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:33:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leadership-by-doris-kearns-goodwin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Leadership: In Turbulent Times&amp;rdquo; is a compelling non-fiction book written by Doris Kearns Goodwin, a renowned historian and Pulitzer Prize-winning author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Excellence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ben Bergeron</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/chasing-excellence-by-ben-bergeron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:58:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/chasing-excellence-by-ben-bergeron/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Chasing Excellence: A Story About Building the World&amp;rsquo;s Fittest Athletes&amp;rdquo; by Ben Bergeron is a compelling book that delves into the world of competitive CrossFit and provides insights on building a mindset of excellence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tools Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Phil Stutz and Barry Michels</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-tools-by-phil-stutz-barry-michels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:09:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-tools-by-phil-stutz-barry-michels/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Tools: 5 Tools to Help You Find Courage, Creativity, and Willpower—and Inspire You to Live Life in Forward Motion&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Phil Stutz and Barry Michels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Science of Getting Rich Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Wallace Wattles</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-science-of-getting-rich-by-wallace-wattles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:58:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-science-of-getting-rich-by-wallace-wattles/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Science of Getting Rich&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Wallace Wattles and first published in 1910.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daring Greatly Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brené Brown</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/daring-greatly-by-brene-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:40:09 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/daring-greatly-by-brene-brown/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Daring Greatly: How the Courage to Be Vulnerable Transforms the Way We Live, Love, Parent, and Lead&amp;rdquo; is a transformative book written by Brené Brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solving the Procrastination Puzzle Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Timothy Pychyl</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/solving-the-procrastination-puzzle-by-timothy-pychyl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:22:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/solving-the-procrastination-puzzle-by-timothy-pychyl/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Solving the Procrastination Puzzle: A Concise Guide to Strategies for Change&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Timothy A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With Winning in Mind Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Lanny Bassham</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/with-winning-in-mind-by-lanny-bassham/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:08:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/with-winning-in-mind-by-lanny-bassham/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;With Winning in Mind&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Lanny Bassham, a renowned sports psychologist and Olympic gold medalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win Forever Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Pete Carroll, Yogi Roth and Kristoffer Garin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/win-forever-by-pete-carroll-yogi-roth-kristoffer-garin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:58:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/win-forever-by-pete-carroll-yogi-roth-kristoffer-garin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Win Forever: Live, Work, and Play Like a Champion&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and self-help book written by Pete Carroll, Yogi Roth, and Kristoffer Garin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Minimalism Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Cal Newport</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/digital-minimalism-by-cal-newport/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:43:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/digital-minimalism-by-cal-newport/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Digital Minimalism: Choosing a Focused Life in a Noisy World&amp;rdquo; by Cal Newport is a thought-provoking book that delves into the impact of digital technology on our lives and offers a framework for reclaiming control over our attention and time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Way of the SEAL Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mark Divine and Allyson Machate</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-seal-by-mark-divine-allyson-machate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:31:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-way-of-the-seal-by-mark-divine-allyson-machate/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Way of the SEAL: Think Like an Elite Warrior to Lead and Succeed&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Mark Divine, a former Navy SEAL commander, and Allyson Machate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/flow-by-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:09:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/flow-by-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Flow: The Psychology of Optimal Experience&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book written by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi, a renowned psychologist and researcher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Think Like Leonardo da Vinci Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Gelb</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-think-like-leonardo-da-vinci-by-michael-gelb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:00:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-think-like-leonardo-da-vinci-by-michael-gelb/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Think Like Leonardo da Vinci: Seven Steps to Genius Every Day&amp;rdquo; by Michael Gelb is a fascinating exploration of the genius of Leonardo da Vinci and provides practical guidance on how to cultivate the same kind of thinking in our own lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ed Diener and Robert Biswas Diener</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happiness-by-ed-diener-robert-biswas-diener/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 05:46:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happiness-by-ed-diener-robert-biswas-diener/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Happiness: Unlocking the Mysteries of Psychological Wealth&amp;rdquo; is an intriguing book written by Ed Diener and Robert Biswas-Diener.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Champions Think Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Bob Rotella</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-champions-think-by-bob-rotella/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 05:06:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-champions-think-by-bob-rotella/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How Champions Think: In Sports and in Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by renowned sports psychologist Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Taking Action Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gregg Krech</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-taking-action-by-gregg-krech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:45:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-taking-action-by-gregg-krech/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Art of Taking Action: Lessons from Japanese Psychology&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Gregg Krech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superhuman by Habit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tynan</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/superhuman-by-habit-by-tynan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:34:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/superhuman-by-habit-by-tynan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Superhuman by Habit: A Guide to Becoming the Best Possible Version of Yourself, One Tiny Habit at a Time&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Tynan, an influential blogger and author in the personal development space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbeatable Mind Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mark Divine</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/unbeatable-mind-by-mark-divine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:25:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/unbeatable-mind-by-mark-divine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Unbeatable Mind: Forge Resiliency and Mental Toughness to Succeed at an Elite Level&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by former Navy SEAL Mark Divine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atomic Habits Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Clear</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/atomic-habits-by-james-clear/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:13:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/atomic-habits-by-james-clear/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Atomic Habits: An Easy &amp;amp; Proven Way to Build Good Habits &amp;amp; Break Bad Ones&amp;rdquo; by James Clear is a self-help book that explores the power of small habits and incremental changes in achieving personal and professional growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ego Is the Enemy Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ryan Holiday</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/ego-is-the-enemy-by-ryan-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 03:58:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/ego-is-the-enemy-by-ryan-holiday/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ego Is the Enemy&amp;rdquo; is an intellectually challenging book written by Ryan Holiday, an author known for his insightful works on Stoicism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Takes What It Takes Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Trevor Moawad and Andy Staples</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/it-takes-what-it-takes-by-trevor-moawad-andy-staples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 03:48:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/it-takes-what-it-takes-by-trevor-moawad-andy-staples/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It Takes What It Takes: How to Think Neutrally and Gain Control of Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book co-authored by Trevor Moawad, a renowned mental conditioning coach, and Andy Staples, a sports journalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Ownership Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jocko Willink and Leif Babin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/extreme-ownership-by-jocko-willink-leif-babin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 03:32:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/extreme-ownership-by-jocko-willink-leif-babin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Extreme Ownership: How U.S. Navy SEALs Lead and Win&amp;rdquo; is a book written by former Navy SEAL officers Jocko Willink and Leif Babin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Your Zone Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Lardon</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/finding-your-zone-by-michael-lardon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 03:14:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/finding-your-zone-by-michael-lardon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Finding Your Zone: Ten Core Lessons for Achieving Peak Performance in Sports and Life&amp;rdquo; by Michael Lardon is a book that explores the principles and strategies behind achieving peak performance in sports and various aspects of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Good They Can&#39;t Ignore You Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Cal Newport</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/so-good-they-can-t-ignore-you-by-cal-newport/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:58:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/so-good-they-can-t-ignore-you-by-cal-newport/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You: Why Skills Trump Passion in the Quest for Work You Love&amp;rdquo; by Cal Newport is a thought-provoking book that challenges the commonly held belief that passion is the key to finding meaningful work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Be A 3% Man Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Corey Wayne</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-a-3-man-by-corey-wayne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 06:23:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-a-3-man-by-corey-wayne/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How To Be A 3% Man: Winning The Heart Of The Woman Of Your Dreams&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Corey Wayne aimed at men who desire to improve their dating and relationship skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oxygen Advantage Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Patrick McKeown</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-oxygen-advantage-by-patrick-mckeown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:41:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-oxygen-advantage-by-patrick-mckeown/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Oxygen Advantage: Simple, Scientifically Proven Breathing Techniques to Help You Become Healthier, Slimmer, Faster, and Fitter&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Patrick McKeown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spartan Up! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joe De Sena</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spartan-up-by-joe-de-sena/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:32:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spartan-up-by-joe-de-sena/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spartan Up!: A Take-No-Prisoners Guide to Overcoming Obstacles and Achieving Peak Performance in Life&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and self-help book written by Joe De Sena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Compound Effect Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Darren Hardy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-compound-effect-by-darren-hardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:22:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-compound-effect-by-darren-hardy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Compound Effect: Jumpstart Your Income, Your Life, Your Success&amp;rdquo; by Darren Hardy is a self-help book that explores the power of small, consistent actions and their cumulative impact on achieving success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything is Figureoutable Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Marie Forleo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/everything-is-figureoutable-by-marie-forleo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:13:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/everything-is-figureoutable-by-marie-forleo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Everything is Figureoutable&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Marie Forleo, a renowned entrepreneur, writer, and motivational speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Selected Writings of Ralph Waldo Emerson Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ralph Waldo Emerson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-selected-writings-of-ralph-waldo-emerson-by-ralph-waldo-emerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:03:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-selected-writings-of-ralph-waldo-emerson-by-ralph-waldo-emerson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Selected Writings of Ralph Waldo Emerson&amp;rdquo; is a compilation of essays, speeches, and poems by the renowned American philosopher, essayist, and poet, Ralph Waldo Emerson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jefferson Bible Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thomas Jefferson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-jefferson-bible-by-thomas-jefferson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:50:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-jefferson-bible-by-thomas-jefferson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Jefferson Bible: The Life and Morals of Jesus of Nazareth&amp;rdquo; is a unique work by Thomas Jefferson, the third President of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying Not to Try Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Edward Slingerland</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/trying-not-to-try-by-edward-slingerland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:39:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/trying-not-to-try-by-edward-slingerland/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Trying Not to Try: Ancient China, Modern Science, and the Power of Spontaneity&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Edward Slingerland that explores the concept of wu-wei, a central idea in ancient Chinese philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The How of Happiness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sonja Lyubomirsky</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-how-of-happiness-by-sonja-lyubomirsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:28:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-how-of-happiness-by-sonja-lyubomirsky/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The How of Happiness: A New Approach to Getting the Life You Want&amp;rdquo; by Sonja Lyubomirsky is a self-help book that explores the science of happiness and provides practical strategies to cultivate happiness in one&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Visions Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Edward Hoffman and Abraham Maslow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/future-visions-by-edward-hoffman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:17:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/future-visions-by-edward-hoffman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Future Visions: The Unpublished Papers of Abraham Maslow&amp;rdquo; is a captivating book written by Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gratitude Works! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robert A. Emmons</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/gratitude-works-by-robert-emmons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:05:19 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/gratitude-works-by-robert-emmons/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Gratitude Works!: A 21-Day Program for Creating Emotional Prosperity&amp;rdquo; by Robert A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happier Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tal Ben-Shahar</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happier-by-tal-ben-shahar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 15:52:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happier-by-tal-ben-shahar/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Happier: Learn the Secrets to Daily Joy and Lasting Fulfillment&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Tal Ben-Shahar, a former Harvard University professor and expert in positive psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Positive Thinking Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Norman Vincent Peale</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-positive-thinking-by-norman-vincent-peale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 16:53:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-positive-thinking-by-norman-vincent-peale/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Positive Thinking&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Norman Vincent Peale and first published in 1952.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gary Vaynerchuk</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/jab-jab-jab-right-hook-by-gary-vaynerchuk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 16:47:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/jab-jab-jab-right-hook-by-gary-vaynerchuk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Gary Vaynerchuk, a serial entrepreneur and marketing expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crushing It! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gary Vaynerchuk</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/crushing-it-by-gary-vaynerchuk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 08:46:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/crushing-it-by-gary-vaynerchuk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Crushing It!: How Great Entrepreneurs Build Their Business and Influence-and How You Can, Too&amp;rdquo; is a bestselling self-help book written by entrepreneur and social media expert Gary Vaynerchuk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Amy Cuddy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/presence-by-amy-cuddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 15:18:09 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/presence-by-amy-cuddy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Presence: Bringing Your Boldest Self to Your Biggest Challenges&amp;rdquo; is a book written by social psychologist Amy Cuddy published in 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Stephen R. Covey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-7-habits-of-highly-effective-people-by-stephen-covey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 17:26:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-7-habits-of-highly-effective-people-by-stephen-covey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Stephen R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Positive Thinking Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gabriele Oettingen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rethinking-positive-thinking-by-gabriele-oettingen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 20:42:20 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rethinking-positive-thinking-by-gabriele-oettingen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Rethinking Positive Thinking: Inside the New Science of Motivation&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Gabriele Oettingen, a professor of psychology at New York University and the University of Hamburg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tao Te Ching Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Lao Tzu and Ursula Le Guin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/tao-te-ching-by-lao-tzu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 17:50:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/tao-te-ching-by-lao-tzu/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Tao Te Ching&amp;rdquo; is a classic Chinese text believed to have been written by Lao Tzu, a philosopher and poet, in the 6th century BC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Anders Ericsson and Robert Pool</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/peak-by-anders-ericsson-and-robert-pool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 13:37:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/peak-by-anders-ericsson-and-robert-pool/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Peak: Secrets from the New Science of Expertise&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Anders Ericsson and Robert Pool, published in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Analects Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Confucius</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-analects-by-confucius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 19:32:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-analects-by-confucius/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Analects&amp;rdquo; is a collection of sayings and ideas attributed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rumi Daylight Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Camille Adams Helminski</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rumi-daylight-by-camille-helminski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:25:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/rumi-daylight-by-camille-helminski/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Rumi Daylight: A Daybook of Spiritual Guidance&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Camille Adams Helminski, an author, translator, and spiritual teacher who has focused much of her work on the teachings of Rumi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Movement Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Kelly McGonigal</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-joy-of-movement-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 19:02:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-joy-of-movement-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Joy of Movement: How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Kelly McGonigal, a health psychologist and lecturer at Stanford University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Habits Summary of Key Ideas and Review - B.J. Fogg</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/tiny-habits-by-bj-fogg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:17:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/tiny-habits-by-bj-fogg/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Tiny Habits: The Small Changes That Change Everything&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dhammapada Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-dhammapada-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 16:52:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-dhammapada-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Dhammapada&amp;rdquo; is a collection of sayings of the Buddha in verse form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Angela Duckworth</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/grit-by-angela-duckworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:27:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/grit-by-angela-duckworth/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Grit: The Power of Passion and Perseverance&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Angela Duckworth, a psychologist and professor at the University of Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bhagavad Gita Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-bhagavad-gita-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 11:10:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-bhagavad-gita-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Bhagavad Gita&amp;rdquo; is a Hindu scripture that contains a dialogue between the warrior Arjuna and his charioteer Krishna, who is actually an incarnation of the Hindu god Vishnu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Shortness of Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Seneca</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/on-the-shortness-of-life-by-seneca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 17:32:54 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/on-the-shortness-of-life-by-seneca/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;On the Shortness of Life&amp;rdquo; is a philosophical essay by the Roman Stoic philosopher Seneca, originally written in Latin around the year 49 AD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Stoic Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ryan Holiday and Stephen Hanselman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-daily-stoic-by-ryan-holiday-and-stephen-hanselman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 15:04:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-daily-stoic-by-ryan-holiday-and-stephen-hanselman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Daily Stoic: 366 Meditations on Wisdom, Perseverance, and the Art of Living&amp;rdquo; by Ryan Holiday and Stephen Hanselman is a modern-day guide to Stoic philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles: Life and Work Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ray Dalio</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/principles-life-and-work-by-ray-dalio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 21:17:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/principles-life-and-work-by-ray-dalio/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Principles: Life and Work&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Ray Dalio, who is the founder of the investment firm Bridgewater Associates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Discourses Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Epictetus</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-discourses-by-epictetus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 14:19:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-discourses-by-epictetus/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Discourses&amp;rdquo; is a collection of lectures given by the Stoic philosopher Epictetus, transcribed and compiled by his pupil, Arrian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man&#39;s Search For Meaning Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Viktor Frankl</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mans-search-for-meaning-by-viktor-frankl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 09:25:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mans-search-for-meaning-by-viktor-frankl/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Man&amp;rsquo;s Search for Meaning: An Introduction to Logotherapy&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Viktor Frankl, a psychiatrist and Holocaust survivor, first published in 1946.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditations Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Marcus Aurelius</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/meditations-by-marcus-aurelius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 23:08:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/meditations-by-marcus-aurelius/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Meditations&amp;rdquo; is a book written by the Roman emperor Marcus Aurelius, in which he reflects on his personal philosophy of life and offers practical advice on how to live a good and virtuous life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivation and Personality Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Abraham Maslow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/motivation-and-personality-by-abraham-maslow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 20:19:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/motivation-and-personality-by-abraham-maslow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Motivation and Personality&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Abraham Maslow and published in 1954.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Together Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Suzann Pawelski and James O. Pawelski</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happy-together-by-suzann-pawelski-and-james-pawelski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 10:32:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/happy-together-by-suzann-pawelski-and-james-pawelski/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Happy Together: Using the Science of Positive Psychology to Build Love That Lasts&amp;rdquo; by Suzann Pileggi Pawelski and James O.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Coaching Habit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Bungay Stanier</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-coaching-habit-by-michael-bungay-stanier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 11:12:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-coaching-habit-by-michael-bungay-stanier/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Coaching Habit: Say Less, Ask More And Change the Way You Lead Forever&amp;rdquo; by Michael Bungay Stanier is a bestselling book that has revolutionized the way leaders approach coaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinventing Yourself Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steve Chandler</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/reinventing-yourself-by-steve-chandler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 08:13:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/reinventing-yourself-by-steve-chandler/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Reinventing Yourself: How to Become the Person You&amp;rsquo;ve Always Wanted to Be&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Steve Chandler, a motivational speaker and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Nicomachean Ethics Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Aristotle</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-nicomachean-ethics-by-aristotle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 08:12:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-nicomachean-ethics-by-aristotle/</guid>
      <description>The book is one of Aristotle&amp;rsquo;s most well-known works, and it focuses on the nature of ethics and moral behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fifth Agreement Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Don Miguel Ruiz and Don Jose Ruiz</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-fifth-agreement-by-don-miguel-ruiz-and-don-jose-ruiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 06:31:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-fifth-agreement-by-don-miguel-ruiz-and-don-jose-ruiz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Fifth Agreement: A Practical Guide to Self-Mastery&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Don Miguel Ruiz and his son Don Jose Ruiz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Rules For Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jordan Peterson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/12-rules-for-life-by-jordan-peterson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:07:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/12-rules-for-life-by-jordan-peterson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;12 Rules for Life: An Antidote to Chaos&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book by Canadian clinical psychologist and psychology professor Jordan Peterson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stillness Is the Key Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ryan Holiday</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stillness-is-the-key-by-ryan-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 10:55:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/stillness-is-the-key-by-ryan-holiday/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Stillness Is the Key&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Ryan Holiday that explores the power of stillness and mindfulness in modern life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Work Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Cal Newport</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/deep-work-by-cal-newport/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 10:55:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/deep-work-by-cal-newport/</guid>
      <description>In &amp;ldquo;Deep Work: Rules for Focused Success in a Distracted World&amp;rdquo; by Cal Newport, the author explores the concept of deep work and its importance in today&amp;rsquo;s world of constant distractions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flourish Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Martin Seligman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/flourish-by-martin-seligman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 09:59:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/flourish-by-martin-seligman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Flourish: A Visionary New Understanding of Happiness and Well-being&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Martin Seligman, a psychologist and researcher who is known for his work on the topic of positive psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
