<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Summaries by Mark Wheeler on Shortened Books</title>
    <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/contributors/mark-wheeler/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book Summaries by Mark Wheeler on Shortened Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:06:17 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shortenedbooks.com/contributors/mark-wheeler/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advice Not Given Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mark Epstein</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/advice-not-given-by-mark-epstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:06:17 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/advice-not-given-by-mark-epstein/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Advice Not Given: A Guide to Getting Over Yourself&amp;rdquo; by Mark Epstein is an exploration of the intersection between Eastern philosophy, psychology, and personal growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Mental Training Summary of Key Ideas and Review - DC Gonzalez</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-mental-training-by-dc-gonzalez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 23:13:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-mental-training-by-dc-gonzalez/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Art of Mental Training&amp;rdquo; is a powerful and insightful book that delves into the world of mental training and its profound impact on achieving performance excellence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miracle Morning Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Hal Elrod</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-morning-by-hal-elrod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 19:36:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-morning-by-hal-elrod/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Miracle Morning: The Not-So-Obvious Secret Guaranteed to Transform Your Life (Before 8 AM)&amp;rdquo; by Hal Elrod is a self-help book that presents a transformative morning routine designed to enhance personal development and improve various aspects of one&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strangest Secret Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Earl Nightingale</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-strangest-secret-by-earl-nightingale/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:43:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-strangest-secret-by-earl-nightingale/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Strangest Secret&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Earl Nightingale, a renowned author, motivational speaker, and radio personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Concentration Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Theron Dumont</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-concentration-by-theron-dumont/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:23:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-concentration-by-theron-dumont/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Concentration&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Theron Dumont, a pseudonym for William Walker Atkinson, a prominent figure in the New Thought movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acting with Power Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Deborah Gruenfeld</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/acting-with-power-by-deborah-gruenfeld/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:56:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/acting-with-power-by-deborah-gruenfeld/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Acting with Power: Why We Are More Powerful Than We Believe&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book written by Deborah Gruenfeld, a social psychologist and professor at Stanford Graduate School of Business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Heart and the Fist Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-heart-and-the-fist-by-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:26:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-heart-and-the-fist-by-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Heart and the Fist: The Education of a Humanitarian, the Making of a Navy SEAL&amp;rdquo; is a memoir written by Eric Greitens, detailing his personal journey from a humanitarian to becoming a Navy SEAL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Life a Masterpiece Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Orison Swett Marden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/making-life-a-masterpiece-by-orison-swett-marden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:00:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/making-life-a-masterpiece-by-orison-swett-marden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Making Life a Masterpiece&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Orison Swett Marden, a renowned author and founder of Success Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Get Fat Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gary Taubes</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/why-we-get-fat-by-gary-taubes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:55:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/why-we-get-fat-by-gary-taubes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Why We Get Fat: And What to Do About It&amp;rdquo; is a stimulating and provocative book written by Gary Taubes, an investigative science journalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Executive Toughness Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jason Selk</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/executive-toughness-by-jason-selk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:34:46 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/executive-toughness-by-jason-selk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Executive Toughness: The Mental-Training Program to Increase Your Leadership Performance&amp;rdquo; by Jason Selk is a self-help book that aims to provide readers with practical strategies and techniques to enhance their leadership skills and mental toughness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastery Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robert Greene</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastery-by-robert-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:23:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastery-by-robert-greene/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mastery&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Robert Greene. Drawing inspiration from the lives of historical figures such as Leonardo da Vinci, Thomas Edison, and Albert Einstein, Greene explores the concept of mastery and provides guidance on how individuals can achieve greatness in their chosen fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louder than Words Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Todd Henry</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/louder-than-words-by-todd-henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 19:15:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/louder-than-words-by-todd-henry/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Louder than Words: Harness the Power of Your Authentic Voice&amp;rdquo; by Todd Henry is a compelling book that explores the importance of finding and expressing your authentic voice in a world filled with noise and distractions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Your Brain, Change Your Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Daniel Amen</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/change-your-brain-change-your-life-by-daniel-amen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:04:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/change-your-brain-change-your-life-by-daniel-amen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Change Your Brain, Change Your Life: The Breakthrough Program for Conquering Anxiety, Depression, Obsessiveness, Lack of Focus, Anger, and Memory Problems&amp;rdquo; is a transformative self-help book written by Daniel G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mental Edge Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Kenneth Baum</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-mental-edge-by-kenneth-baum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:48:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-mental-edge-by-kenneth-baum/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Mental Edge: Maximize Your Sports Potential with the Mind-Body Connection&amp;rdquo; by Kenneth Baum is a comprehensive guide that explores the powerful relationship between the mind and body in the context of sports performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bounce Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Matthew Syed</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bounce-by-matthew-syed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:00:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bounce-by-matthew-syed/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Bounce: Mozart, Federer, Picasso, Beckham, and the Science of Success&amp;rdquo; is a captivating book written by Matthew Syed, a British journalist and former professional table tennis player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 15 Invaluable Laws of Growth Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Maxwell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-15-invaluable-laws-of-growth-by-john-maxwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:05:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-15-invaluable-laws-of-growth-by-john-maxwell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 15 Invaluable Laws of Growth: Live Them and Reach Your Potential&amp;rdquo; by John C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miracle of Right Thought Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Orison Swett Marden</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-of-right-thought-by-orison-swett-marden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:04:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-miracle-of-right-thought-by-orison-swett-marden/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Miracle of Right Thought&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Orison Swett Marden, a renowned author and motivational speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Entrepreneur Roller Coaster Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Darren Hardy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-entrepreneur-roller-coaster-by-darren-hardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:39:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-entrepreneur-roller-coaster-by-darren-hardy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Entrepreneur Roller Coaster: It&amp;rsquo;s Your Turn to #JoinTheRide&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and practical guide written by Darren Hardy, a successful entrepreneur, speaker, and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outliers Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Malcolm Gladwell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/outliers-by-malcolm-gladwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:57:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/outliers-by-malcolm-gladwell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Outliers: The Story of Success&amp;rdquo; is a non-fiction book written by Malcolm Gladwell, a renowned journalist and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choke Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Sian Beilock</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/choke-by-sian-beilock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:28:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/choke-by-sian-beilock/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Choke: What the Secrets of the Brain Reveal About Getting It Right When You Have To&amp;rdquo; is an excellent book written by Sian Beilock, a cognitive scientist and expert in the field of performance psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Road to Character Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Brooks</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-road-to-character-by-david-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 12:47:42 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-road-to-character-by-david-brooks/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Road to Character&amp;rdquo; is a nonfiction book written by David Brooks, a renowned journalist and cultural commentator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living Forward Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Hyatt and Daniel Harkavy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/living-forward-by-michael-hyatt-daniel-harkavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:17:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/living-forward-by-michael-hyatt-daniel-harkavy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Living Forward: A Proven Plan to Stop Drifting and Get the Life You Want&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Michael Hyatt and Daniel Harkavy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seventh Sense Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joshua Cooper Ramo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-seventh-sense-by-joshua-cooper-ramo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:30:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-seventh-sense-by-joshua-cooper-ramo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Seventh Sense: Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks&amp;rdquo; by Joshua Cooper Ramo is an intellectually challenging book that explores the concept of the seventh sense, a heightened awareness and understanding of the interconnectivity and dynamics of networks in our modern world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Common Denominator of Success Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Albert Gray</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/new-common-denominator-of-success-by-albert-gray/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:00:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/new-common-denominator-of-success-by-albert-gray/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The New Common Denominator of Success&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Albert E.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sitting Kills, Moving Heals Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Joan Vernikos</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sitting-kills-moving-heals-by-joan-vernikos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 05:38:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sitting-kills-moving-heals-by-joan-vernikos/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sitting Kills, Moving Heals: How Everyday Movement Will Prevent Pain, Illness, and Early Death—and Exercise Alone Won&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rdquo; by Joan Vernikos is a groundbreaking book that challenges the conventional belief that exercise alone is enough to counteract the negative effects of a sedentary lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leading an Inspired Life Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jim Rohn</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leading-an-inspired-life-by-jim-rohn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:47:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/leading-an-inspired-life-by-jim-rohn/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Leading an Inspired Life&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and self-help book written by Jim Rohn, a renowned entrepreneur, speaker, and author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Smarter Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Shawn Stevenson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sleep-smarter-by-shawn-stevenson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 16:44:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sleep-smarter-by-shawn-stevenson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sleep Smarter: 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to A Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success&amp;rdquo; by Shawn Stevenson is a comprehensive guide that explores the importance of sleep and provides practical strategies to optimize sleep quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Becoming a Leader Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Warren Bennis</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/on-becoming-a-leader-by-warren-bennis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 16:00:42 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/on-becoming-a-leader-by-warren-bennis/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;On Becoming a Leader&amp;rdquo; by Warren Bennis is a book that explores the essential qualities and skills required to become an effective leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Leadership Challenge Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Kouzes and Barry Posner</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-leadership-challenge-by-james-kouzes-barry-posner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:27:42 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-leadership-challenge-by-james-kouzes-barry-posner/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Leadership Challenge: How to Make Extraordinary Things Happen in Organizations&amp;rdquo; by James Kouzes and Barry Posner is a renowned leadership book that explores the principles and practices of effective leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effortless Healing Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dr. Joseph Mercola</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/effortless-healing-by-joseph-mercola/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:39:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/effortless-healing-by-joseph-mercola/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Effortless Healing: 9 Simple Ways to Sidestep Illness, Shed Excess Weight, and Help Your Body Fix Itself&amp;rdquo; by Joseph Mercola is a comprehensive guide that offers practical advice and actionable strategies to optimize health and support the body&amp;rsquo;s natural healing abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Creative Anxiety Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eric Maisel</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastering-creative-anxiety-by-eric-maisel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 10:56:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/mastering-creative-anxiety-by-eric-maisel/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mastering Creative Anxiety: 24 Lessons for Writers, Painters, Musicians, and Actors from America&amp;rsquo;s Foremost Creativity Coach&amp;rdquo; by Eric Maisel is a self-help book that addresses the common anxieties and challenges faced by creative individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Achievement Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brian Tracy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/maximum-achievement-by-brian-tracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 08:02:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/maximum-achievement-by-brian-tracy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Maximum Achievement: Strategies and Skills That Will Unlock Your Hidden Powers to Succeed&amp;rdquo; by Brian Tracy is a self-help book that aims to guide readers toward unlocking their full potential and achieving maximum success in various areas of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movement Matters Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Katy Bowman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/movement-matters-by-katy-bowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:49:28 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/movement-matters-by-katy-bowman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Movement Matters: Essays on Movement Science, Movement Ecology, and the Nature of Movement&amp;rdquo; is an engaging book written by Katy Bowman, a renowned biomechanist and movement educator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fail Fast, Fail Often Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ryan Babineaux and John Krumboltz</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fail-fast-fail-often-by-ryan-babineaux-john-krumboltz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:36:03 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fail-fast-fail-often-by-ryan-babineaux-john-krumboltz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fail Fast, Fail Often: How Losing Can Help You Win&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Ryan Babineaux and John Krumboltz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strength in the Storm Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/strength-in-the-storm-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:01:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/strength-in-the-storm-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Strength in the Storm: Transform Stress, Live in Balance and Find Peace of Mind&amp;rdquo; by Eknath Easwaran is a self-help book that offers practical guidance and wisdom for managing stress and finding inner peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Breathing Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Al Lee and Don Campbell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/perfect-breathing-by-al-lee-don-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:56:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/perfect-breathing-by-al-lee-don-campbell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Perfect Breathing: Transform Your Life One Breath at a Time&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Al Lee and Don Campbell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wired to Create Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Scott Barry Kaufman and Carolyn Gregoire</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wired-to-create-by-scott-barry-kaufman-carolyn-gregoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:57:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wired-to-create-by-scott-barry-kaufman-carolyn-gregoire/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wired to Create: Unraveling the Mysteries of the Creative Mind&amp;rdquo; by Scott Barry Kaufman and Carolyn Gregoire is a captivating exploration of the creative process and the inner workings of the creative mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coaching the Mental Game Summary of Key Ideas and Review - H. A. Dorfman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/coaching-the-mental-game-by-h-a-dorfman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:26:39 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/coaching-the-mental-game-by-h-a-dorfman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Coaching the Mental Game: Leadership Philosophies and Strategies for Peak Performance in Sports—and Everyday Life&amp;rdquo; by H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head Strong Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dave Asprey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/head-strong-by-dave-asprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 08:39:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/head-strong-by-dave-asprey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Head Strong: The Bulletproof Plan to Activate Untapped Brain Energy to Work Smarter and Think Faster—in Just Two Weeks&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Dave Asprey, the creator of the Bulletproof Diet and Bulletproof Coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Plant Paradox Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Gundry</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-plant-paradox-by-steven-gundry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 07:42:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-plant-paradox-by-steven-gundry/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Plant Paradox: The Hidden Dangers in &amp;ldquo;Healthy&amp;rdquo; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Steven Gundry, a renowned heart surgeon and medical researcher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Religion Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dalai Lama</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/beyond-religion-by-dalai-lama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:55:48 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/beyond-religion-by-dalai-lama/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Beyond Religion: Ethics for a Whole World&amp;rdquo; is a book written by the 14th Dalai Lama, Tenzin Gyatso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripping over the Truth Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Travis Christofferson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/tripping-over-the-truth-by-travis-christofferson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:21:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/tripping-over-the-truth-by-travis-christofferson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Tripping over the Truth: How the Metabolic Theory of Cancer Is Overturning One of Medicine&amp;rsquo;s Most Entrenched Paradigms&amp;rdquo; by Travis Christofferson is an insightful book that challenges the traditional understanding of cancer and explores the metabolic theory of the disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Sell Is Human Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Daniel Pink</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/to-sell-is-human-by-daniel-pink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 09:22:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/to-sell-is-human-by-daniel-pink/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;To Sell Is Human: The Surprising Truth About Moving Others&amp;rdquo; by Daniel Pink is a thought-provoking book that challenges traditional notions of selling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lead Yourself First Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Raymond Kethledge and Michael Erwin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/lead-yourself-first-by-raymond-kethledge-michael-erwin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:22:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/lead-yourself-first-by-raymond-kethledge-michael-erwin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Lead Yourself First: Inspiring Leadership Through Solitude&amp;rdquo; by Raymond Kethledge and Michael Erwin explores the concept of solitude as a powerful tool for leadership development and personal growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix Your Feet Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Philip Maffetone</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fix-your-feet-by-philip-maffetone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:50:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fix-your-feet-by-philip-maffetone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fix Your Feet: Build the Best Foundation for Healthy, Pain-Free Knees, Hips, and Spine&amp;rdquo; by Philip Maffetone is a comprehensive guide that focuses on the importance of foot health and its impact on the overall well-being of the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win or Learn Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Kavanagh</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/win-or-learn-by-john-kavanagh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:29:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/win-or-learn-by-john-kavanagh/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Win or Learn: MMA, Conor McGregor &amp;amp; Me: A Trainer&amp;rsquo;s Journey&amp;rdquo; is a captivating book written by John Kavanagh, the renowned mixed martial arts (MMA) coach of Conor McGregor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Artist&#39;s Journey Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Pressfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-artist-s-journey-by-steven-pressfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:20:12 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-artist-s-journey-by-steven-pressfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Artist&amp;rsquo;s Journey: The Wake of the Hero&amp;rsquo;s Journey and the Lifelong Pursuit of Meaning&amp;rdquo; by Steven Pressfield explores the creative process and the artist&amp;rsquo;s journey to find meaning and fulfillment in their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody Wants to Read Your Sh*t Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Pressfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/nobody-wants-to-read-your-sh-t-by-steven-pressfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 17:04:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/nobody-wants-to-read-your-sh-t-by-steven-pressfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Nobody Wants to Read Your Sh*t: And Other Tough-Love Truths to Make You a Better Writer&amp;rdquo; by Steven Pressfield is a book that offers valuable insights and practical advice to aspiring writers who are struggling to gain recognition for their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Down a Dream Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tim Grahl</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/running-down-a-dream-by-tim-grahl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:52:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/running-down-a-dream-by-tim-grahl/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Running Down a Dream: Your Road Map To Winning Creative Battles&amp;rdquo; is a motivational and practical guidebook written by Tim Grahl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Many Ways to Say I Love You Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Fred Rogers</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/many-ways-to-say-i-love-you-by-fred-rogers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 15:21:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/many-ways-to-say-i-love-you-by-fred-rogers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Many Ways to Say I Love You: Wisdom for Parents and Children from Mister Rogers&amp;rdquo; is a heartwarming book that compiles insightful thoughts and advice from Fred Rogers, the beloved host of the television show &amp;ldquo;Mister Rogers&amp;rsquo; Neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Passion Paradox Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Brad Stulberg and Steve Magness</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-passion-paradox-by-brad-stulberg-steve-magness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:48:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-passion-paradox-by-brad-stulberg-steve-magness/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Passion Paradox: A Guide to Going All In, Finding Success, and Discovering the Benefits of an Unbalanced Life&amp;rdquo; by Brad Stulberg and Steve Magness is an exploration of the complex relationship between passion, success, and fulfillment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indistractable Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Nir Eyal</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/indistractable-by-nir-eyal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:28:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/indistractable-by-nir-eyal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Indistractable: How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Nir Eyal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superheroes and Philosophy Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Morris and Matt Morris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/superheroes-and-philosophy-by-tom-morris-matt-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:14:51 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/superheroes-and-philosophy-by-tom-morris-matt-morris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Superheroes and Philosophy: Truth, Justice, and the Socratic Way&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking book co-authored by Tom Morris and Matt Morris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Be a Stoic Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Massimo Pigliucci</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-a-stoic-by-massimo-pigliucci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 11:02:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-a-stoic-by-massimo-pigliucci/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Be a Stoic: Using Ancient Philosophy to Live a Modern Life&amp;rdquo; by Massimo Pigliucci is an interesting book that explores the practical application of Stoic philosophy in the modern world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Character Strengths Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ryan Niemiec and Robert Mcgrath</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-character-strengths-by-ryan-niemiec-robert-mcgrath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 10:44:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-character-strengths-by-ryan-niemiec-robert-mcgrath/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Character Strengths: Appreciate and Ignite Your Positive Personality&amp;rdquo; by Ryan Niemiec and Robert McGrath is a self-help book that explores the concept of character strengths and their impact on personal well-being and success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Healthy Deviant Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Pilar Gerasimo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-healthy-deviant-by-pilar-gerasimo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 10:14:04 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-healthy-deviant-by-pilar-gerasimo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Healthy Deviant: A Rule Breaker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Being Healthy in an Unhealthy World&amp;rdquo; by Pilar Gerasimo is a self-help book that challenges conventional wisdom and offers a fresh perspective on health and well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stoic Art of Living Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Tom Morris</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-stoic-art-of-living-by-tom-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 08:17:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-stoic-art-of-living-by-tom-morris/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Stoic Art of Living: Inner Resilience and Outer Results&amp;rdquo; is a philosophical self-help book written by Tom Morris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Genius in All of Us Summary of Key Ideas and Review - David Shenk</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-genius-in-all-of-us-by-david-shenk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 06:26:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-genius-in-all-of-us-by-david-shenk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Genius in All of Us: New Insights into Genetics, Talent, and IQ&amp;rdquo; by David Shenk explores the complex interplay between genetics, environment, and personal effort in shaping human intelligence and talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Fragility Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robin DiAngelo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/white-fragility-by-robin-diangelo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 05:50:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/white-fragility-by-robin-diangelo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;White Fragility: Why It&amp;rsquo;s So Hard for White People to Talk About Racism&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking and influential book written by Robin DiAngelo, an American author, lecturer, and diversity trainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sapiens Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Yuval Noah Harari</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sapiens-by-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:55:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sapiens-by-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind&amp;rdquo; by Yuval Noah Harari is a captivating exploration of the history of Homo sapiens, from the emergence of our species in Africa to the present day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sea Stories Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Admiral William McRaven</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sea-stories-by-admiral-william-mcraven/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:40:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/sea-stories-by-admiral-william-mcraven/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sea Stories: My Life in Special Operations&amp;rdquo; is a captivating memoir written by Admiral William McRaven, a retired U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Learning Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Josh Waitzkin</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-learning-by-josh-waitzkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:17:45 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-art-of-learning-by-josh-waitzkin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Art of Learning: An Inner Journey to Optimal Performance&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Josh Waitzkin, a former child prodigy in chess who later became a world champion in martial arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organize Tomorrow Today Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jason Selk, Tom Bartow and Matthew Rudy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/organize-tomorrow-today-by-jason-selk-tom-bartow-matthew-rudy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:00:09 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/organize-tomorrow-today-by-jason-selk-tom-bartow-matthew-rudy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Organize Tomorrow Today: 8 Ways to Retrain Your Mind to Optimize Performance at Work and in Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Jason Selk, Tom Bartow, and Matthew Rudy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Thich Nhat Hanh</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fear-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:36:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/fear-by-thich-nhat-hanh/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fear: Essential Wisdom for Getting Through the Storm&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Thich Nhat Hanh, a renowned Buddhist monk, peace activist, and teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Think Like a Roman Emperor Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Donald Robertson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-think-like-a-roman-emperor-by-donald-robertson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:14:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-think-like-a-roman-emperor-by-donald-robertson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Think Like a Roman Emperor: The Stoic Philosophy of Marcus Aurelius&amp;rdquo; by Donald Robertson is a compelling exploration of Stoic philosophy through the lens of the life and teachings of the Roman Emperor Marcus Aurelius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Monk Who Sold His Ferrari Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robin Sharma</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-monk-who-sold-his-ferrari-by-robin-sharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:19:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-monk-who-sold-his-ferrari-by-robin-sharma/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Monk Who Sold His Ferrari: A Fable About Fulfilling Your Dreams &amp;amp; Reaching Your Destiny&amp;rdquo; by Robin Sharma is a motivational and engaging self-help book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Alter Ego Effect Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Todd Herman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-alter-ego-effect-by-todd-herman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 08:40:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-alter-ego-effect-by-todd-herman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Alter Ego Effect: The Power of Secret Identities to Transform Your Life&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Todd Herman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Worked for Me Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Colin Powell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/it-worked-for-me-by-colin-powell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 08:30:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/it-worked-for-me-by-colin-powell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It Worked for Me: In Life and Leadership&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Colin Powell, a retired four-star general in the United States Army and former U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning Pro Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Pressfield</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/turning-pro-by-steven-pressfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 06:35:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/turning-pro-by-steven-pressfield/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Turning Pro: Tap Your Inner Power and Create Your Life&amp;rsquo;s Work&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Steven Pressfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Russell Simmons and Chris Morrow</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/do-you-by-russell-simmons-chris-morrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:45:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/do-you-by-russell-simmons-chris-morrow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do You!: 12 Laws to Access the Power in You to Achieve Happiness and Success&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Russell Simmons, a successful entrepreneur and co-founder of Def Jam Recordings, and Chris Morrow, a writer and entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness of Pursuit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Chris Guillebeau</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-of-pursuit-by-chris-guillebeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:38:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-of-pursuit-by-chris-guillebeau/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness of Pursuit: Finding the Quest That Will Bring Purpose to Your Life&amp;rdquo; by Chris Guillebeau is a self-help book that explores the concept of quests and how they can bring purpose and happiness to one&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Spirit Medicine Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Alberto Villoldo</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/one-spirit-medicine-by-alberto-villoldo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:01:33 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/one-spirit-medicine-by-alberto-villoldo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;One Spirit Medicine: Ancient Ways to Ultimate Wellness&amp;rdquo; is a transformative guide written by Alberto Villoldo, a renowned medical anthropologist and shamanic healer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Full Engagement Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jim Loehr and Tony Schwartz</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-full-engagement-by-jim-loehr-tony-schwartz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:20:21 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-power-of-full-engagement-by-jim-loehr-tony-schwartz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Power of Full Engagement: Managing Energy, Not Time, Is the Key to High Performance and Personal Renewal&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Jim Loehr and Tony Schwartz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 80/20 Principle Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Richard Koch</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-80-20-principle-by-richard-koch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:03:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-80-20-principle-by-richard-koch/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The 80/20 Principle&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Richard Koch, a British author and management consultant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Joseph Campbell Companion Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joseph Campbell</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-joseph-campbell-companion-by-joseph-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 07:59:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/a-joseph-campbell-companion-by-joseph-campbell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A Joseph Campbell Companion: Reflections on the Art of Living&amp;rdquo; is a collection of essays, interviews, and lectures by Joseph Campbell, a renowned mythologist, writer, and lecturer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Upside of Stress Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Kelly McGonigal</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-upside-of-stress-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:31:47 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-upside-of-stress-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Upside of Stress: Why Stress Is Good for You, and How to Get Good at It&amp;rdquo; by Kelly McGonigal is a groundbreaking book that challenges the traditional negative perception of stress and offers a fresh perspective on its benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spark Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Ratey and Eric Hagerman</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spark-by-john-ratey-eric-hagerman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 05:08:15 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/spark-by-john-ratey-eric-hagerman/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spark: The Revolutionary New Science of Exercise and the Brain&amp;rdquo; is a book written by John Ratey, a renowned psychiatrist, and Eric Hagerman, a journalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolution Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Joe Manganiello</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/evolution-by-joe-manganiello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:41:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/evolution-by-joe-manganiello/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Evolution: The Cutting-Edge Guide to Breaking Down Mental Walls and Building the Body You&amp;rsquo;ve Always Wanted&amp;rdquo; is a self-help and fitness book written by Joe Manganiello.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Willpower Instinct Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Kelly McGonigal</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-willpower-instinct-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:26:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-willpower-instinct-by-kelly-mcgonigal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Willpower Instinct: How Self-Control Works, Why It Matters, and What You Can Do to Get More of It&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Kelly McGonigal, a health psychologist and lecturer at Stanford University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Character Strengths Matter Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Shannon Polly and Kathryn Britton</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/character-strengths-matter-by-shannon-polly-kathryn-britton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:46:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/character-strengths-matter-by-shannon-polly-kathryn-britton/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Character Strengths Matter: How to Live a Full Life&amp;rdquo; by Shannon Polly and Kathryn Britton is a book that explores the concept of character strengths and how they can be harnessed to live a more fulfilling and meaningful life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bored and Brilliant Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Manoush Zomorodi</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bored-and-brilliant-by-manoush-zomorodi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:09:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/bored-and-brilliant-by-manoush-zomorodi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Bored and Brilliant: How Spacing Out Can Unlock Your Most Productive and Creative Self&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Manoush Zomorodi, a journalist and podcast host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling Upward Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Richard Rohr</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/falling-upward-by-richard-rohr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 15:26:59 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/falling-upward-by-richard-rohr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Falling Upward: A Spirituality for the Two Halves of Life&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Richard Rohr, a Franciscan priest and renowned spiritual teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Inner Game of Tennis Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Timothy Gallwey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-inner-game-of-tennis-by-timothy-gallwey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:28:14 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-inner-game-of-tennis-by-timothy-gallwey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Inner Game of Tennis: The Classic Guide to the Mental Side of Peak Performance&amp;rdquo; by Timothy Gallwey is a groundbreaking book that explores the psychological aspects of tennis and how they can be applied to improve overall performance in sports and life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EntreLeadership Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Dave Ramsey</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/entreleadership-by-dave-ramsey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 12:36:39 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/entreleadership-by-dave-ramsey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;EntreLeadership: 20 Years of Practical Business Wisdom from the Trenches&amp;rdquo; by Dave Ramsey is a comprehensive guide that combines the principles of entrepreneurship and leadership to help individuals build successful businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gandhi the Man Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Eknath Easwaran</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/gandhi-the-man-by-eknath-easwaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:43:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/gandhi-the-man-by-eknath-easwaran/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Gandhi the Man: How One Man Changed Himself to Change the World&amp;rdquo; by Eknath Easwaran is a profound exploration of the life and teachings of Mahatma Gandhi, the influential leader of India&amp;rsquo;s nonviolent independence movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ONE Thing Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Gary Keller and Jay Papasan</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-one-thing-by-gary-keller-jay-papasan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:12:52 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-one-thing-by-gary-keller-jay-papasan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The ONE Thing: The Surprisingly Simple Truth About Extraordinary Results&amp;rdquo; by Gary Keller and Jay Papasan is a self-help book that focuses on the power of focusing on one thing at a time to achieve extraordinary results in all areas of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Inner Citadel Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Pierre Hadot</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-inner-citadel-by-pierre-hadot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:38:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-inner-citadel-by-pierre-hadot/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Inner Citadel: The Meditations of Marcus Aurelius&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Pierre Hadot, a renowned philosopher and historian of ancient philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wooden Summary of Key Ideas and Review - John Wooden and Steve Jamison</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wooden-by-john-wooden-steve-jamison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:51:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/wooden-by-john-wooden-steve-jamison/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wooden: A Lifetime of Observations and Reflections On and Off the Court&amp;rdquo; is a book written by John Wooden, a renowned basketball coach, and Steve Jamison.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Leo Buscaglia</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/love-by-leo-buscaglia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:20:20 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/love-by-leo-buscaglia/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Love: What Life Is All About&amp;rdquo; is a captivating and insightful book written by Leo Buscaglia, a renowned author and professor known for his teachings on love and human connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Hypothesis Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Jonathan Haidt</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-hypothesis-by-jonathan-haidt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:12:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-happiness-hypothesis-by-jonathan-haidt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Happiness Hypothesis: Finding Modern Truth in Ancient Wisdom&amp;rdquo; by Jonathan Haidt is a stimulating book that explores the complex nature of human happiness by combining modern scientific research with ancient philosophical wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Superman Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Steven Kotler</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-rise-of-superman-by-steven-kotler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:56:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-rise-of-superman-by-steven-kotler/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Rise of Superman: Decoding the Science of Ultimate Human Performance&amp;rdquo; by Steven Kotler is a captivating exploration into the realm of extreme sports and the state of mind known as flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enchiridion Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Epictetus</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/enchiridion-by-epictetus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:16:01 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/enchiridion-by-epictetus/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Enchiridion&amp;rdquo; is a philosophical manual written by the ancient Greek philosopher Epictetus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/flow-by-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:09:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/flow-by-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Flow: The Psychology of Optimal Experience&amp;rdquo; is a groundbreaking book written by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi, a renowned psychologist and researcher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Think Like Leonardo da Vinci Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Gelb</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-think-like-leonardo-da-vinci-by-michael-gelb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:00:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-think-like-leonardo-da-vinci-by-michael-gelb/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to Think Like Leonardo da Vinci: Seven Steps to Genius Every Day&amp;rdquo; by Michael Gelb is a fascinating exploration of the genius of Leonardo da Vinci and provides practical guidance on how to cultivate the same kind of thinking in our own lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atomic Habits Summary of Key Ideas and Review - James Clear</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/atomic-habits-by-james-clear/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:13:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/atomic-habits-by-james-clear/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Atomic Habits: An Easy &amp;amp; Proven Way to Build Good Habits &amp;amp; Break Bad Ones&amp;rdquo; by James Clear is a self-help book that explores the power of small habits and incremental changes in achieving personal and professional growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Good They Can&#39;t Ignore You Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Cal Newport</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/so-good-they-can-t-ignore-you-by-cal-newport/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:58:30 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/so-good-they-can-t-ignore-you-by-cal-newport/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You: Why Skills Trump Passion in the Quest for Work You Love&amp;rdquo; by Cal Newport is a thought-provoking book that challenges the commonly held belief that passion is the key to finding meaningful work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Be A 3% Man Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Corey Wayne</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-a-3-man-by-corey-wayne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 06:23:35 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/how-to-be-a-3-man-by-corey-wayne/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How To Be A 3% Man: Winning The Heart Of The Woman Of Your Dreams&amp;rdquo; is a self-help book written by Corey Wayne aimed at men who desire to improve their dating and relationship skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Selected Writings of Ralph Waldo Emerson Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Ralph Waldo Emerson</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-selected-writings-of-ralph-waldo-emerson-by-ralph-waldo-emerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:03:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-selected-writings-of-ralph-waldo-emerson-by-ralph-waldo-emerson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Selected Writings of Ralph Waldo Emerson&amp;rdquo; is a compilation of essays, speeches, and poems by the renowned American philosopher, essayist, and poet, Ralph Waldo Emerson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gratitude Works! Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Robert A. Emmons</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/gratitude-works-by-robert-emmons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:05:19 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/gratitude-works-by-robert-emmons/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Gratitude Works!: A 21-Day Program for Creating Emotional Prosperity&amp;rdquo; by Robert A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presence Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Amy Cuddy</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/presence-by-amy-cuddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 15:18:09 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/presence-by-amy-cuddy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Presence: Bringing Your Boldest Self to Your Biggest Challenges&amp;rdquo; is a book written by social psychologist Amy Cuddy published in 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Analects Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Confucius</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-analects-by-confucius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 19:32:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-analects-by-confucius/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Analects&amp;rdquo; is a collection of sayings and ideas attributed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Angela Duckworth</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/grit-by-angela-duckworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:27:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/grit-by-angela-duckworth/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Grit: The Power of Passion and Perseverance&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Angela Duckworth, a psychologist and professor at the University of Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Discourses Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Epictetus</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-discourses-by-epictetus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 14:19:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-discourses-by-epictetus/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Discourses&amp;rdquo; is a collection of lectures given by the Stoic philosopher Epictetus, transcribed and compiled by his pupil, Arrian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Coaching Habit Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Michael Bungay Stanier</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-coaching-habit-by-michael-bungay-stanier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 11:12:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-coaching-habit-by-michael-bungay-stanier/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Coaching Habit: Say Less, Ask More And Change the Way You Lead Forever&amp;rdquo; by Michael Bungay Stanier is a bestselling book that has revolutionized the way leaders approach coaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Nicomachean Ethics Summary of Key Ideas and Review - Aristotle</title>
      <link>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-nicomachean-ethics-by-aristotle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 08:12:38 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shortenedbooks.com/summaries/the-nicomachean-ethics-by-aristotle/</guid>
      <description>The book is one of Aristotle&amp;rsquo;s most well-known works, and it focuses on the nature of ethics and moral behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
